<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Deep Water Solo on Imperial College Mountaineering</title><link>YAYAYA/tags/deep-water-solo/</link><description>Recent content in Deep Water Solo on Imperial College Mountaineering</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="YAYAYA/tags/deep-water-solo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Summer Tour 2011</title><link>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/0.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Summer Tour 2011" /&gt;&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;10 members of Imperial College Mountaineering Club travelled to the sunny
island of Mallorca from the 12th to the 25th September. Not for the cheap thrills of
Shagaluf but for the vast amounts of climbing on offer. While on tour many
different areas were visited with all sorts of climbing on offer from caves to slabs.
Some members achieved very highly whereas others had a less fortunate time.
The aims and objectives of the tour were for members to climb in a different
environment to those that they are used to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Mallorca the climbing was all sport
or deep water soloing which are less common in the UK. There were also some
longer multi pitch routs that members enjoyed climbing. Due to unforeseen
circumstances 2 members had to use their recently acquired advanced first aid
skills to help one team member out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall Mallorca was an excellent location to visit. There was a wide range of
grades from very easy to very hard. A lot of the very interesting routs were
harder than many members could climb. Despite being a relatively small island
there was a significant amount of driving. We managed to take advantage of
cheap villas due to the off peak season and found some cheap car rental places,
food was also remarkably low cost. We all learnt the hard way that accidents can
happen, even when not doing a particularly difficult climb and we must always
be aware of hazards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/5.jpg"
alt="Top Row: Ruth, Jon, Ali, Lisa, Ollie, Elliot, Murray. Bottom Row: Tristan, Abi, Fails" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Top Row: Ruth, Jon, Ali, Lisa, Ollie, Elliot, Murray. Bottom Row: Tristan, Abi, Fails&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="people"&gt;People
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The people going on the tour were:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Matthew Lees (Murray) - President&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mike Jones (Fails) – Vice President&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jonathan Price&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alastair Brash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lisa Alhadeff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elliot Carrington&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tristan Pollitt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruth Lawson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Abi Attrell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oliver Mower&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="diary"&gt;Diary
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="day-1--flight"&gt;Day 1 – Flight
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;With 10 members flying from all over the country to Palma it was quite
remarkable that all but one person had met in the country just after noon. The
one member who had decided to take a later flight for a sweet deal wouldn’t
arrive until much later that night and cause much unnecessary driving, the fuel
for which probably cancelled out his own saving. Picking up the cars turned out
to be not as simple as expected, the rental firm was too cheap to buy a place in
the airport and needed a bus to get there. The cars however were very cheap
and were already scratched and dented, as a bonus hey came with free
insurance meaning we wouldn’t get fined for bumping the car.
Driving out of Palma proved to be difficult but after a scenic drive around the city
the motorway was found and the other side of the island quickly reached.
Arriving at the accommodation Ali was convinced that the lead diver Murray was
completely lost but was surprised when it turned out that they had arrived at
their accommodation. The villa was perfect for the club needs and was very
cheap. Classic ICMC Chilli was had for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/0.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-2--el-fumat"&gt;Day 2 – El Fumat
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first crag to be visited on the trip was
thought to be a local crag called El Fumat,
but turned out to be the other side of a
mountain so there was some slow uphill
diving. The crag had excellent views and
was well bolted. Most members found the
grades to be hard; this was probably due
to the new location and tiredness. On the
menu for dinner was Curry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-3--les-perxes"&gt;Day 3 – Les Perxes
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The area chosen today had a couple of
different crags. Most of the group went to
the easier section near the car park called
Hairpin but Ali and Lisa decided to go for
the cave nearby. The easy crag got sun
around 2 and became too hot for climbing,
the cave being north facing remained cool
all day. Some members decided to go
watch the cave climbing and take photos but others went to the higher crag that
had a little bit more shade.
Ali managed to climb an impressive climb up with some good tufa action and a
nice rest in the middle. One of the local climbers then crushed it while warming
up for a much harder climb. Carbonara was on the table tonight, there was much
debate over what the ingredients should be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/1.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-4--deep-water-solo"&gt;Day 4 – Deep Water Solo
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Being the tour’s first venture into DWS an easy small crag was chosen. There
were 3 routs on the smallest section; the 6a was enjoyable and easy and done by
most. The water was very clear and we could easily see that the bottom was
a long way down There was a good 7a with a cool dino in the middle which
many people fell off. Some members quickly decided they didn’t like DWS
and others needed to work on jumping off to get over a fear of height. Some
members had no problem jumping off the cliffs but had some minor issues
entering the water.
At the top of the cliff there was a mast, probably used for sailing the island
to new locations, where we left all of our food and bags. Ali, Ruth and Lisa
managed to hit their heads on the mast; unfortunately since they were not
climbing at this point in time they didn’t have helmets on, all 3 felt very silly.
A DWS dinghy was bought to help get people to the bottom of the climbs
and to rescue them in case something went wrong. Various names were put
forward, there were: Lizzie Wilkins, Fun Splash, Enema, Ella and Emma. After
some debate the name Ella stuck, it was later revealed that this was also the
name of Jacob Dean’s 12 year old sister, after this the innuendos came thick and
fast. Fajitas were for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/2.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-5--rest-day-1"&gt;Day 5 – Rest day 1
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people slept in late this day after some early starts on the previous days.
Everyone except Ali went for a walk along the coast but Ali remained behind to
do a literature review. While walking a large number of naked people were seen,
this was highly disturbing. An old abandoned pill box was found and explored, it
was very hot inside. Finding a small cover everyone sat down and had a lovely
time playing in the water. Murray kicked a rock while swimming and bled all over
the place. Fails annoyed a sea anemone by destroying its home and it got its own
back by stinging Fails, Elliot and Ruth. Since it was Elliot’s last night with us we
had another Chilli to remind him of all the good times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-6--sa-gubia-eastern-side"&gt;Day 6 – Sa Gubia, eastern side
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another early start to get to the crag before the sun hit it. The massive walls of
Sa Gubia were on the table for today. Ali and Lisa decided to have a day alone
and headed over to the steep hard world of Fraguel. After quite a long walk in up
a dry river bed the bottom of the wall was reached where we met 2 local
climbers who gave us a lot of tips about which crags not to visit as they had bad
bolts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 2 best climbs of the day were
a delicate 6a and an outrageous
6a+ which had some cool tufa
action on it. Ali and Lisa also had a
good day out. The group split in 2
with half heading back to make a
curry for dinner and the others
taking Elliot to the airport for him
to head home early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-7--dws--more-sa-gubia"&gt;Day 7 – DWS &amp;amp; more Sa Gubia
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Murray, Jon, fails, Abi and Ollie
headed over to Cala Sa Nau to try
out a different area. There were a
number of easy climbs, fails
managed a 6b but failed on the
7a. Murray tried the 7a from day 4
but ripped the tip of his finer off
on the sloping crimp. Abi jumped
off the top and made a big splash.
Ella was launched; she was a
much finer vessel than the other group who were at the crag.
The climbers at Sa Gubia tried a number of different things. Tristan and Ruth had
a mini adventure on their 2 pitch multi pitch. Ali and Lisa tried a few hard things
with little success. Since it was a Sunday most shops were closed so there was
not a lot of food to be had. Heavy rain made the road outside the apartments
turn into a small river. Since it was Lisa’s last day she decided to get drunk
instead of packing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-8--rest-day-2"&gt;Day 8 – Rest Day 2
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ali got up early to take Lisa to the airport, everyone else stayed in bed for quite a
while. While Ali was sleeping most other people went for a large food shop taking
advantage of Lidl’s cheap prices. After the shop everyone moved to the beach to
enjoy the Mallorca sun. The slack line was put up and everyone had a good go
with various levels of susses, this attracted many tourists who took&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;photos, if a hat had been left out we probably would have made some money.
Towards the end of the day we moved the slack line to two trees that were much
further apart, right at the limit of how far the slack line could reach. While
tensioning the line we melted a section as there was so much force! This line was
very long and wobbled a lot. Murray and Tristan both got about half way on it but
nobody made it the whole length. Some people were scared off by the height of
the line but the soft sand gave a good landing and when it sagged in the middle
it was quite close to the floor anyway. While slack lining Fails failed and landed
with one leg either side of the line and had to sit down for a while, see right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/3.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/4.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-9--the-accident"&gt;Day 9 – The Accident
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ali and Fails headed off to a hard over hanging crag with short boulder like routs.
Everyone else went to Puig St Martin where there was shade all day and easy
climbs. A number of different routes were done. While trying a 5+ with a high first bolt Ollie slipped and hit the ground. He had broken his ankle and mountain
rescue were called to evacuate him. Jon and Murray had both been on the union
run outdoor first aid course which proved very useful. Both tried to check for
broken bones but didn’t feel anything that felt broken, both were carrying first
aid kits but there was little they could do. Four firemen arrived with a stretcher to
carry him out, they were not particularly gentle. Everyone went to visit Ollie that
evening, he was on pain killers at this point and seemed quite merry, fortunately
he had BMC insurance and everything was OK.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-10--dws"&gt;Day 10 – DWS
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abi decided that she wanted to stay with Ollie for the day and keep him company
as being in a foreign hospital. Everyone else decided to go deep water soloing as
there would be nothing to hit and get hurt on. Ali and Fails went to Cala Barques
and everyone else went to Santanyi. Ali and Fails found their perfect climbs of
steep jug climbing with big powerful moves. The others enjoyed their day and
went to visit the legendary Es Pontas and were surprised by how shallow the
water was there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-11--les-perxes-mark-ii"&gt;Day 11 – Les Perxes Mark II
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;A permanent problem with Mallorca was trying to find shady crags where the
heat was not too severe. Port Soller had a large amount of shade but we
discovered building works and so couldn’t climb there. Returning to a previously
visit crag is generally avoided on tour but this area has several sections. Ali and
Fails went to the cave and tried more hard things. Everyone else went to the
upper section called Muro de Caimari. There were several hard climbs done by
all. Ruth and Tristan found an extremely pumpy 6b which was very hard. Ollie
was visited in the evening and this time had a large amount of metal in his leg
after the operation and was in for a bad night sleep. After climbing we took Fails
to the airport as he had found a sweet deal and booked an earlier flight home&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-12--betlem"&gt;Day 12 – Betlem
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Waking to the sound of heavy rain was not a good start to the day. Almost all the
climbing locations would be soaked and the only things able to be climbed would
be caves. Contrary to the malicious propaganda spread by the Outdoor Club we
did not go to a pub, we went climbing instead. A crag called El Calo de Betlem
was decided upon as it had some shelter and easy cave climbs. Arriving at the
crag to find that rock fax lied and only a part of the routes were dry we soldiered
on. Most people tried a cool looking 6b which had some hard moves in it to a
hidden and now sodden slot. While Abi was on top rope an assisted dyno was
attempted with no result. Another nearby area was investigated but the best
routs were slabs that were still wet and there were serious signs of seepage.
Murray and Ruth checked out an abandoned house which had an aloe vera plant
in front that was about 3m tall and you could stand on its branches/leaves.
Setting up a water line over the pool was discussed at length. We found 2 points
that we felt would be suitable anchors and active spotting near the edges of the
pool was also proposed. Unfortunately it was felt that the 2 anchors were too far apart and a water line was not put up. Instead a raft was built from the many
empty water bottles with an impressively poor result.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-13--home-time"&gt;Day 13 – Home Time
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ali and Abi went back to Les Perxes for Ali to try and finish his route. The top slab
was wet and no route finishing happened. Packing the cars with all of our stuff
took a while and lead to a rather uncomfortable trip to the airport. Both cars had
to be returned empty and so the economy race was on. Murrays diesel had only
had 1 ½ tanks of fuel so was already low but made it to the rental drop of shortly
after the fuel light came on. Ali was forced to put in an extra 5 euros of fuel. At
the airport there was a slight challenge convincing the staff that Ollie couldn’t
walk and that he needed a wheel chair. After a large amount of repacking to get
everyone under the weight limit we all ate and drank as much as we could to get
as heavy as possible to reduce the fuel economy of the plane to restore Ryanair’s
karma. Arriving late at Stansted we were all greeted by an enormous line for
border control with some grumpy staff who were extremely unhelpful. We retried
our bags and then all went our separate ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="finances"&gt;Finances
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="cost-breakdown"&gt;Cost Breakdown
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="data-table" role="region" tabindex="0" &gt;
&lt;table class="table %!s(&lt;nil&gt;)" id="987463251"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Income&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Member Income&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£1800&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;ICU Funding&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£410&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="data-table" role="region" tabindex="0" &gt;
&lt;table class="table %!s(&lt;nil&gt;)" id="325681794"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Expenditure&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Consumable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£400&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Accomodation&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£1240&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Car hire&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£370&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Fuel&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£200&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description></item><item><title>Summer Tour 2009</title><link>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/0.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Summer Tour 2009" /&gt;&lt;h2 id="members-who-attended"&gt;Members who attended
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alistair Brash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simon Partridge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tom Coyne&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brigette Atkins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Joergen Myrtroeen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ed Poore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charlene Lawton&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lizzie Wilkins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob Dean&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jonathan Hazell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-1"&gt;Day 1
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the 10 tour members departing from different airports throughout the country everyone
arrived in Alicante Airport, Spain at roughly the same time (varying between 09:30am and 11am
local time). The first port of call was the car rental station where two hire cars were collected. One
being upgraded two stages for free because they didn&amp;rsquo;t have the booked car, thus providing us with
a 7-seater, dubbed the &amp;ldquo;win-car&amp;rdquo; for the rest of the tour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A (theoretical) hour later with some exploration of the Spanish coast led to everyone arriving in the
first villa of the stay, graciously provided by Joergen. Unloading and lunch ensued then reloading
into the cars and off to the beach to find one of the deep-water-soloing crags mentioned in the
guide-books. After some non-existent right-turns eventually an alternative was found and the fun
began.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For many of our members this was the first time they had been deep-water-soloing, climbing
without ropes above the sea, the day ended with a spot of tombstoning from the top of the cliff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-2"&gt;Day 2
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We traveled the short journey down the coast to Sierra de Toix to climb at a place called Toix TV.
After spending thirty minutes driving around the maze of holiday homes, we finally reached the crag
as it began to pour with rain. Climbing began, regardless, with several routes being lead including a
7a (very hard!) lead by Joergen. After this, Tom set off on a route –accessed via a dodgy rope bridge -
but ended up climbing past the lower-off, resulting in a run out traverse and a scramble to safety!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-3"&gt;Day 3
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We set off to Forrada in search of some quality climbing. Four hours later, after driving through
continuous hairpins, we reached a track described in the guide book as “rough in places”. This was
discovered to be something of an understatement!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The climbing at Forrada was fantastic and turned out to be well worth the journey. At least it was
until the monsoon arrived and forced us to shelter in a cave for the next hour, waiting for the rock to
dry. The heavy downpour turned out to be a daily occurrence and always coincided with Brigette
being stranded halfway up a lead. Joergen and Jacob managed to find some more difficult climbing
in an area sheltered from the storm. One particular route (Starman, 7a+) provided them with
conversation for the rest of the week. The journey back to the villa that evening was considerably
shorter due to the saturated soil which allowed us to ‘mud-plane’ back down the track from the
crag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-4"&gt;Day 4
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/1.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We headed back to the Sierra de Toix region but this time to Toix Ouest. Once again it rained in the
afternoon (there is a theme here) so we went back to the villa for lunch. The plan for the afternoon
was to head a short distance from the villa to Echo Valley. Unfortunately we got lost and drove half
an hour into the valleys, ending up at a place that wasn’t in the guide book but did come
recommended by a woman in stripy yellow trousers (clearly a climber). The boulderers among the
group made friends with a local man-of -the-crag who showed them the best traverse in the area
whilst chain smoking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-5"&gt;Day 5
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the antics of the previous three days, it was decided we should take a rest day. We had a lazy
morning by the pool followed by some deep water soloing in the afternoon. It was warmer in the sea
than out, so we swam about before coming home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/2.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/3.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-6"&gt;Day 6
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was our first trip to Sella (the biggest crag in the area) and we were not disappointed. The
routes were amazing. Tom and Brigette started a multipitch but true to form, when Brigette’s
involved, it began to rain as soon as they had both reached the first belay. After much commotion
and a variety of problems, they both abseiled down to safety. Meanwhile, diehard boulderer, Jacob
gets his head for heights as he takes his first fall whilst leading (after much bullying from Alistair and
Joergen).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fresher took a less active approach to the day and made a hammock at the base of the crag. His
creativity got the better of him later in the day when he attempted to make a zip line into the
swimming pool back at the villa. Fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-7"&gt;Day 7
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We went to Echo Playa and for the first time since the first day, the sun was out. Quickly, we realized
that it was too hot and hoped for mild temperatures once again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of us went off to do ‘traditional’ climbing, whilst the others climbed sport routes. By lunch
time everyone was far too hot, so we decided to go back to the villa for a siesta.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, Fresher had a brilliant idea: He built a raft from water bottles and set sail in the
swimming pool. However, his success was short lived as Tom and Jacob bombed him, sinking his
raft!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That night, we moved to a villa in the mountains. Whilst everyone was packing, Fresher managed to
put a large dent in the car. However, he did fix it with his trusty plunger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-8"&gt;Day 8
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jacob, Alistair and Joergen climbed a three pitch route. Joergen, however, left his shoes at home, so
they ended up sharing two pairs between three people, swapping shoes for each pitch. In the
meantime, Charlene and Simon completed their first lead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/4.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That evening ICMC stormed Benidom! We saw the delights that were on offer, Sticky Vicki, The
Mediteraneun Bar to name but two&amp;hellip; We opted for the beach. Simon and the girls somehow ended
up in the sea, partly clothed and Fresher got buried. ICMC returned home, distinctly weter and
sandier than before and settled down for a nice bowl of carrot curry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/5.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/6.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-9"&gt;Day 9
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back to Sierra de Toix again! Spurred on by the previous days multipitch, Fresher, Simon and Brigette
set off on a three pitch excursion. Charlene climbed a route with a rope that was too short to be
lowered off, so had to do some imaginative maneuvers to get down!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By this stage everyone else was bored with Toix and decided to do some more deep-water-soloing,
leaving Fresher and co halfway up their multipitch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-10"&gt;Day 10
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was our last full day of climbing, so we decided to go back to Sella as it was so good before. Tom
and Ed managed to complete the multipitch that they got rained off last time. Charlene and Simon
continued to tick off a number of lead climbs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During late afternoon, there was a massive downpour which resulted in half the group running for
cover and leaving everyone else to pack up all the gear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-11"&gt;Day 11
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last day! The weather was worse than ever, it was raining when we woke up! We packed and
cleaned the house before driving towards Alicante. When we got there it was far too wet to sit on
the beach, so what would a group of university students do in Alicante for a day? Obviously we
found the nearest Toys ’R’Us and set about trying to play with every toy in the shop!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the tour went very well. I would not have made any fundamental changes to the way
it ran, things that could be improved in the future are small organizational things such as being
better at buying the correct amount of food for a large number of people. Financially, the tour broke
even. And a good time was had by all! The only thing that did not go as planned was the fact that it
rained so often! But that being said, we went climbing every day and still had an amazing time.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>