<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Archives on Imperial College Mountaineering</title><link>YAYAYA/categories/archives/</link><description>Recent content in Archives on Imperial College Mountaineering</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="YAYAYA/categories/archives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ICMC Journal 1997</title><link>YAYAYA/p/icmc-journal-1997/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 1997 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/icmc-journal-1997/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;By the editor, Rich Marshall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A journal of ICMC activity from 1997/98 by Rich Marshall, titled &amp;ldquo;Jammin&amp;rsquo;Crack&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The original cover featured a bra attached to someone&amp;rsquo;s buttocks, and was omitted as a reflection of the change in the club since that era.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The full document can be found here:
&lt;a class="link" href="YAYAYA/documents/jammingcracks.pdf" &gt;Click here to download&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="transcription"&gt;Transcription
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="editorial-i-made-this"&gt;Editorial: I MADE THIS
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;As far as I can deduce this happens to be only the third journal in 29 years, the last being printed
in 1974! Amazingly this relic from the past contains stories the traditional last meet of the first tern
(Bosigran!), the dinner meet, an expedition in the Bolivian Andes (with 23 routes climbed, some
potentially 15
ascents!) and talks by Doug Scott (I&amp;quot; ascent of Everest&amp;rsquo;s north face!) Has the club changed
over the years, I ask myself? Well to be honest, NO. There are enough of stories of stopping for &amp;ldquo;spew
stops&amp;rdquo; and disappearing off to far flung corners of the globe with union money only to end up drinking
and pulling to realise we&amp;rsquo;re probably doing them proud! May it continue!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In writing the editorial and having to put the journal together in the first place 16 1S usual to grip
about the hassle and stress of the job. My predecessor described it as &amp;ldquo;one of the lowest orders of the
alhatros&amp;rdquo; next to
&amp;ldquo;grodpole holder&amp;rdquo;! I can assure you however that after one has experienced all emotional
states between fussing (over picture choice) and mad panic (when word crashes again!), this is not the
case. Combine this with a picture of me trying to explain to my Greek female ottice mate exactly why.
have a picture of a bum in a bra on my computer screen and you&amp;rsquo;ll understand that this has been far tron
boring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m now only have my thankyous to left to say. Firstly thanks must go to the exec this year whos
hard work has been reflected through the success of the club, well done. Secondly thanks to Megan who:
bright smile followed by swift punch in the groin has &amp;ldquo;encouraged&amp;rdquo; many people to contribute! Alsc
thanks to Rich Marr who sorted out all the pictures, aren&amp;rsquo;t they cool! A short note of thanks to my
supervisor for not pointing out the obvious fact that I haven&amp;rsquo;t done any work fOr the last two weeks anc
finally thanks to the contributors. without whom I would have been shafted good and proper&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="dinner-meet-dave-makes-a-speech"&gt;Dinner meet: Dave makes a speech
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;ll never get me p*ssed&amp;rdquo; says Dave, as we set off in the bus to the Lake District&amp;hellip; 24 hrs
later, after a bottle of whiskey the fact that he can still stand amazes most people, although getting dressed
proved a little tricky with others having to help out. Mucn amusement coming mom Dave assuring Us n6
can put on his tie himself, yeah right.
Anyway, we arrive for the dinner and ask the waitress for a bucket just in case. Phil Wicken:
makes THE quote, offending the waitresses to the degree that they refuse to serve his table /Typical caver.
Ed./. Dave gets up and makes his speech , which was remarkable coherent considering the whiskey,
Although nobody can remember what he said, was
it the bottle of Tequila? I&amp;rsquo;m just guessing here. We
did however get him to read out the following.
Like wot?
Where do I put mi hands now?
No No No No No!
Sivams
I didn&amp;rsquo;t fit in the crack.
You I never
get me p#ssed
The dinner finished swiftly with the
elections followed by the first of many chats on
the big white telephone. Dave (*5), Rich Marr and
Martin amongst the fallen on the battle scene with
the another 10 or so casualties the following morning. The few trying to get away with a sneaky vomi
didn&amp;rsquo;t manage it. vou will be remembered. Those who managed courageously to keen their stomach
lininas. throuchout the previous night fell at the last post, breakfast. The biggest greasy spoon you have ever seen was served up by the owners of the hut. Consequently many posts were abandoned in the rush to
save respectability, and thanks to the unknown person adding diced carrots to the, much used, dunking
trough. The best excuse going AWOL came from Graham who tried to get away with blaming it on thi
Tequila worm he&amp;rsquo;d eaten, until he realised someone else had drunk it!
Remember the worm 1S out there..
By Graham Cooper and Phil Mayers (Translated into English by the Ed.]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="exiled-to-sg-for-being-silly"&gt;Exiled to S&amp;amp;G for being silly
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some people over the last year have done some very silly things, haven&amp;rsquo;t they? We all know what happens
to you if you do that don&amp;rsquo;t we? Yes, you&amp;rsquo;re exiled to S&amp;amp;G (and if that doesn&amp;rsquo;t teach you a lesson, nothing
will!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="el-chorro-97-bolt-clippers-sunbathe-and-do-brave-stuff"&gt;El chorro &amp;lsquo;97: Bolt clippers sunbathe and do brave stuff
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;It all started one afternoon above a betting shop on Fulham Road. A collection of alcoholics
watching an evening of British cinema including The Italian Job&amp;rsquo; and Monty
Python&amp;rsquo;s .and now for something completely different. This unbounded of
Stupidity was to set the atmosphere for the entire holidav.
A Taxi ride at breakneck
speed in the wee small hours took us to Gatwick airport. where the more enthusiastic
of us raced in luggage trolleys across the deserted terminal.
A plane and a train later we found ourselves in El Chorro (the centre of
nownere) onlv to tind an automobile driver
I by
our gracious host, and rally-driver wannabie
Jean, ready to take us further away tron
anvwhere. The climbing started immediately (although some more
relaxed members of the club decided that they wanted to acclimatise
to the nice weather betore doing anything too strenuous, 1e
sunbathing). El Chorro is a small town on the train line between
Malaga and Seville and is a popular venue for climbers from all
around Europe. The gorge (through which the train line winds its
way) provides varied routes of all grades for beginners and hard-core
climbers alike. with routes anvwhere from 20ft to 400ft in length. In
addition to climbing, the surrounding hills are excellent for mountain
biking.
A 70 vear old steel cable, stretchina diagonallv across the
gorge provided entertainment and photo opportunities as thre
members of the club travelled across (at this point please bear in
mind that the cable is over 100m above a white-water river and is 150m long). Surprisingly enough there were no serious casualties during the trip, (and all of the minor
injuries seemed to be focused on James a rock fell on me&amp;rsquo; Philips). Our honoured treasurer did some
rather impressive shit, and we all cheered. He also fell off, and we cheered again and threw beans at him
Arguably the most epic climb of the trip was a route named El Amptrax, graded French 6a (where 8c is
about the hardest climbable). Amptrax was a route that went up the highest part of the rock and took the
entire day for two pairs of climbers to complete, and included a dramatic overhang on the final pitch
Not all Of our time was spent being macho, tanned, hard-bodj
types. We also spent some time walking in the hills absorbing the beautifu
scenery (yean right), as well as swimming naked in the reservoir just north
of the upper gorge (no seriously we did, apart form the naked bit, I lied
about that) / and the bar, Ed. J. At this point I would like to say that Belay
bunny only had chips (SOrry a personal joke, It&amp;rsquo;s very tunny, trust me). Al
the end or the week we were loath to leave, but with shortening tunas and
looming exams we returned home, with improved personal bests and some nice tans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="les-alpes-sams-epic"&gt;Les alpes: Sam&amp;rsquo;s epic
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quite a few people managed to get out to the Alps this summer (Graham, Ian, James,
sJam
Myself and others/ completing many routes despite the appalling weather experienced. The most notable
assents being the Tour Noir, Aig. L&amp;rsquo;M and the Aig. De Perseverance. With such a large number of climbs
completed the reports from the Alps could have potentially filled the entire journal, so I had to restrict the
number of entries to a single arucie.
My reason for choosing this over other
potential candidates is simply that it
was an epic. It also nappened to De the
same route that the du anoteep
the quotes section. / came trom 2
weeks later when they followed me up
the route. ha. ha. ha. So over to Sam&amp;hellip;
Finally! The weather forecast from the &amp;ldquo;Office de Haute Montagne&amp;rdquo; in Chamonix, predicted a
Clear sunny day. Vur chance had come to do a route on the Aiguille de I&amp;rsquo;M. My climbing partner, Ben and I set off early from the campsite to catch the cable car from the town at 7am to reach the Plan du
&amp;lsquo;Aiguille. We had decided to do a relatively low route (a maximum altitude of 2844m) to avoid the snow
that had built up, but there was still up to a foot of snow on the lower slopes.
We trekked for two hours across small snowfields and glacial moraine. The route we had planned
to do had a bit of snow and ice on it and looked very bad. We had crampons and ice axes with us, but w
decided to do an easier route which Should be in better condition with more sun facing it. After another
trek we finally began climbing the NNE ridge of the M. The route was better, but still had snow coverer
ledges, and climbing in rock shoes made getting over these difficult. A couple of other climbers started to
follow us up, and they turned out to be British.
The first pitches of the climb were alright, but they began to get harder. We soon reached a large
ledge which had lots of snow on it, and I got my feet cold and wet. The next pitch was a small chimner
but it had ice on the inside, which made it difficult to gel
up. Ben lead the ditch and I managed to scramble un it
By the time I reached the top I was thoroughly tired, anc
the weather
Was Star ung to close in. I was temnted to call
it a day and abseil off, but we decided it should be easier
to Keep going to the top, and find the easy walk ont from
there. we could see the English couple were struggling.
but persevering. We continued to the ton, and now the
clouds had come in and it was starting to snow. It was
also getting late and we were in danger of missing the
last cable car down. Finally we reached the top and coulc
nardlv see a counle of metres in front of us Worse still
we couldn&amp;rsquo;t find the route off the top, as there was so much snow, and it looked too dangerous to try
We were soon joined by the other climbers, Roger and Michelle (trom Barnsley), who were alsc
very tired and unsure of the &amp;lsquo;walk out&amp;rsquo; route. Ben and I decided to abseil off the way we had climbed up, as
at least we knew the way. The chance of us catching the cable car was now very slim. We had onlv:
single 50m rope with us so it would take several abseils to get down. We had to leave bits of sling and
cord behind tied around spikes to thread the rope through. We saw the others following us down, but they
were using two 50m ropes tied together.
We reached the large ledge about a third of the way down, when we heard shouts from above. We
stopped and looked up to see Michelle shouting down to us that they had got their ropes jammed,
anC
couldn&amp;rsquo;t budge them. Roger was trying to free them but without any luck. He was about half way down hi.
ropes and quite stuck. While we waited he managed to cut his rope and retie it to abseil dowr
) where
Michelle was waiting. They managed to absell and scramble down to where we were waiting. They only
had two pieces of rope left, about one third of their original length.
It was starting to get dark now, and was still snowing. The four of us abseiled down our rope off
the rest of the mountain. By the time we reached the base, it was black and we had missed the cable car
down by hours. There was nothing for it but to walk down to the valley, 1500m below us.
We only had a few torches with us, and the ground was very difficult with snow to start with
leading onto the glacial moraine, large lumps of granite which are hard to cross. After several hours wt
managed to find a path which eventually led to a track through the forest. We were all extremely
exhausted and stumbling along these rough tracks, often tripping up over rocks and roots. Our torch
batteries were beginning to fade. We kept on going, even though I was tempted just to find a nice bush
and go to sleep under it. We could see the town lights, but they never seemed to get closer. At 2am We
finally reached the campsite and just flopped into bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Sam Downer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="ireland-sea-stacks-dont-jump"&gt;Ireland: sea stacks, don&amp;rsquo;t jump
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having conquered the Alps a couple of weeks previously, the
Spacevan then travelled off to SW Ireland with Graham and I in it. Having
bored the f*ck out of Graham looking for my ancestral home in Cork, we
finally managed to climb a handful of stunning pitches near Killarney in Cr
Kerrv. Even though this part holds the highest mountain in Ireland
(Carrantouhill), the amount of rock climbing is quite limited compared to the
northern and eastern areas (e.g. Wicklow) - which I encourage vou to visit in
the not too distant titure
The highlight of the trip was when Graham almost killed himself
jumping 18m off a sea stack. Soloing up the 30m high stack (about V Diff
was nevertless superb. However, one morning whilst culturing around
Dingle in Kerry, I discovered the true magic of freshly made Irish Soda
Bread.
I have recently discovered a scientific explanation for this magic - it 1:
in the acidity of the buttermilk which reacts with the alkalinity of the soda
making it rise even better! Grabam was not impressed - luckily he didn&amp;rsquo;t have
to suffer this decadence as he had remembered to bring his own strange
variety of bread all the way from the co-op in Devon&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By James &amp;ldquo;NICE&amp;rdquo; Carter&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="postcard-from-lyon-graham-cooper-on-tour"&gt;Postcard from Lyon: Graham Cooper on Tour
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dear Club,
being a keen student, I naturally took the opportunity of spending a year in France at a college in Lyon as
to broaden my horizons and learn the French way of engineering. It had nothing to do witl
the close proximity of the Alps and endless possibilities of routes on rock, snow and ice to explore.
The mountaineering club in Lyon are a good crowd who I met at the year&amp;rsquo;s hirst p&lt;em&gt;ss up, and who
then decided it would be a laugh to invite some English p&lt;/em&gt;sshead, to do some climbing with them. The
year started well with a few easy warm up peaks ( Pic de l&amp;rsquo;tendard, and the Alberon) which gave me
chance to overcome some quite important communication difficulties. These routes were simple glacie:
walks although a little steep in places for the Alberon. After that, before it got too cold we did one
weekend of big rock routes in the Erins massif. this was one of the best weekends I&amp;rsquo;ve had this year and
we did one route high up graded D, and one route the next day of 350m at a level around 6a, quoter
ID/ID+. You hardcore nutter. Ed. I
Unfortunately after that there were lots of parties so I stayed in Lyon. (Two coachloads of
students spending a whole day visiting wine caves accompanied by a less than sober brass band being one
Delore Christmas however, I did manage to spend 5 davs near Chamonix (Cluses&amp;rsquo;
doing some big rock routes (not too high up because it was cold) and a weekend in the Calanques (set
cliffs near Marseilles: reminded me of Devon)
After Christmas the ice chimbing season begins. We are but mortal men, so interspersed with
some climbing a group of us had a go at that to. By halt term we were getting quite reasonable and hadn'1
yet had any fatal injuries, but then one dark night while descending I tripped over and cut my finger. Fully
recovered by half term I did a bit more including Chere Couloir on Mont Blanc du Tacul. /A route I car
personally recommend, Ed./ Finally on the last day I did my first bit of vertical ice which was a cigar of
about 10 meters followed by other smaller vertical passages. [NICE, Ed.] After that all the ice falls fell
down, sometimes with people on them, so we stopped climbing them.
Since half term I&amp;rsquo;ve done a few other things, some skung and ski trekking but what I really want
to do is an approach on skis, then an iced up gully then decent on skis, but the weather hasn&amp;rsquo;t beer
so that will have to walt.
That&amp;rsquo;s about all. I hope you&amp;rsquo;ve had a cool year, and if any one wants to come out to the Alps al
Easter or in the summer, I shall be there all the time. Hope you have a good dinner meet, (worms aren&amp;rsquo;t
good for you).
Also if it&amp;rsquo;s not too late I&amp;rsquo;d like to give the presidents spot a go, so don&amp;rsquo;t forget to vote for me.
cheers Graham Cooper world reputed second rate mountaineer
P.S. This is the longest mail I&amp;rsquo;ve ever written in my life . If it f*cks up and doesn&amp;rsquo;t send I will kill myself.
Sounas like a promise to me, Ed. l
By Graham Cooper (Translated by the editor (again), Ed.].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="cornwall-1-belays-lob"&gt;Cornwall 1: belays lob
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apparently, it&amp;rsquo;s traditional to go to Cornwall for the last trip of the Winter term - and as far as
I&amp;rsquo;m concerned it&amp;rsquo;s a bloody good one! The trip started with having our normal early hours arrival at thr
Count House which was complete with regimented lines of drawing pins, and more rules than a nunnery.
We emerged from our sleeping bags, later that morning (about 4 hours later to be precise) only tc
realise that we had picked the one weekend in the entire Cornish winter that had seen any sun! The
weather outside even managed to motivate Garth to emerge from his bag with less than the customar:
seven thousand curses, insults and threats of death. After a breaktast of porridge/concrete (no one was toc
sure) which really hit the spot (in the bin we were prepared for the long walk into the crag.
Hive ministe
later we were basking in the morning sun and several members of the club wel
re contemplauna takinc
there trousers off (well Rob had seen some prime lamb).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A day of decadent climbing followed, with Megan and Ruth forming the women&amp;rsquo;s liberation
front climbing corps and deciding that all men were bastards on the way up Door-post /I told you not t
let them out of the kitchen, Ed. J. The old school boys managed to find a few routes that they hadn&amp;rsquo;t done
at least twenty times before, while everyone else sampled all the treats Bosigran had in store. Rob jogger
up Anvil Chorus and hauled James P up the last pitch atter him he then announced that VSs were going
OK
so he&amp;rsquo;d try an El (Suicide Wall)
While Rob and Al started Suicide Wall, Ian and myself decided to do
the awesome Anvil chorus - the first pitches were pure climbing pleasure anc
then we got to the infamous layback crack. It was all going fine and I was
about 2/3rds of the way up the crack when I saw the top and went for It. A
purely instinctive reaction, two layback moves (now with a left leg thal
wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have been out of place in an Elvis dance routine) later and I was
covering some serious air miles.. One of my bits of gear decided that it didn&amp;quot;
particularly like being in the rock, in fact it didn&amp;rsquo;t even like being on the rope
and duly detached itself from it, the second held and I bounced on the rope
about and inch or two below the belay ledge
Remarkably lan managed to sustain the worst injury (I was fine) with
a nice little burn mark across his belaying hand (cheers lan). After
establishing that my left leg was now having problems sticking to the ground, let alone the rock (due to
unwanted vibrations that a Union van would be proud of), I decided to ab. down later to get my bit of gear
out. I spent the rest of the day trying to find my bit of projectile gear and seconding up a lovely slab routt
with Al.
While James &amp;ldquo;Nice C and his sous-chet Ruth, worked their magic with a saucepan, we all
buggered off down the pub&amp;hellip; on return we discovered a meal fit for a King, in fact about 500 kings, and
we all tucked in. A night of drinking, smoking and pulling ourselves along the floor with some
professional climbers ensued. followed by another cats chorus (which I&amp;rsquo;m sure the other inhabitants of the
hut appreciated).
The next day was spent in pretty much the same fashion as the first, with me getting my
confidence back and everyone else basking in the second day of lovely sun. We prepared to leave with a
great deal of reluctance, Megan providing entertainment for Sam and Garth - Sam attempting to drown
her in the shower and Gareth performing the first steps of some bizarre mating ritual by wiping a dirty T
towel in
her face (whatever turns you on &amp;rsquo;ehh Megan!). James and Al. sped off in the space-mobile (mark
I while the rest of us chugged back in the van&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;content after vet another corker of a trio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Belav &amp;ldquo;fancy a sweaty little bov&amp;rdquo; Bunnv.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="north-wales-2-98-sheep-and-lots-of-them"&gt;North Wales 2 &amp;lsquo;98: Sheep and lots of them
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last weekend ICMC embarked on their second trip of the year to North Wales. Although just
before the trip the thought of spending two grim days in what I expected to be a very wet and cold Wales
didn&amp;rsquo;t fill me with joy, it turned out to be on of the best weekends ever
We didn&amp;rsquo;t get the weekend off to a great start with most of Friday evening spent waiting for the
AA in our traditional stop at Lutterworth. We were at least kept entertained by watching the locals
smashing
up cars and trying to kill each other, a typical notherners Friday night entertainment
After arriving at the hut fairly late we got off to a typical start, 1.. slept in till the afternoor
When we did get up we went off to the pass and did some great routes, with Simon coming close tr
getting a few more Air Miles (as if he doesn&amp;rsquo;t have enough already). The general feature of most of the
routes was mud and cr*p, inspiring Sam to do a new route and naming it &amp;ldquo;Sam&amp;rsquo;s grassy plateau&amp;rdquo;, nc
Drizes for
guessing what that consisted of.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later it was back to the hut to consume a fantastic meal prepared by James Carter along with vas
amounts of beer/What even you? Ed]. The rest of the evening was
spent planning how best to use the spare keys to S&amp;amp;G&amp;rsquo;s minibus
which we had somehow acquired! Suggestions included ram
raiding the Snowden Honey farm, unfortunately everyone was ta:
to sone to carry anv or them our
Sunday we split up, half climb in Treamadog and the rest
go up to Snowden via the Crib Goch ridge with continuos sunshine
ensuring both parties enjoyed themselves. The day ended with a
complete tour of London on the way back as Dan tried to remembe
exactly where he lived, pronouncing
&amp;ldquo;I must live near Wembley, I
can see the stadium from my house&amp;rdquo; to much hilarity from withir
the bus!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Megan &amp;ldquo;Mancy-Lancy hotpot&amp;rdquo; Bradley.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="lob-of-the-day-the-ants"&gt;Lob of the day: the ants
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three ants carrying a piece of bread slipped on an overhang, although one of them held onto the
rock. the bread and the other two ants. / Climoing in El Chorro is really hard core as you can see, Ea.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By unknown&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="scotty-98-proper-mountaineering"&gt;Scotty &amp;lsquo;98: proper mountaineering
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m sitting in a Scottish hut watching Dam busters waiting for the others to arrive. The weather
being an absolute pig has been blasting the Scottish bills for the last three days with a ferocity greater thar
Jack Russell with a firework up its butt, filing me with a sense of foreboding.
The others duly arrive, a motley crew composed of ICMC and S&amp;amp;G members. Ahhhbh it&amp;rsquo;s a joint
trip with S&amp;amp;G I hear you cry, well you&amp;rsquo;ll just have to bean be later! Antoine, of burning water fame, gets
underway with organising the kitchen whilst the Gear (Alan) organises the gear! All the other S&amp;amp;Gites
loaf about getting in the way with one exception, Hideous Buggar, who manages to do it with such
professionalism others start to question his parentage
An earlv start (up at 6:30! was folled by the weather dumping several inches of snow on the roac
closing giving us half an hour of hilarity watching incompetent skiers mess around. On arriving
annE
Cairngorm car park and trekking in the conditions were found to be excellent leading to many ascenti
over the next few days. These included The Runnel (RH variation), Aladdin&amp;rsquo;s Couloir, Red Gully, Fiacle
Ridge, Broken Gully and Jacobs ladder. The hardest route of the week, Invernookie (LIL/IV) was
completed by the mountaineers, Of course.
Chosen because the guide book describes it as a route that changes little with conditions. A
phrase I now consider to be the biggest lie I&amp;rsquo;ve ever heard, including the excuses for not writing articles!
The first pitch (out of condition) consisted of using 3 lumps of turf to climb 20m of iceless slab.
second pitch (out of condition), lead by Julian consisted of levitating up s &amp;ldquo;powder&amp;rsquo;
steps without
knocking them down on me. The third pitch (out of condition) should have been a near vertical pitch in
kind of broken chimney, ho ho ho what a joke. Instead it involved hooking iceaxes on overhanging rocks
to the left whilst using ice smears for your feet, a technique I learnt very quickly! This was followed by :
small powder filled offwidth with an overhanging wall to the left trine to push vou onto a totally blant
face on the right. How we laughed. tears in our eves. The pitch can only be best characterised by the amount of swearing Julian managed in one breath along with the number of times he forcefully suggestec
I was a f*cking psycho.
The only comfort from this was a sudden heat wave ensured no more routes could be done,
topping the last one would be tricky! This meant the last few days merged into a series of distillery trip:
and bimbling, we had to play along with S&amp;amp;G a little. End of week celebrations gave Antoine the
opportunity to surpass himself with a whiskey a haggis evening to beat all others along with Alan
Claiming a pot prize for managing to pull, something I have never witnessed on a mountaineering trir
hefore&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Rich Marshall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P.S. Best wishes to Julian Rickard in the Himalavas this summer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="cornwall-2-98-nice"&gt;Cornwall 2 &amp;lsquo;98: NICE
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a pretty cool weekend - on arriving at 2 in the morning we camped next to the &amp;ldquo;No
Camping&amp;rdquo; sign in the Chair ladder car park we couldn&amp;rsquo;t be arsed to find anywhere else! After discovering
that most of the tents had certain essential bits missing, we managed to erect some vaguely tent like tents
and collapse into them only to be evicted in the morning by a pointy head with a dog which wanted to get
into James bivvy bag with him! However it did get going nice and early, we were climbing at Sennen by
about 9.30!
Sennen was pretty nifty, the routes are quite hard and exposed for their grade. I did two HSs, on
the first I had to place a bit of pro whilst using an undercut to reach over an overhang (then proceed lc
pull over the overhang!!). On the second I had to swing out onto a large flake, hand traverse along it with
smears for feet and then mantle shelf onto it - with no hand holds to pull on. Phoar, can 1 have your
children? Ed. / It was excellent! I think I might go back in the summer cause it would be gorgeous
without a force 10 gale!! We managed to find a valid campsite after climbing, despite James&amp;rsquo; cained
protestations that we should go to St Ives &amp;ldquo;cause it was NICE&amp;rdquo;!! The site owner however was a old pointy
headed female with the site itself not being much better. Since all the proper sites were shut however it
was a pretty good, cheap place to camp, with a dub up the road.
Sunday we went to Bosigran and while Daffy launched up Door post I sat about getting rained or
by intermittent showers contemplating whether I could be arsed to climb a very slimy Ding. I decided I
couldn&amp;rsquo;t and went for a hard core bimble (hard core since I was carving a 30-40 pound sack!!)/No excuse
join S&amp;amp;G, Ed.I. Of course this was the cue for the sun to arrive for the rest of the day, so when I found a
nice secluded beach in the blazing sun I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist a quick dip. This, of course, caused the entire bas
to suddenly be filled with parents and small children leaving me to run back to my bag (half way up the
beach) in my wet boxers in front of a crowd Wembley would be proud of!! The others, by all accounts
went bouldering in a cove round the corner. After that Alex did his Nigel Mansell impression and drove
all the way back - getting us back before midnight&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By Simon &amp;ldquo;fancy a sweaty little boy&amp;rdquo; Judge&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="baldric-the-sausage"&gt;Baldric the sausage
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once upon a time there was a little sausage named Baldric and he lived happily ever after.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nicked by Rich Marr, dedicated to Simon Judge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="swanny-98-13th-15th-feb-nice"&gt;Swanny &amp;lsquo;98 (13th-15th feb): NICE
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;By far and away one of the best weekends despite a rather low turnout. Upon arriving in Lanator
Matravers, we headed for a rendezvous with Sam in The King&amp;rsquo;s Arms. This turned out to be a counle o
barrels of ale in someone&amp;rsquo;s living room, and we almost apologised for bursting into the landlord&amp;rsquo;s home
before we realised it was the local pub. Our local guide arrived before closing time with the news that Old
Tom&amp;rsquo;s Field was closed, so we set up for the night in Young Sam&amp;rsquo;s Lounge. This is a highly recommender
camp site, but watch out for Sam&amp;rsquo;s chocolate logs. Many thanks to the wardens for the use of their well
mamtamned faculties.
The following morning we took the ferry across to Swanage, a surreal experience in the dense
morning fog and eerily silent and calm waters. After breakfast at Ricky&amp;rsquo;s we checked out the local
shop and agreed to meet back at the bus. As per tradition, we lost Al K and almost left him behind. We
chose to go for the climbs at Winspit because they offered a good range of climbs in some fabulou:
surroundings. Al P and I decided to try a well polished HVS 5b ammonite but by the end of the day it had
managed to defeat all of us. Meanwhile Daffy tackled an excellent VS and Ruth, Sam and Al P had a go at
some bolted E&amp;rsquo;s (blot wendies, Ed.] which were far too exciting. Cursing the bad design of ancient sea
creatures, Al P and I went to try the trad routes by the sea but found them to be a bit wet (and there was :
lot of water too). We returned to the Juarrvman&amp;rsquo;s Wall to nav on the bolted routes instead. At the end of
the day Daffy lobbed fantastically on an HVS he was trying to lead, and Ruth and Al P found a trad route
in the quarry that wasn&amp;rsquo;t apparently in the guide book, and promptly named it Lard Arse.
As the night drew in we decided to head back into Swanage to find a pub. We encountered some
particularly odd locais in The Anchor (even odder than us), and decided to hide from them in the back oi
the pub. However they
probably thought Ruth was pretty odd [and who wouldn&amp;rsquo;t, Ed.] when they heard
her announce that she &amp;ldquo;alwavs noticed when it was in front of her. but didn&amp;rsquo;t notice it from behind&amp;rdquo; and
that &amp;ldquo;doing it forwards is much worse that doing it backwards&amp;rdquo; - abselling of course. We decided to cros:
quickly over to The Swan where we dined and danced the night away to the live music from the rocking
and totally un-valentines band. Finally we staggered back up the hill to camp out under the glittering stars
and sweeping bear of the lighthouse&amp;hellip; or on a log if Daffy had anything to do with putting up the tent!
The next morning we arrived at the country park before the crack of dawn (So that&amp;rsquo;ll be Llish
then? Ed.J. As the sun rose we knew we were in for a fabulous day at the Subluminal cliffs. Al K
promptly established our presence at the cliffs by setting up the &amp;ldquo;Abseil Rope Of Doom&amp;rdquo; just east of the
popular Balcony route. A number of friendly climbers who politely asked to make use of the rope were
seen to struggle back up over the edge of the cliff a few hours later, in an obviously less friendly mood.
The bottom of the abseil involved a lovely near-inverted, &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t wanna break my skull&amp;rsquo;, free-fall finish fo
added amusement factor - thanks Al. This provided excellent practice for those in the group (previously)
not keen on the activity, and prepped us for some excellent climbs on possibly the best coastal crags in the
country. The easier severe route Gangway provided valuable trad gear leading experience for both Daffy
and myself. Later in the day we were joined by other members of ICMC. James took Megan on the climbs
near face, and lan et al. disappeared to look for some nice hard routes /located in the pub perchance:
Ed.J. Ruth, Daffy and Al P tried a mixed up combination of Highstreet and Bypass, and later Megan made
a leisurely lead up the Highstreet (trust a woman to spend ages on the highstreet). When Al K and I got
rudely blocked off an HS route by some other climbers we decided to take a break, but Daffy and Al F
carried on by tackling first Corner. As the day came to its inevitable but unnecessary end, Ruth finishec
off by leading Damo up Curving Crack and after Al K finished his billionth cigry and went to rescue the
infamous ab rope. Of course, he managed to make another spectacular cock-up of the entire operation anc
almost ended up taking a swim (sorry Al but it&amp;rsquo;s true)! He forgot his prusick (essential for ascending), anc
we suspect he used fart power from the previous night&amp;rsquo;s Skull-ache bitter to get back un. Overall an
entertaining day to round off a perfect trip.
Many thanks to Al P for his excellent driving through the fog-scaped nights and WOCdt Woody for organising the trip (And the Banana Joke).
BV Dan&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>An apology to the custodian of StoneHenge</title><link>YAYAYA/p/an-apology-to-the-custodian-of-stonehenge/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 1960 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/an-apology-to-the-custodian-of-stonehenge/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/an-apology-to-the-custodian-of-stonehenge/stonehenge.png" alt="Featured image of post An apology to the custodian of StoneHenge" /&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/an-apology-to-the-custodian-of-stonehenge/stonehenge.png" width="600"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Transcription:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Addressed to: The Chief Custodian, Stonehenge, Wiltshire&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear Sir,
I am writing to apologise on behalf of the Imperial College Mountaineering Club for the inconveniance certain members cause on Monday Morning the 8th of December. We respectfully request that you return our confiscated rope which we need for our expedition to Scotland this Christmas. I enclose a 51-postal order to cover the postage. Again offering my sincere apologies,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yours Faithfully&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Author unknown&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Club archives, 1929-1951</title><link>YAYAYA/p/club-archives-1929-1951/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 1954 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/club-archives-1929-1951/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/club-archives-1929-1951/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Club archives, 1929-1951" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;A compilation of the club&amp;rsquo;s history from 1929-1951 was found in the club archives (a.k.a Box of Doom). You can find tales of the club&amp;rsquo;s early days, the origin of the ULMC club hut in the Peak District, and various accident reports from the 1930&amp;rsquo;s.
&lt;a class="link" href="YAYAYA/documents/icmc_archives_compiled.pdf" &gt;Click here to download&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>