<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>France on Imperial College Mountaineering</title><link>YAYAYA/tags/france/</link><description>Recent content in France on Imperial College Mountaineering</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="YAYAYA/tags/france/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Summer Tour 2021</title><link>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Summer Tour 2021" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Oliver Tippett&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="background"&gt;Background
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="history"&gt;History
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fontainebleau (Font) was used to practice the skills necessary for alpinism since the
1870s, but since the 1930s it has solidly established itself as one of the premier
bouldering destinations in the world. Everywhere you look there is something to
climb, with soft sandy landings and old shoeless Frenchmen offering advice on
technique. The boulders in Font are made of soft sandstone, which often forms very
rounded, chest shaving tops to boulders that can make even the most elegant of
climbers look like a beached whale. It is also world famous for its ridiculously
technical and sandbagged slabs that are incredibly useful for popping an overinflated
ego. It is also home to classic boulders of every grade, from &lt;em&gt;La Marie Rose&lt;/em&gt; (f6a+), to
&lt;em&gt;Carnage&lt;/em&gt; (f7b+) and &lt;em&gt;Rainbow Rocket&lt;/em&gt; (f8a). Moreover, every sector in Font will have
a couple of circuits. These comprise of about 50 easier problems and the aim is to
complete all of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fontainebleau was made famous to us by the movie &lt;em&gt;The Real Thing&lt;/em&gt; , a 1996 classic
full of techno and hard climbing featuring Jerry Moffatt and Ben Moon. In this they
train on the gritstone boulders of Derbyshire and then come over to teach the French
how to climb on their own rock. Spurred on by our club trips to the Peak, we were
determined to make the journey to Font to do the same!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="objectives"&gt;Objectives
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;After more than a year of COVID and lockdowns, our main objective was to be able
to travel abroad safely and responsibly. We all made sure to read up on the current
guidelines about international travel before setting off and adhered to all necessary
testing. It was unfortunate that the associated costs with extra testing in France and
on return to the UK made the trip prohibitively expensive for many potential
attendees. This limited our numbers to a small group of 8, but this served to
strengthen the relationships made within the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also aimed to enjoy ourselves whilst staying safe as well as to sample some of
the French culture and language. This was done with great aplomb at the Lidl bakery
section. We all had our own climbing objectives for the trip, which are detailed below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="the-team"&gt;The Team
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="data-table" role="region" tabindex="0" &gt;
&lt;table class="table %!s(&lt;nil&gt;)" id="732496851"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Name&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Role&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Degree&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Aim&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Olly Tippett&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Tour Leader&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Mech Eng&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;4th&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Do Rainbow Rocket, some circuits and slabs&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Jake Lewis&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Tour Organiser&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Aero&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;4th&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Climb a f7a, 100 boulder problems&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Miguel &amp;ldquo;One Move f7a&amp;rdquo; Boland&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;One Move f7a Eliminate Fetishist&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;One Move f7a training&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;f7a&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Climb a one move f7a eliminate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Emyr Williams&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;The Slab Hero&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Aero&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;4th&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Get back into climbing post COVID and do a full circuit.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;James Gibson&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;The Wad&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Maths&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;3rd&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Flash everyone else&amp;rsquo;s projects&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Chorley King&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Monsieur Dyno&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Aero&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;3rd&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Climb a f7a&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Ben Jones&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;The Medic&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Medicine&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;4th&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Climb a f7 in Font&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;George Gun&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Le Garçon Large&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Des Eng&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;3rd&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Climb a f7a&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="overview-of-the-tour"&gt;Overview of the tour
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="itinerary"&gt;Itinerary
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h4 id="day-1-19921"&gt;Day 1 (19/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first day was spent travelling to Fontainebleau. Olly
drove his van with a few pads to the campsite and set up
in the early afternoon. He was then joined by Miguel,
Jake, James, and Emyr who had driven a separate car
from England. They all set up the brand-new tent and
were excited by its lack of mould and holes. A tarp was
set up from the van to some trees to construct a sitting
area for when it rained. They had just missed the season
for the campsite swimming pool being open, so had to
settle for the occasional shower with poor water pressure. Eager to get climbing, the
early to arrive people ventured out to &lt;em&gt;Gorge aux Chats,&lt;/em&gt; the local crag to the
campsite. There they acquainted themselves with the local rock and attempted the
softest problem in Font, &lt;em&gt;Dallain&lt;/em&gt; (f6c). It was a one move dyno that most people did to
make them feel better about themselves after getting completely shut down by a
desperate f3+ slab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/van.png" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/ben.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a brief tickle of the rocks, Olly had to leave
to pick up Ben and George from the train station.
By the time this was done it was getting dark, so
everyone met back at the campsite. The team
cooked chilli sin carne and ate it very quickly. The
evening concluded with everyone sipping on
cheap tiny French beers, when suddenly the
question arose, where was Chorley?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/jake_ben.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-2-20921"&gt;Day 2 (20/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;That night, everyone could hear the sound of
rain on the tent, signalling a mandatory rest
day. Sandstone is very fragile when wet, so it
is very bad form to try to climb it after rain. This
meant that they decided to walk the 25 mounds
circuit of the forest. It was about 13 miles and
took in 25 hills with over 1000m of vertical
ascent, going through some of the classic
climbing locations. Miguel and Emyr decided to
run this circuit and did so impressively in under
3 hours. The rest got about halfway before
questioning their motivations but had to carry
on as it was the shortest way back. They all arrived back shortly before dark, all
grumpy that they had to go for a massive trek rather than climb.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/jake.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, Miguel had picked Chorley up from the train station, and everyone
was now at the campsite. Chorley had to undergo a Flixbus nightmare. His bus was
late on the ferry, meaning that he missed his connection. After being ushered onto a
seemingly random coach, he had to check maps on his phone to make sure the bus
was in fact destined for Paris. He eventually made it after almost 24 hours of travel.
For dinner, Olly made his famous chorizo carbonara, which everyone managed to
force down, but spirits were high as the forecast looked good for the next few days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/chorley_2.png" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-3-21921"&gt;Day 3 (21/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next morning the team headed to &lt;em&gt;Roche aux
Sabots&lt;/em&gt; , a crag with relatively little forest cover so the
rocks got the sun and dried quicker. The aim was to
complete either the blue or orange circuit over the
course of the day, however for most this changed to
climbing whatever looked cool. Most people got to
about the 20th problem of the circuit before going to try
hard on something else. A group went to try &lt;em&gt;Graviton&lt;/em&gt;
(f7a). The hard part of this was getting over the very
top, which prompted Chorley to
try to jump past the top, resulting in a rash over his chest.
Meanwhile Miguel was working on a boulder called &lt;em&gt;Legalize
This&lt;/em&gt; (f7a). This was a one move f7a eliminate from undercuts
to the top of the block. Miguel was consistently getting his
hand over the top but couldn’t latch the hold. Chorley came
over and sent it, fulfilling his aim of climbing f7a on his first day
climbing. He then repeated the problem next go to get it on
video. Olly also did the problem, first go, in flip flops, proving
once again that he is the greatest climber in the club. Olly had
also achieved his goal of completing the blue circuit that day,
which provided a lot of varied and entertaining boulder
problems. The best of these were recommended to the rest of
the group. Over the day James had done a few f7a and f7a+s without anyone
noticing. At the end of the day, Miguel had to be pulled away from his one move
eliminate f7a project as it was getting dark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/oli_rainbow.png" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/chorley_3.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/george_2.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/17.png" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ben cooked coq au van for dinner, which was delicious and contained a good
amount of red wine although it could not compete with the Lidl “peach rings” that
everyone on the trip had become addicted to by now. Everyone felt thoroughly
knackered by the end of the meal and got to sleep very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-4-22921"&gt;Day 4 (22/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next day most of the team ventured to F &lt;em&gt;ranchard Isatis&lt;/em&gt; , a classic of Font
bouldering areas. Chorley and Olly however went to &lt;em&gt;Franchard Sablons Carriers&lt;/em&gt;
instead in the morning to try their projects. Chorley was trying &lt;em&gt;Sylphide&lt;/em&gt; (f7a) whilst
Olly attempted &lt;em&gt;Rainbow Rocket&lt;/em&gt; (f8a). Both took turns at trying their boulders while
the other rested in the hammock. They each touched the top of their dynos, but neither could stick it. After a couple hours of trying, they both gave up and headed to
&lt;em&gt;Isatis&lt;/em&gt; to meet up with the others. When they got there,
they found that the rest had befriended an old pof-riddled
Frenchman. He was chastising them about using shoes
and crash pads as well as spotting with one hand with a
cigarette in to other. He did show us some good problems
though, as well as Miguel another eliminate f7a dyno for
him to wear his skin more on. Everyone was fairly tired
after the previous day of climbing so were taking it easy,
although a few people went to try some highball problems,
which put hairs on their chests. After a final bit of climbing, they all retreated to the
campsite for some well-earned risotto and rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/18.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/19.png" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/20.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-5-23921"&gt;Day 5 (23/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a brief stop to buy every baguette and
pastry at Lidl, the team ventured to &lt;em&gt;La Canche
aux Merciers&lt;/em&gt; for some more bouldering. This was
a particularly nice crag despite the hordes of
French urchins school children running around
being annoying and the disabled dog that could
boulder harder than any of us to get to our food
bag and eat our cured meats and cheese.
Today’s aim was the same as the others; start
trying to do a circuit, then get distracted and try
something too hard. Olly, Emyr and Jake did
manage to complete their full circuits, whilst
James smashed out some more f7a and f7a+s. A
multitude of other problems were attempted; a
few people tried a f7a+ roof, a few tried some
weird crack, and Miguel found another one move
f7a eliminate. Ben nearly finished the whole
circuit, but got completely shut down by a f3+
slab, which caused most people a lot of
frustration. They left the crag late that evening
with very sore skin and very hungry.
Unfortunately, they had to wait until 11pm for
Jake’s underwhelming spaghetti bolognaise to be
ready, by which time everyone was full from
snacking on too many peach rings and
bolognaise flavoured crisps. They didn’t let Jake
be in charge of cooking again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/21.png" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-6-24921"&gt;Day 6 (24/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;On their penultimate climbing day, the team awoke to a dense
fog. They drove to &lt;em&gt;Bas Cuvier&lt;/em&gt; to see if the rock was dry and
were greeted by a slightly moist crag. The team did some
stretching on the pads while they waited for the rock to dry
and realised that they were all very stiff from all the climbing.
They then warmed up by throwing a
crash pad at each other. By the time
they were bored of this the fog had
cleared, the sun was out, and the rock
was dry. &lt;em&gt;Bas Cuvier&lt;/em&gt; was supposed to
be the most classic crag in Font, however it was strewn with
broken glass, used hypodermic needles, condoms and
human excrement. This rather diminished the psych to
climb, and the rock was quite polished, however the team
tried &lt;em&gt;La Marie Rose&lt;/em&gt; (f6a+), which is potentially the most famous boulder in Font.
James tried to do &lt;em&gt;Carnage&lt;/em&gt; (f7b+) and got close
before giving up. Olly tried to do &lt;em&gt;L&amp;rsquo;Hélicoptère&lt;/em&gt;
(f7a), named for what your legs do when you fall
off. He didn’t do it but he also didn’t break
anything, so that was a win. Miguel couldn’t find a
one move eliminate f7a so was grumpy. George
tried &lt;em&gt;Pif-paf&lt;/em&gt; (f7a), a route named after a powerful
nerve agent cockroach killing spray. He swiftly
gave up due to the problem’s proximity to the
human turd. Well before it was dark, everone
realised that they were absolutely wrecked, so they went back to the campsite via a
pizza place for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/george_3.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/george_4.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-7-25921"&gt;Day 7 (25/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The day began with a trip to the local town to be
tested for COVID before travelling back to the UK.
After and French lady had aggressively swabbed our
noses, we headed to &lt;em&gt;Le Cul de Chien.&lt;/em&gt; This was half
crag half beach and was probably the best one that
the team went to. After a long week with only one rest
day at the very start, the team weren’t psyched on
trying anything too hard, so aimed for another circuit.
This didn’t end up happening for most however, since
as normal they were distracted by a different boulder.
The team tried some f6a+ mantle, which was another
chest scraper. Most people managed this, despite
some astounding inflexibility from Jake. A few people also managed to finish their
circuits after this, and the team made sure to dog proof their food bag. George tried
&lt;em&gt;Le Toit du Cul du Chien&lt;/em&gt; (f7a), which looked a bit like (and is named after) the behind of a dog. He got some good pictures
of him falling off it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miguel, again
unhappy with the lack of one move
f7a eliminates, went back to the
nearby &lt;em&gt;Roche aux Sabots&lt;/em&gt; to try his
one move f7a eliminate project. He
spent a short while trying before
realising that this one move f7a
eliminate wasn’t for him. He decided
in future to change his style and aim
to climb a one move f7a eliminate in
the UK on different rock. A few people
had meanwhile managed a full circuit,
while others lay on the sand trying to
grow back their skin that had been eroded over the week. They drove back to the
campsite for a final night of curry and tiny French beer, sad at the thought of leaving
the next day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/george_5.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-8-26921"&gt;Day 8 (26/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next morning they woke up and packed the tent
up. After checking out the campsite, Miguel drove his
car back to the UK. Olly and George had booked a
later ferry before going back in the van, so went to
have a final look at &lt;em&gt;Rainbow Rocket&lt;/em&gt; , but it was wet
after an overnight shower, so they drove back and
ate chips in Calais waiting for their ferry. The team
made the most of their duty free allowance, George
hasn’t been able to walk in a straight line since he got
back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="tour-review"&gt;Tour Review
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We all achieved negative COVID results both in
France and on return of the UK, which meant that we
had fulfilled our goal of not spreading the virus. We
had also had a week of climbing with no injuries or
major dramas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In terms of personal climbing objectives, only Chorley
managed to reach his goal of climbing f7a, whilst
Olly, Jake and Emyr managed to complete at least
one full circuit. Jake did manage to climb well over 100 problems and Emyr got back
into climbing with style. James ticked a number of hard problems over f7a but failed
to do the hardest problem of the trip, so decided to lock himself in a gym and train for
6 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miguel’s search for a one move f7a eliminate continues. The whole trip ran smoothly, without any real issues. The low number of people
meant that logistics were easier and that we could drive around crags. The main
negative of the trip was the lack of rest days. The team had 5 climbing days in a row,
which really took a toll on their skin and their psych. Next time it would be better to
go for a week extra and have more rest days. All in all Font delivered all that we
hoped it would, and the club will definitely be back in future years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="budget"&gt;Budget
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the initial budget was made for 15 people to take three
cars from the UK, the costs associated with being tested
both in France (€20 each) and in the UK (~£50 each) made
the trip more expensive per person than anticipated. This
was offset by the fact that only 8 people came as opposed to
the 15 budgeted for. Overall, the expenditure on travel was
£1665,13, which included getting a car and a van, as well as
the other members who couldn’t fit in these, to and from
Fontainebleau. The IC Trust gave us £670.50 of funding,
which was slightly less than the 40% of travel expenditure
we ended up having (£695.95). Overall, the trip could have
been much cheaper had we not had to spend so much on
testing and had we all gone to and from London together,
however space in the car was a major constraint. Added to this, George came from
Croatia and Ben from Rome, and Ben left a day early, adding to the expenses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="data-table" role="region" tabindex="0" &gt;
&lt;table class="table %!s(&lt;nil&gt;)" id="714623895"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Expenditure&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Campsite&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£488&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Food&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£253.33&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Ferries&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£380.73&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Tolls&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£91.27&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Fuel&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£449.15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;COVID testing&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£520&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Busses&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£113.99&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Trains&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£183.99&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Total&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£2480.46&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="conclusion-and-future-plans"&gt;Conclusion and Future Plans
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour was a fun trip abroad for everyone, and we will definitely be back to Font in
future. All attendees not in their final year of study expressed interest in going on and
potentially running future tours, and the experience and competence of outdoor
boulderers in the club has been markedly improved. Miguel is still looking for a one
move f7a eliminate, if you know of one please contact him at:
&lt;a class="link" href="mailto:miguel@1movef7aeliminate.com" &gt;miguel@1movef7aeliminate.com&lt;/a&gt;. Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Summer tour 2014 - Verdon Gorge</title><link>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/4.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Summer tour 2014 - Verdon Gorge" /&gt;&lt;h3 id="member-attendees-17"&gt;Member Attendees: 17
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will Smith, Ben Coope, Harry Stuart- Smith, Yadu Bhageria, Mathew Lees, Milan Thakore, Will Macleod, Sam Cockman, Chris Brahms, Nathasha Saw, Catherine Spilsbury, Simeon Tsang, Anthony Fleming, James Weale, Jo Robbings, Amar Nanda, Kristjana Xhuxhi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="non-member-attendees-3"&gt;Non-Member Attendees: 3
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Georgia Drew, Laura Braun, Ed Poore&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="aims-and-objectives"&gt;Aims and Objectives
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The aim of the trip was to explore the Verdon area and give all those attending the opportunity to try the long, exposed and committing multipitch routes it had to offer. The trip achieved this aim; everybody was sad to leave! (Probably because of the two days in the minibus it would take to get home).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="financial-breakdown"&gt;Financial Breakdown
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class="data-table" role="region" tabindex="0" &gt;
&lt;table class="table %!s(&lt;nil&gt;)" id="765943218"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Income&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Member Income&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£4085.10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;ICU Funding&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£304.60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Total&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£4389.7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="data-table" role="region" tabindex="0" &gt;
&lt;table class="table %!s(&lt;nil&gt;)" id="923576418"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Expenditure&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Minibus&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£1430&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Fuel&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£802.02&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Tolls&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£178.88&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Accomodation&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£948.09&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Food&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£985.56&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Guide books&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£45.25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Total&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£4389.7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note that the above financial breakdown only applies to member attendees.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/0.jpg" width="400"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-1"&gt;Day 1
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everybody arrived on time in Beit Quad at 6 am ready to finish packing the busses and set off. Harry turned out to be a little worse for wear and had forgotten his passport. After a quick call to his dad it was agreed that the two busses and the car would rendezvous at the ferry terminal ready for the morning crossing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One bus arrived earlier, crossed on its own, both busses and the car all got lost independently and took different routes around Paris. We eventually ended up at Pres Camping south of Fountainbleu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-2"&gt;Day 2
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We got up early and had eggy bread, then headed over to boulder for the day. It was very hot and sunny, a slack line was set off and a few of us played boules while we enjoyed lunch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/1.jpg"
alt="The first of many games of danger boules." width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first of many games of danger boules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-3"&gt;Day 3
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/3.jpg"
alt="Harry." width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This day involved hundreds and hundreds of miles of driving. Luckily there were loads of drivers and we had lots of food. At one point Jo stopped wearing trousers and decided that the heated seats in the car were all a bit much. Late in the evening the red bus was hit by an oncoming van which destroyed the wing mirror, and the passenger side window. Thankfully nobody was hurt, though there was a lot of glass everywhere. A nearby irrigation system ensured that everybody in the windowless van stayed refreshed, which was great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We arrived in Palud Sur Verdon at around 11:30 pm and found the road leading up to the valley a bit exciting; the enormous drop to the right of the driver and sharp bends made sure that everybody was still awake. We arrived at the wrong campsite and put up the tents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-4"&gt;Day 4
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After waking up and realising that the campsite was wrong and rubbish, we de-camped and headed into town to try and find where we were meant to go. We immediately found Jean- Paul camping and headed over to pop the tents up. We then went to one of the shorter and supposedly more accessible crags in the area. After an hour of swearing and bashing through shrubs we arrived and got a decent afternoons climbing in, introducing the novices in the group to the techniques they’d need over the coming week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/4.jpg"
alt="Jo and James doing some of the very pleasant routes at the single pitch crag a little way down the valley." width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jo and James doing some of the very pleasant routes at the single pitch crag a little way down the valley.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-5"&gt;Day 5
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We headed over to a multi-pitch crag that didn’t involve any abseiling to give people some experience of the rope work before we committed to bigger routes. In the afternoon we headed down to the river for a swim!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-6"&gt;Day 6
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We knew that if we wanted to get anything big done while we were there we’d have to get used to the exposure presented by the enormous cliffs. To do this we spent the next day at one of the many abseil points at the edge of the road. Lots of tourists were taking our photos!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/5.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-7-8--9"&gt;Day 7, 8 &amp;amp; 9
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having taught people what they needed to know we split into three’s and took a series of groups to different multipitch crags over the next three days. The routes ranged from enormous crack and chimney climbs to interesting arête’s. Notably Ben and Amar tackled La Demande, one of the more famous routes in the area. Groups that didn’t do multipitch routes headed to abseil points along the roadside or along the valley to the extremely impressive Hulk area; a large scoop/ cave with some really interesting and challenging single pitch climbs. Handily it also stayed dry when the rest of the area was wet!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/6.jpg"
alt="Temperature inversion in the valley" width="400"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Temperature inversion in the valley&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/7.jpg"
alt="Georgia climbing above the river on a 9 pitch route." width="400"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Georgia climbing above the river on a 9 pitch route.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="images8.jpg"
alt="Milan and Sam on their first multipitch route, l’arete belvedere" width="400"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Milan and Sam on their first multipitch route, l’arete belvedere&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-10"&gt;Day 10
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a tiring few days we headed down to the river to wind down for a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/9.jpg" width="400"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/10.jpg" width="400"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-11"&gt;Day 11
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group went over to the Hulk area because of poor weather. The crag is in the middle of a series of ladders and narrow paths which allows for pretty big exposure in relative safety. On the opposite side of the valley a few people experienced the total darkness of the 1.5km long tunnel which runs along the river. Milan and Anthony got a bit stuck on their route so Ben and Amar shot up an adjacent route to help them out after their abseil line got stuck after they completed their route. Everybody got down in time for a late dinner though Milan and Anthony owed a lot of people a lot of drinks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/11.jpg"
alt="Milan climbing in Hulk" width="400"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Milan climbing in Hulk&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-12"&gt;Day 12
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the final day in Verdon the weather turned for the worse, those who hadn’t yet done it had a go at the via–ferrata which was about the only thing that was safe to do in the weather. The rest of the group had a relaxing day at the campsite and sorted the mountains of equipment out! The trip was rounded off with a meal at the local restaurant in Palud Sur Verdon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-13"&gt;Day 13
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We left Verdon and headed north making the campsite just south of Paris by 10 pm. Chilli was cooked hastily while a fire was built. Lunch and snack stops were spent at some of the many roadside picnicking areas that the cover much of the French road network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-14"&gt;Day 14
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a quick stop at the wine shop we caught the ferry home and remarked on how great cat-eyes were in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Easter Tour 2011</title><link>YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/cover.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Easter Tour 2011" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on a true story&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="1-introduction"&gt;1 Introduction
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the Easter break of 2011 members of Imperial College Mountaineering Club (ICMC) departed
on a 14 day trip that would take them through 3 different countries in their quest for climbing.
Taking the union minibus these brave adventurers drove 2276 miles through tunnels, over
mountains, off road and even on the flat. Due to several members dropping out and several other
members lacking just one of the requirements to be able to drive there were only two drivers of the
minibus for the duration of the trip. Most of the team returned with no injuries&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were several aims and objectives for the tour, primary aim of the tour were to take members
of the club to a number of locations and climb on a range of rock types and in styles unusual to that
of the UK. Other aims were for members to improve their ability and to climb in styles that they
were not so used to. The Pyrenees also offered some longer multipitch climbs that are far larger
than anything available in the UK and these were the main target of some members of the tour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Four distinctly different rock types were seen on tour, these were limestone, sand stone, granite and
conglomerate however within these broad rock types there were a range of styles from slabs to
overhangs. All members felt they had improved and were stronger towards the end of the trip.
Certain crags offered very interesting routes which combined different styles of climbing such as
steep over hangs into technical slabs which was very rewarding to climb on. While multi pitch climbs
were done by all members the attempt at Enfants de la Dalle (a 1000m+ route) was called off for
concerns about the safety of the attempt. The Pyrenees mountain range has a lot to offer in the way
of climbing, another tour could easily be run and not have to climb in any of the same areas. It would
also be of value to return in the future and climb some of the routes that defeated the climbers this
time around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For future tours there are some lessons to be learnt. While taking the minibus is a reasonable way to
travel it is slower and more tiring than flying. The minibus did have the major advantages of being
able to take all of the equipment and did allow the tour to visit a lot more areas than would have
been practical if flights had been used. The main problem was the lack of drivers, only having two
drivers meant that they were very tired at the end of long stretches of driving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A final issue, which only became apparent after the tour was finished, was the amount of things
done on tour. So much was crammed into the 14 days that an extensive tour report was required to
describe the events of the tour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="2-people"&gt;2 People
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The people who went on the tour were:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Matthew Lees (Murray)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edward Stott&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tristan Pollitt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jonathan Price&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elliot Carrington (Choss Master)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adrian Jeakins*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michael Jones (Fails)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jonathan Mason (The American)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Justine Courty*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All people on the tour were full members of ICMC at the time&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*These members were not present for the entire trip&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="3-tour-diary"&gt;3 Tour Diary
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="31-day-1--beit"&gt;3.1 Day 1 – Beit
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;While most students were finishing up for the term and moving over to the union to relax and have
a few drinks before going home for Easter the ICMC members were busy packing the bus and getting
ready for their 2 weeks away. Murray had spent the morning chasing various Sabbaticals and union
staff for money, bus keys and tarps and had managed to get it all together in time for the bus to be
packed and make a slightly delayed departure at 7 pm. Heading towards the euro tunnel took from
South Kensington took the bus through central London which was packed. Eventually the motor way
was reached and the lack of a 6th gear became annoyingly obvious with the engine droning away in
5 th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The euro tunnel was reached in remarkably good time considering the traffic and late get away. The
spare hour was used by most to wonder around the terminal but Ed took this opportunity to climb
on top of the bus and have a snooze. The train was boarded just before midnight and departed on
time&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="32-day-2--font"&gt;3.2 Day 2 – Font
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arriving in France shortly after departing and not
being entirely sure of the time anymore Ed took the
wheel and headed towards Fontainebleau; we
arrived much earlier than expected. Since it was
still dark all the members decided to find their own
sleeping spots and have a good sleep before the
day’s bouldering. Some members slept in the bus,
some in the woods, and Ed chose the top of the bus
again. The people who had chosen to sleep in the
woods were woken first by the numerous dogs that
went to investigate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a good breakfast of cereal the group moved
off into the forest to find the boulders they had
come looking for. Murray, Ed, Fails and Choss
Master set off on the purple circuit which proved to
be just the right difficulty. There were some
interesting problems as well as a high ball part and
an impressive tunnel to crawl through. At lunch
time the 4 decided to head back to base camp for
food and while walking back Choss Master had a
disagreement with a rock, the disagreement escalated into a fight. Choss Master decided that the
best option was to head but the rock but this proved to be a bad idea. After sending someone for ice
at the cafe and making Choss Master sit still for a while they continued back to base camp.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That afternoon Fails found an impressive looking roof section that he managed to climb after a few
goes, Murray and Choss Master both climbed it afterwards. Ed and Jon both slept on top of the roof
being climbed while The American did some impressive spotting for those on the roof. After
everyone had climbed themselves out for the day they got back on the bus and headed for
Targasonne stopping in some services for Chilli.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="33-day-3--targasonne"&gt;3.3 Day 3 – Targasonne
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;After some more speedy driving at 100 kph by Ed and Murray Targasonne was reached ahead of
schedule and again people decided to sleep by the road instead of going straight for the climbing.
Just when everyone had got to sleep it began to rain, most people dived straight into the bus but Jon
and Ed had other ideas, they slipped under the bus to use it as a shelter and both slept there. A
couple of hours later an angry French man turned up and told us we were in the wrong place, the
bouldering was further out of town, and he told us to get out of the lay-by we were in. Seeing the
rain hadn’t stopped and not wanting to get in trouble the decision was made to make a break for the
border. On the way there was a rather long tunnel and the tunnel game was introduced to all (where
one holds their breath while in the tunnel), unfortunately the 13 km tunnel proved far too long for
anyone to finish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later that day the bus rolled into their new home for the next week and set up camp, this time in the
right place. On the Spanish side the weather was much more favourable with no sign of rain, not
wanting to waste the rest of the day everyone jumped back into the bus and went to the closest crag
that had things easier than 7a; Crestes De Conill. After getting spanked by the easiest of climbs and
blaming it on being tired and on unusual rock the team returned to the campsite. Homemade
burgers were on the menu that evening, after burning all of them in an effort to avoid food
poisoning everyone turned in for the first good night’s sleep to be had in a couple of days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="34-day-4--conglomerate"&gt;3.4 Day 4 – Conglomerate
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;After waking up to surprisingly good health after dinner the night before a relaxed pace was adopted
for this days climbing. The destination was an area called Collegats, quite a large area of
conglomerate climbing. Most of the routs had a boulder start, easy middle and a difficult top section.
The conglomerate rock had an interesting mix of hidden jugs and a lot of traps. Fails and Choss
Master decided to demonstrate their punter like skills by setting up a top rope on a 6c and did not
attempt the lead. Murray tried a 6a on lead but had to retreat and let fails rescue his quick draws.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some refreshing rain started at the end of the day making the decision to end climbing and go back
to camp for everyone. Dinner that night was a tuna and tomato pasta dish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="35-day-5--lleida"&gt;3.5 Day 5 – Lleida
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was the first time breakfast had been porridge on
the trip. The plan was to have a rest day and go into
Lleida to pick up Adrian who had flown in late after
needing to finish project work. In Lleida the food
supplies were restocked and lunch consisted of 2 Kg of
mystery meat purchased at the reasonable sum of €4.
Decathlon was next on the shopping trip for people to
restock on climbing equipment they had decided they
needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a phone call from Adrian saying there was a delay
and he would be getting into Lleida 2 hours later than
originally planned the idea of a rest day was scrapped
and the guide book was reached for. The closest
climbing to Lleida was a cave with a number of routs
ranging from 8a to unclimbed, deciding this was a bit
hard bouldering a bit further away was chosen. After
about half an hour driving on a dirt track into the desert
leaving a massive dust cloud in the wake of the bus the
boulders were discovered with the tell tale chalk of a
long history of being climbed. A number of hard
powerful problems were climbed and many remained
unclimbed even after ridiculous back breaking beta was
used. Once Adrian was picked up from the train station
and the short journey back to camp completed dinner
was put on, this time it was carbonara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="36-day-6--accident"&gt;3.6 Day 6 – Accident
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The destination for climbing this day was Camarossa. Being a road side crag made access very easy,
luckily the road lead to a hydro electric plant and had very little traffic on it. Being at the bottom of a
valley there was no direct sun for much of the day. Fails had spotted a short 6c+ that had a powerful
crux, ideal for the Westway climber. After some working he eventually got it clean, attempts were
made by Murray and Choss Master but were unsuccessful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While climbing elsewhere Ed took a rather large lob (4 – 5 m) whilst trying to clip a bolt.
Unfortunately during the fall he inverted in the harness and hit his head on the rock below, he was
not wearing a helmet at the time. At first glance the injury was quite bad; there was a lot of blood on
Ed and the rock. On closer inspection while the cut was deep it was not through to the skull so it was
bandaged up. Within a short period Ed was feeling much better but decided not to climb anymore
that day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further up the road from the crag was an interesting looking cave which had a couple of inches of
water in the bottom. The cave was large enough for a car to drive down and the tell tale tyre marks
at the entrance confirmed this had been done. The cave extended about 100 m into the rock, made
a turn and ended. It was concluded that this was a secret government facility with a concealed
entrance and we would all disappear if exploration continued. Dinner that evening was a BBQ which
was enjoyed by all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="37-day-7--schorchio"&gt;3.7 Day 7 – Schorchio!
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The morning was spent in the town of Balaguer stocking up on food. While the team were shopping
Fails took decided to go for a haircut. On the return from the hairdressers to the bus he managed to
get lost and needed to be rescued by Ed. Fully stocked the team left the town to find some climbing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After parking next to a bee hive the team walked up to the climbs at Cubells. This was by far the
hottest day of the trip. The crag was south facing and right a t the end of the foot hills, from the base
of the walk in the land was flat for as far as the eye could see. While the climbing was very good the
heat was exhausting and the constant bees following the climbers up the crag were annoying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Returning to camp a curry was cooked up
and eaten in very little time. Just before
going to bed some members decided to
take showers, one of these members was
Fails. It turned out that fails had forgotten
his towel and thought that the best
solution was to dance in front of the hand
dryer in his boxers until fully dried. This
matter was not aided by people flicking
water at him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="38-day-8--birthday"&gt;3.8 Day 8 – Birthday
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a day of being roasted by the Spanish
sun a rest day was called for. Various
activities were devised by members.
Revision was a popular idea but very little
was achieved. Some members went on a
walk around the camp site and found a
chain of 65 caterpillars following each
other nose to tail. Attempts to join the 2
ends of the chain together failed so they
were left alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later a trip was organised into Balaguer to restock on food again. While in town the idea of ice
creams was put forwards, unfortunately at a mere 32 o the local ice cream shop felt it was too cold
for anyone to buy ice creams and had not opened. While wondering around town a rather unusual
shop was discovered that had many sweet
deals, fails was in heaven and splashed out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once all the entertainments of Balaguer were
exhausted swimming in the river was suggested
and all members agreed this was a perfect way
to cool off, near to the camp site was a lake that
looked ideal. At the entrance to the lake a small
bridge crossed, at approximately 5 m high it was
a good height for jumping into the river from.
After extensive testing by throwing rocks of
various size into the river it was deemed safe
enough for Fails to jump in. Driving the minibus
off the bridge and into the river was also put
forwards as a more conclusive test but the
barriers next to the road prevented this. After
Fails jumped into the water with a small Spanish
audience and survived it was then considered
safe enough for the other more valuable
members to enter. Murray took the longest to get over his psyche problem but did jump in the
end. The water was very cold and quick exits
were made by all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After some issues with the stoves catching fire
due to leaky petrol canisters chilli was served
but, rather unusually for ICMC, there was also a
desert on offer. The desert was a quadruple
chocolate cake hand crafted for The American’s
birthday. It consisted of 2 chocolate sponges
glued together with melted chocolate, covered
in more melted chocolate, with chocolate eggs
on top each with a soft chocolate centre.
Candles were fashioned from the left over
cheese wax wrapped around sticks and soaked
in petrol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="39-day-9--policía"&gt;3.9 Day 9 – Policía
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was to be the last day spent in Spain. The
tent was packed up with impressive speed and
everything was ready to go so fast that the
reception was not yet open. After waiting for
reception to open and paying for the camp site
ICMC was on the road again. Heading north
towards France they stopped to check out
Pachamama, Chris Sharma’s famous 9a+, all
were amazed at the size of it and how over hanging it was. While having lunch it was realised that
more people had been to the moon than had climbed that piece of rock. With that sobering thought
they got back on the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The crag for the day was located on an abandoned stretch of highway that was left to crumble after
the new highway was constructed that tunnelled straight through the rock rather than winding
around the valley. The abandoned highway could easily be from a scene in a post apocalyptic film
and as such everyone was on guard for zombies or gangs who might want our supplies. The walk up
to the crag was steep and had a lot of loose rock, once at the top everyone immediately found a
bush to hide behind as the sun was beating down again. Finishing climbing early as there was still a
lot of driving to do that day they got back on the road and played the tunnel game, again being
defeated by the 13 km monster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While on the road heading towards France the bus was waved over by the policía, they asked for the
drivers licence and there seemed to be some problem with it not being valid for the type of vehicle
being driven. Trying to explain it only had 9 seats so was not category D failed due to the language
barrier. One of the policía seemed interested in what we had on the room and after shouts of
“escalada” their attitude changed and they waved us on. Deciding that they would not hang around
long enough for the policía to change their mind they made a break for the border. There was an
interesting detour from the main road that the sat-nav seemed to think was better, while being a lot more picturesque it was unclear if it was any faster. Arriving at the very cheap camping municipal
after a long hill climb in the bus the team settled down for what might be a rather cold night due to
the altitude.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="310-day-10--la-dent-dorlu"&gt;3.10 Day 10 – La Dent d’Orlu
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Waking up to a surprisingly warm morning considering the altitude the first views of the new scenery
were seen and impressed all. There was still snow on top of many of the mountains and the ski lift
was running. The plan for the day was to check out a mountain called La Dent d’Orlu, on the south
and east faces were many multi pitch climbs, one of which was of particular interest: Les Enfants de
la Dalle. This rout had been chosen by Murray and Jon as their main target for the tour, the total
height was 1100 m of rock made of 28 pitches all needing to be done in 1 day. Today was going to be
a reconnaissance trip in order to climb some smaller routes and work out where then needed to be
for the main ascent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The town of Aux les Thermes was called at for fuel and food before heading to Orlu to find the
mountain. Parking in a large car park at the bottom the first views of the climb were intimidating to
say the least. A huge face of dark stone that looked much higher and steeper than expected with the
top few hundred meters capped in snow greeted the climbers and they had not even done the walk
in yet. The topo suggested a 30 minute walk in but this was more like an hour and 30 up steep
woodland with a difficult to follow path. Reaching the bottom of the climbs a well deserved lunch
was had. Part way through lunch a rock landed a couple of meters away from the happy picnickers,
from the sound it was estimated to be going very fast and about toaster size. Helmets were donned
by all who had them and the guide book was placed over the head of the one member who had left
theirs behind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While scoping out routs, rain drops could be felt and the weather looked like it might be about to
take a turn for the worse. Large seepage patches could be seen and few bolts could. The decision
was made to abandon climbing here as it was unsuitable for teaching multipitch and would have
been potentially dangerous even for the experienced climbers. The walk out was no better than the
walk in and would have been near impossible if the sky had opened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A crag much closer to the camp site was located with a good selection of climbs and even some
multipitch. It turned out to be an interesting mix of some technical slab and powerful overhangs and
was very enjoyable. Fails and Choss Master climbed a 6c, when Murray attempted it he slid down
the slab section losing some fingertips. Jon and Murray climbed a multipitch and had a difficult
conversation half way up, they decided that it was not a good idea to climb Enfants as it would be
too dangerous and getting benighted was a certainty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Returning to camp after an exhausting day of walking up hills everyone was in the mood for a less
strenuous day the next day so bouldering was again on the table. Dinner was carbonara.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="311-day-11--the-mountain-pass"&gt;3.11 Day 11 – The Mountain Pass
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deciding to take an easy day after all the fell wondering the day before a group decision was made
to do some hard bouldering Targasonne. Realising that it was on the other side of the 13 km an
alternate route was looked for to avoid the toll, a mountain pass over the tunnel was found which
was open so this became the new route, the sat nav objected heavily. Driving up the zig zagging
roads was reasonably fun until the bus entered fog that was as thick as pea soup, then the drivers realised they had made an amazing decision and the trip was to be a lot more fun. After some time
of driving with about 15 m visibility the bus suddenly left the fog into the sunny clear air on the other
side of the mountain, turning a corner the team got a view of what they had just driven out of. It
looked rather like someone had dropped a large amount of dry ice on France and the smoke was
pouring through the cull.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arriving at Targasonne and not having a guide book meant finding the climbing was rather difficult,
driving along the road many small boulders were pointed out until rounding a corner a gigantic
boulder field appeared and it was obvious where they were meant to go. Parking in a road version of
an oxbow lake, the bus was unloaded and everyone headed off in the direction of the closest
boulders. The plan was to wonder around and find cool looking problems to try and not worry about
grades or what was possible, a plan which proved to be excellent. The first big boulder that base
camp was set up at had a number of problems on which were all enjoyable. The top out appeared
flat when climbing but long chalk streamers ran down the top of the rock that guided the hands to
hidden jugs. People wondered around for a while each picking out their own rocks of interest. Fails
and Adrian found an impressive problem that they spent most of the day working requiring difficult
moves into under cuts and a top out that was not particularly friendly. After many attempts and
almost at the end of the day Adrian almost made an ascent but failed at the final move when he
tried to pull onto the top but found there were only prickly bushes, making a dynamic retreat all the
observers saw his grazed torso caused by the top out. Inspired by this effort fails put a tee-shirt on
and managed to top out the problem grading it V6+ or V7. Several other problems were climbed and
not climbed and overall everyone had a very good day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sharp granite had taken its toll and everyone’s fingertips were feeling very thin. The journey
back involved driving back through the fog again which was no thinner. Dinner that night was
another BBQ. Some members decided to eat in to the next day’s lunch rations and cook some
bananas with chocolate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="312-day-12--choss"&gt;3.12 Day 12 – Choss
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking through the guide book for some multipitch climbs that everyone could do the location
Sinsat 1, Le Pubis, sector GR4B+ was chosen. Upon arriving the discovery was made that the climbs
were half way up a mountain, the long walk in the baking sub began. While walking up the foot path
it was noted that a number of the climbs on different walls could be linked to make a multipitch
ascent which was much longer than the guide book had first indicated, some French climbers were
doing this. The topo used for the Foix area was printed from the internet, if pictures had been
included it would have been easier to identify the crags and it may have been noticed that the
various climbs could be linked up sooner. The climbs were good quality with little polish. This was
some member’s first experience of the slightly sparse nature of multipitch bolting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While climbing Fails and Ed reached the top anchor first, this anchor was shared between two routs
and Murray and Jon were on the other route. While Murray and Jon had set off first, Fails and Ed
had the advantage of one
less pitch. Murray and Jon’s
route finished with a good
jamming crack that would
have been a quality trad lead.
With the French climbers
closing in from the bottom
Murray had to unclip some of
Fail’s quick draws after Fails
was safely on the anchor and
build his own as there was
not enough space on the
existing one. The top out was
covered in choss, some of
which was knocked down by
almost everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After the first set of groups
topped out they began their
walk down so that they could
rest and prepare for the next
climb. The second set of
climbers topped out and
descended without trouble.
This left the Choss Master
and the American as the last
group to finish the climb. The
Choss Master had earned his&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;name previously by knocking off vast quantities of choss onto his b-layers all trip, and this climb was
no exception. Using the radios to warn of the large quantities of choss descending the cliff allowed
everyone time to run for cover, after the first load helmets were replaced. During the descent the
two climbers took a wrong turn, after some time the other members became concerned about their
absence. They were on the far side of a ridge, so radio contact was useless. After some time radio
contact was re-established by walking to the top of the ridge and all was well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The decision was made back at camp to travel back to Font that evening so as to have more
bouldering time. A curry was cooked up by fails and the tent packed in record time and ICMC were
on the road again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="313-day-13--loughborough"&gt;3.13 Day 13 – Loughborough
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arriving at Font very early in the
morning a few hours sleep were
had in the forest again. Another
member of ICMC would be joining
for just the 1 day of climbing;
Justine who lived in Paris got the
train to join us. Numerous
problems were climbed including
one with many monos in it, finding
the monos difficult to hold Murray
climbed it without the m. A slab
next to base camp was found and
it had few holds, a few finger nail
crimps and smears, it was alto
slightly slimy. Attempts were made
by most people who all slid down
its face. Murray used the incredible
friction of his stealth onyx rubber
to climb it using the crimps and
later eliminated these as well
proving once again that 5.10 make
the best rubber.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going to a real campsite this time
ICMC met Loughborough university
mountaineering club. It turned out
that they were on their annual trip to font for 10 days. They were all very impressed by our big red
bus and were even more amazed after they found out what we had been doing for the last two
weeks. Some members of Loughborough had slack lines and were very skilled at it, one member
having a 100 m long one at home. The evening was spent sitting around the camp fire exchanging
stories eating chilli with a slightly soapy taste.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="314-day-14--blood-sweat-and-washing-up-liquid"&gt;3.14 Day 14 – Blood, Sweat and Washing up Liquid
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having a lazy start to the day everyone stayed in bed for a while before getting up and showering.
While preparing breakfast washing up liquid was found all over one of the boxes and needed
cleaning out, this explained the interesting flavour in the previous nights meal, on the positive side
the cooking box was the cleanest it had been since it was new. The tent was packed up one last time
and farewells were said to the Loughborough climbers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Travelling to a different area of Font this day. Jon was feeling very ill so spent most of the day asleep.
A blue circuit was attempted but it was poorly sign posted so was abandoned. Murray found an even
bigger, steeper smoother slab to climb which took him quite a long time to work but he got it in the
end. A large overhanging bulge was found by Fails and Adrian who worked out beta and climbed it,
other members tried and Murray managed it after many goes. While driving back to a different car
park to have dinner Murray had a random nose bleed while driving so pulled over and let Ed finish.
The last supper was carbonara and everyone was full to bursting after eating it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Setting off on the drive back to England the decision was made to avoid the toll roads since there
was so much spare time before the train left. Most of the drive back was on minor roads and
through villages, this didn’t have much impact as the speed limits were all 100 kph so the bus was
maxed out anyway. Arriving at the terminal 4 hours early the bus was upgraded for free onto a much
earlier train so that they arrived back into the UK in god time. Arriving at the union shortly after
dawn the bus was unpacked and all the equipment dumped into stores to be sorted at a later date.
Keys, first aid kit and minibus documentation returned to the SAC, all the members went their
separate ways to get a proper sleep in a bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="4-finances"&gt;4 Finances
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="41-income"&gt;4.1 Income
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Item Price (£) Quantity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full price ticket 225 7&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cheap ticket* 175 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Union Grant 129.54 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;IC Trust 238.93 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total = £2108.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;*Adrian flew in 4 days late so didn’t pay full price&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="42-expenditure"&gt;4.2 Expenditure
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Item Cost (£)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minibus 592&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fuel 560&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guide Books 56&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Camping 365&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Euro Tunnel 116&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Road Tolls 100&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Food 420&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Total =£ 2209&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;script src="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/jquery-3.7.0.min.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/lazy/jquery.lazy.min.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/swipebox/js/jquery.swipebox.min.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;link rel="stylesheet" href="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/swipebox/css/swipebox.min.css"&gt;
&lt;script src="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/justified_gallery/jquery.justifiedGallery.min.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;link rel="stylesheet" href="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/justified_gallery/justifiedGallery.min.css"/&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;div id="gallery-9c082d45b47ea5316133c3f3f0edb991-0-wrapper" class="gallery-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;div id="gallery-9c082d45b47ea5316133c3f3f0edb991-0" class="justified-gallery"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/9.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="450"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABgAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AGrECACAR3FVb6ZWUoAyKuPmXrV&amp;#43;3Ku8gI6LkDtWXHKk2pqFljVI5AxLNgECuSMW2dMmka3hnzLSR9SkjUeYPLiDDt3OK3b3W55iDvUKmQoUYrM0&amp;#43;2jmuAbWV5Lc7SfMYFYz0PTp0&amp;#43;vtWZcXElney2kzpK0TEGRBwSP/ANVdCdkYtamNqGoS71jiLR5JU7DyR3z/ACqvb2E1qCyTPul46Ag57c4xTbn/AI/R9T/OtM/dg/66p/MVmlqXa9h1lLLpl5bTzbkUSBn3d&amp;#43;eeKh1S7SXVLi4s2AgkkZlA6jPNWNf&amp;#43;5F9D/OsWL7j/AENaqmm7kVPdk4o//9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/9_hu_f5c5f0b77ee97a85.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/8.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="358" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAEwMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AKzeCLnqr7o2fBYOpAzgDoeueKjfwfeuy20iuGHLIvzbVJwCcfj&amp;#43;VWotDs43LKDk&amp;#43;nSp/wCzYhyrSr/uvip50R7WBSi8MapBGIljnIX/AKZtTv8AhHtV/wCeU3/ftqvCykxxe3g9vPaj7FJ/z/Xn/f8AapuivaxGJqVuejCplvYD/GtcWVu14Klh7U03cyHkuvseankZxWZ3P2uPHEi/nR9rj/56L&amp;#43;dcGdRkz9/9KT&amp;#43;0pP74/KlyMNT/2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/8_hu_a4014b191b3b87c9.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/7.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="450" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAGAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AINGjb&amp;#43;zjNPGsYzgbcgscDk81oW0dunyBGxIT8yLznPufr0q6iStbtFDApdRhCQG2&amp;#43;mOfb0rnY/Flhp2ozQy2wZy/lCSOMDDhuee/wCeKkuxvrOYA21VBLbckZP0POen0/Wl&amp;#43;1yeqf8Afo//ABVQSTx6fuklkIdjko2Qfbgdaj/4SOL/AGfyagRMVSa0liUMyv8AfYNhyexJGD9Kr3miWNxaR2jRr&amp;#43;6x5RZc7cdz6/jUyyPHAomHmyKBkpxwB0HTHb8qiOsWFtIxlfczAfu05K/X0pjM7UZV8opMrpIZihSSLeFUDqp7j0NZ/k2v95P&amp;#43;/NdJeG3CJdBPJG0guIw3Xp&amp;#43;pqj9qtv8An/8A/JSkI//Z"
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/7_hu_58ef14a9709ff74d.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/6.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="450" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAGAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AL6xpuAwQO&amp;#43;BmnMjBlCKMdy1V498QA4YeuME&amp;#43;mfwzT/tO6NjGzSHopYcHn&amp;#43;VAD5VRRnbuIPGDimb2/54t&amp;#43;dPEmEDOCcDkgYzzS/a7f8AuSfp/hQMqwOZ4/m289gOlMmeOKQeXIPmACjIJ/z61C0KyQchAidVOAW69qEtLSJ/NWFQF6YWkAjXgWbYbVlYLku5&amp;#43;9&amp;#43;lL9t/6ZL&amp;#43;QqT5WLcZDd8Gk&amp;#43;zp6j/vn/69MD//2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/6_hu_7f33d6c26cc1da4b.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/5.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="400"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABUAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AOo1XxPbXtyiW7Fo0VjtB&amp;#43;8&amp;#43;PfrVCTUvOnhacKSoLnLnCnHOfwrhrXUJvNUNGVXBJOev0q1NqlxbW4ZrEzvLu/d8kqB/FxyOorJyk2VG2zOguy4mLxyI8Ug3hsggZ9PalFtHJaswGXB4OMg9eorg9O8XTjUI7SWMG0dgoDD5lzxnP15rspJXAzH8nzDoevFQ00ykRXVpb28iokYzgZYnrmtW30e1FvfSNvJSzZQAxXqQT0/3RVDUf&amp;#43;Ppfotb0P8Ax5aj/wBexqovWxLik7nhxQefKBkGBiVPc&amp;#43;lenXz7IGfHzKp59a8zP/HzefU/zr0vUP8Aj0l/3T/I1q&amp;#43;hm9z/2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/5_hu_3c2530bad6ed5de9.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/4.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="293" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAEAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/APZGwAS2AB1Jrm9T8X6RaOyeYZSvGUxgn0HrWd471a8it5IbWaMQjCugOGY98npgZH6&amp;#43;leXXa3E0W57hMqQSinI68YxTvYTV9xNW1G/vBtE5lQHO1znOQBnPXt3ptvJGbdVcMrMNrjbnn1Ht9azW1QFOVKt0wRSx6isIxkcVI7o//9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/4_hu_1ce0e00319e87ad3.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/3.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="450"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABgAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AKCET2rQEHJTjBxg&amp;#43;35VeuNSvbi2igvJ2ujB038Opx14/CqNoNtwhBBA9v8APrUerSeXHI0auWZgTMpwIsHILf7Jxj&amp;#43;tAWGbN8oRzkscnHplav3ijyvJGSqDOOv51Str&amp;#43;1vLiNrOTzCi/OzDgEjFbcTFG8x4FZNwO4EFV56dqya6DcTntF1AX0055jSJtuD1PvVyK3F1NKXaQo&amp;#43;Bg4Cntj6Vh&amp;#43;HP9befQfyro7P/AFafQVtyqW5Ldie5u7bTp4fOX91JF5f7xlwCDnPT&amp;#43;XqaNOvLmW0ljufJlZmZkYDACZ4GQe1ZPjP/AI9bP/eP9KvaZ/x6D/dP8hVyhH2d&amp;#43;olN8x//2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/3_hu_4dd4b32f4f1b3b20.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/2.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="400" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAFQMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AOZZQbfJGdvX8wKscTRAoWWNN&amp;#43;MHGOnr9aBaTPDJCqfvCOATjvn&amp;#43;QqGCynmUrEUZskEBuR9am42ieaU2ZEMp3kE4CkHbz0/Oovt8f9x//Hf8KjfSb0O2QnX&amp;#43;/Tf7KvPSP/vunzMXKdBdqsCmeRgisNu/Jyp7cD8eap6TMJtQ3Qi6VIGJV3wyyc9&amp;#43;B/Wt0QoUKumSw7gEflUoVUXaiAZ/Km2nG1gtre5Wnj81/MZhluTgAfpUf2df7/6ipZ5ArAfMeMHBqLzh/des0rFn/9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/2_hu_8719961111e147fb.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/10.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="450" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAGAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AJk1GylVtswG0kEGs6&amp;#43;uHuYp47RgrKo&amp;#43;f/PT61BHp8z4RokVlHALcfiBRC66VcKpiFzNMwTyoxjbkjkn354rrliptWOeOHinczbXw/dvKtxcSNjdwccn1NaX9kx/89n/AFrevLa7aMx2saIhO5pX6/gP8ao/2ff/APP2P&amp;#43;/S1yWRuXZbu3s4Xl3LMoHBBzuNUvDtot9dS3gUpGpCqM4BOMZ9eAcfjXLm5mvbqGBV2tJhVRWOBn/61d/pEEFjapbRndj&amp;#43;JupJ6n888UDNR4R5Rj81VXJJPTAqr9nt/wDn&amp;#43;H/fZ/xqSOY4IaTC5yqt3FO&amp;#43;0Qf7H60Af//Z"
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/10_hu_d4150dbae699bc.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/1.png"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="250" height="126"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABAAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AOZF/LFOsdnd3N3mceftfaUH3sDB&amp;#43;bbu5yCQMjjGRr6/LNZalZR2niB9UtTOisjyOphViowFJ56g4yevTFent4L0ItLH/YkXl53Anadxx&amp;#43;fcjmiPwXoKZC6FFGqHcgDDlh05zkH8adwPEV8QalDLHLa3d15i3jJMoZtsfVRjnPHB69T7V03hiSG/hmm1jXbrSZYbkNC4dnEozxg88dBgknOeRyK9JPg/R2ZwdGjww3Z3gfN16D3rC1bwPbQ31td6dZJFK9zGvkSRI8ZUsN7fKAQQBu5JHGMc0Af/2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/1_hu_a00bd9b66f507119.png"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/0.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="450" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAGAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/ALR2y6bu4ZJcDJ9G/wD11jNaiWdYY8Y8wKwHYZ/wrR0fbLpANuSwIAdG7FOB&amp;#43;JwD&amp;#43;NNtIduuNHg5YtIPpXJRXvpHVV&amp;#43;Fs0Eg9qf5PtV1YfaneVXv3PCMDS9Im0eJlnlLHfuaNM44HBx3/wA&amp;#43;ladhapLrMsytnbHggdOT/wDWP51W0zWJ9WthbSqslyjbd&amp;#43;QDjnn8OKXVptT0a3a4iZVTBMhUAnqMcfia8Gi7VE2e5VXNTaRuXDLax72Ule&amp;#43;Ooqp/atp6Sf8Afs1xUvjW/dSpupNo6nAH9Krf8Jhcf8/clei666M89Ue6P//Z"
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/easter-tour-2011/images/0_hu_1fcc75c542db5402.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
if (!jQuery) {
alert("jquery is not loaded");
}
$( document ).ready(() =&gt; {
const gallery = $("#gallery-9c082d45b47ea5316133c3f3f0edb991-0");
let swipeboxInstance = null;
gallery.on('jg.complete', () =&gt; {
$(() =&gt; {
$('.lazy').Lazy({
visibleOnly: true,
afterLoad: element =&gt; element.css({filter: "none", transition: "filter 1.0s ease-in-out"})
});
});
swipeboxInstance = $('.galleryImg').swipebox(
jQuery.extend({},
{ }
)
);
});
gallery.justifiedGallery({
rowHeight : "150",
margins : "5",
border : 0,
randomize : false ,
waitThumbnailsLoad : false,
lastRow : "justify",
captions : false,
});
});
&lt;/script&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>