<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Summer Tour on Imperial College Mountaineering</title><link>YAYAYA/categories/summer-tour/</link><description>Recent content in Summer Tour on Imperial College Mountaineering</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="YAYAYA/categories/summer-tour/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Drill and Chill Summer Tour 2022</title><link>YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/cover.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Drill and Chill Summer Tour 2022" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;ICMC had the Summer Tour of 2022 go to the climbing Festival Drill and Chill.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="background"&gt;Background
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="history"&gt;History
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Climbing in Bosnia &amp;amp; Herzegovina is a new pastime, with all of the routes being developed since the millennium and most in the last 10 years. It is a region full of beautiful unclimbed rock and stunning scenery. Very few locals climb, this hampers the growth of the sport as there are very few people who have the skills to develop climbing areas and inspire people to take up the sport. In 2015 the Extreme Club in Banja Luka created the ‘Drill &amp;amp; Chill’ Festival. This sought to bring experienced climbers and highliners from all over the world to the region to develop new climbing routes and to celebrate the unique culture within the sport. Since then it has grown from strength to strength, and is responsible for the development of over 350+ new routes. The festival is located in the beautiful Canyon Tijesno on the outskirts of Banja Luka. It contains some of the region’s finest climbs, with sport routes ranging from easy 5+, to a near impossible 9a as well as a range of adventurous multipitches. The canyon is also ideally suited for highlines, ranging from 35m in length to a regional record breaking 705m line. As well as the climbing the festival has a range of workshops, ranging from juggling and traditional embroidery to acro-yoga and aerial silk. The festival also runs a free bolting course, teaching competent climbers how to develop and bolt new routes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="objectives"&gt;Objectives
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team was keen to experience the beautiful scenery and climbing the region has to offer as well as contribute to the development of the sport in the region. Developing crags and bolting your own route is something that is near impossible in the UK as the climbing scene is very mature and potential sites saturated. Some team members were psyched on creating their own route and developing the local scene, others wanted to push themselves on highlines and all were keen on enjoying the delights of Bosnian limestone. A few wanted to progress into multipitch climbing. Some just wanted to chill after a stressful summer of high frequency trading at one of the city’s top cream sucking firms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="the-team"&gt;The Team
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class="data-table" role="region" tabindex="0" &gt;
&lt;table class="table %!s(&lt;nil&gt;)" id="598342716"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Name&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Role&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Course&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;George Gunn&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Supreme Commander&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Des-Eng&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Elliot Badcock&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Mr Badcock&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;PhD in numbers&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Jake Lewis&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Caffeine Scout&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;PhD in very fast air&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Tim Bickerseth&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Chief Chiller&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Geology&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Liam Gallagher&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Cream Sucker&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;EIE&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Alisha Oner&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Networking&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Biochemistry&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Victor Szwarcberg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Barbie Custodian&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Bioengineering&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;James Gibson&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Strong&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Maths&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;William Lovett-Turner&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Psyche Dealer&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Geology&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="tour-overview"&gt;Tour Overview
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="day-0"&gt;Day 0
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alisha and Tim were keen beans and flew out a day ahead of the main crowd, most of whom were working on Friday. The extortionate cost of roaming data meant their trail went cold shortly after crossing the border into Bosnia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-1"&gt;Day 1
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main pack congregated at Liverpool Street for an early train out to Stanstead. Will and Elliot managed to blag a lift from relatives and so missed out on the egg &amp;amp; bacon breakfast McMuffin. After clearing security, the group stopped off for some light refreshments. Boarding the plane was hairy as some members of the group had come up with creative ways of maximising their hand luggage allowances, much to the dismay of the Ryanair staff. After a short argument Will had managed to convince them that a helmet was an item of clothing, and his roll mat was simply a blanket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/image1.jpg" width="200"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two uneventful hours later we landed in Zagreb. After getting confused by local taxis we made it to the bus stop. George put his incredibly poor Croatian language skills to use and convinced the bus driver that we had 7 tickets through some broken Czech and vigorous hand gestures. We boarded and headed off towards the border. The 8 Bosnians on the bus promptly started smoking creating a veiling haze and giving most members a migrane.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We arrived in Banja Luka a few hours later and stocked up on provisions for the week. We got lucky and managed to stumble upon the only taxi driver in Banja Luka who also climbed and happened to know where the festival was. 40 minutes later we were cruising down the dirt road to the festival site. Upon arrival the group was pleased to find Alisha and Tim, both alive and well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-2"&gt;Day 2
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group were psyched to get going. Jake was starting to panic as we hadn’t found any gas for our stove the day before. Will attended the bolting course theory session. 2 hours of PowerPoint presentations later he worked out bolting was a lot of effort and promptly decided that 5 days of manual labour was not the optimal way to spend a tour. So much for developing the local climbing scene. At least his trad climbing ethical standards are still intact. Jake and George went off to charm a fellow festival attendee into boiling some water for a brew. Upon the first sip of the coffee Jake realised we had bought the most disgusting beans possible, but soldiered on for his caffeine fix, rubbing the remaining grounds into his gums to little added effect. After this it was discovered the camp had a Snack-bar run by Vito, a local legend, who served coffee at reasonable prices. Jake had never been happier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The group spent the rest of the morning day getting acquainted with the site, visiting all the crags and highline spots. Sector ‘Amfiteatar’ proved to be the most inspiring with its stunning setting and steep overhanging walls. Sadly grades started at 6c+ and topped out at Interklemezzo - 9a a route bolted by Adam Ondra, the team decided some warm up routes were needed. After lunch a contingent headed out to sector Vito, where Liam, James, Will and Elliot enjoyed the pleasant at the grade ‘Living La Vito Loca’ – 6a and the slightly chossy ‘One hand minus’ – 5b.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/image2.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tim enjoyed soaking up the chilled atmosphere and continued to make friends with the other festival goers at the camp. George, Jake, Alisha and Victor and ventured out to the 35m highline to test their mettle. Each taking turns to roll out into the middle of the line and soak up the exposure. Jake was mesmerised by the 200m of open air below him, so much so he decided climbing was actually a rubbish sport and he was going to become a highliner instead. George, who had previous highline experience was reminded how painful sitting on the 1” webbing was, especially for the duration of time it took to compose himself before attempting to stand up. He never stood a chance and fell straight off. This would become a recurring theme throughout the week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/image3.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team congregated for dinner, refreshed from the previous days travel and thoroughly psyched for the week ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-3"&gt;Day 3
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day 3 started with the team attending a functional breathing workshop. Tim, Alisha, Victor and especially Will getting invested in the practice. George and Jake were finding it hard to keep a straight face as the coach explained the kidneys stored all the soul’s trauma, over the sound of 50 hyperventilating climbers. They made a B-Line for Vito’s to get their morning caffeine fix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/image4.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;James, Will, Victor, Elliot and Alisha headed out to sector Krilo and finally found some rock that was more secure. Some highlights of the day include ‘Paprika’ – 5c which all the team managed to tick, whilst strong James eased back in after an injury by climbing ‘Dirty Dan’ – 6B which was then repeated by Victor and Will. Over at the highlines, George, Jake and Liam were making progress towards their goal of standing up. This involved a lot of falling followed by an equal amount of shouting. The Trio decided to mask their inadequacy and build their confidence by hanging upside-down from the lines instead of walking them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/image5.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After regrouping at dinner, the team prepared themselves for a big night: the drill and chill Triathlon. This team event involved a timed race across 3 disciplines: rope coiling, 10 pullups and drinking a beer whilst on a slackline. Sadly we did not make it out of the selection phase and were forced to watch from the side-lines. The team quickly forgot this disappointment and started enjoying the rest of the evening. To add to the misery, DJ Baba Djex was unable to make it and instead we were treated to a evening of Jawharp music. This was complemented nicely by a substantial quantity of local brandy known as ‘Rakia’. Jake and Elliot seemed to lose themselves in the tribal tones as the team danced the evening away. Tim’s networking earlier in the week paid dividends as he was offered a shot on the stage playing a jaw harp. He did the team proud, and despite not attracting the attention of any record labels on his debut, he held his own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/image6.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-4"&gt;Day 4
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nursing a slight headache from the day before, the team decided to make the most of the workshops on offer and take a rest day. After two visits to Vito’s Jake was just about feeling human again and the pack headed to the forest chill zone. Here a large space net was found, and the team proceeded to do very little for the next few hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/image7.jpg" width="400"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first workshop of the day was in the art of Aerial Silk acrobatics. The team took to this like ducks to water. After a few pointers, Will was able to string together a series of moves, taking in two elegant poses whilst fully embracing his inner swan. He swiftly forgot the details for the subsequent move and ended tying himself in a knot on the floor and in need of a rescue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/image8.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The group then ventured to the highlines in an attempt to do something with the day. Victor and Tim made their maiden voyage out onto the lines, whilst Liam struck up a conversation with some people playing the guitar. Tim later leveraged his newfound musical reputation to form a band with them, and they promptly released their first single “like a butterfly”. This went down a treat, with the rest of the highliners joining in for the chorus. Rumor has it their EP drops in early December.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That evening a classic Bosnian film was shown in camp. It covered the trials and tribulations of two pioneering Bosnian hip-hop artists as they navigated their way through failed relationships to fame in Yugoslavia. Whilst not suitable for the British cinema industry, it didn’t stop a few team members from having a good chuckle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/image9.jpg" width="200"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-5"&gt;Day 5
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The objective of the day was to climb a route bolted by George the year prior, ‘Crack and forth’ – 6a+. The team headed out to sector Jazbina, only to find the sector shut and the bolting course attendees hanging 30m above our heads. A swift retreat to sector Vito followed. George, Victor and Alisha enjoyed excursions up the delighful ‘Veni, Vidi, Vito’ – 6a and the less delightful ‘Livin la vito loca’ – 6a+. Will, James and Liam kept themselves occupied and tackled the more difficult ‘Einfach Tapfer Sein’ – 6b. Jake and Elliot had a hairy experience on ‘Illatos Olomos’- 4+ which seemed to have more trees than a medium sized arboretum. This killed their psyche for the day and they headed back to camp to further develop their aerial silk skills. George and Victor later tried to repeat Einfach Tapfer Sein but to little success. The team returned to camp and enjoyed a traditional local cabbage soup dinner with accompanying burek.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/image10.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-6"&gt;Day 6
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team was full of psyche on the last full day. With reports of bad weather brewing in the afternoon they set off early to make the most of the day. Shortly after setting off the wind and rain rolled in. The window in Will and James’ tent decided it was the perfect opportunity to detach itself, leaving an 8” hole for the menacing rain. As any self-respecting engineer would do, George decided the obvious answer was duct tape and a Sainsburys bag. 10 minutes later the tent was good as new, Will initially doubted the repairs integrity, however preferred this to the porta-loo alternative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/image11.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully the rain packed quickly, and after a few hours of drying we headed out back to the rock. Victor took the opportunity to take climbing barbie to new heights on ‘Honeymoon Suite’ - 6a, whilst George got to the top of the route he bolted the year before ‘Crack and Forth’. The send train was then left the station with Will, Victor, Liam and James also ticking the route. Jake pushed himself and ticked ‘Toxic MascuGINity’ – 5c as did Elliot shortly after.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/image12.jpg"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pack then headed to Sector Amfiteatar for the afternoon. Will was keen to try something hard and hoped on ‘Hustensaft’ – 6c+, which he onsighted, but not without a few expletives. Strong James not to be outdone, then repeated the route. George and Victor raced up ‘Good boy’ – 6b. George, Jake, Liam and Tim had one more go on the highlines and failed to make any significant progress. Before they could get a second attempt the wind picked up and the lines started oscillating, they figured it was safer to retreat to the camp and get a beer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Due to the weather the goodbye party was moved a day earlier, and the team took full advantage. After getting bored of the light show, Elliot embraced his inner ‘Mr Badcock’ and put his PGCE to good use by organising a festival wide game of hide and seek. None of the team got lost and we quickly congregated around the slacklines to attempt some night slacking. This was unsuccessful, with most of the team making fools of themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-7"&gt;Day 7
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team awoke to it chucking it down. It was clear nothing was going to climbed that day, and packed the tents down in misery. We then said our goodbyes and left the festival site. Tim decided to cancel his flight and venture onwards to a Hungarian Jawharp festival with his new friends Bruno, Dan and Sophie. The remainder of the pack got back on the early bus to Zagreb. We stashed our bags at the station and decided to explore what Zagreb had to offer. After finding the main cathedral was under repair, Liam and James decided to flip a coin at each junction they encountered to explore the less visited parts of the city. The remainder of the pack ventured to a park, where Elliot climbed the final route of the trip ‘Playground’ - 7c+, then decided we needed to find a pub. Luckily James and Liam’s coin had a similar idea, and the group congregated to reminisce about the tour. We then headed to Zagreb airport and found a comfortable corner to setup camp for the night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/image13.jpg" width="250"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-8"&gt;Day 8
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the sound of ‘please do not leave your baggage unattended’ being blared over the tannoy every 15 minutes, it’s safe to say the team did not find themselves well rested in the morning. After boarding the flight most passed out to recoup the lost sleep. We landed in London and went our separate ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Footnote:&lt;/strong&gt;
After a further 10 days cruising around Europe with his new friends, Tim safely returned to London to continue his geology degree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="conclusion--lessons-learnt"&gt;Conclusion &amp;amp; Lessons Learnt
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, the tour was a massive success. Everyone had pushed themselves either through climbing or highlining. The team developed new skills in the art of aerial silk, embroidery, juggling, acro-yoga and music. Liam returned more chilled than ever before and ready to suck some more cream. Most importantly, the team were all exposed to opportunities they would not have had within the UK. The outdoor climbing experience of group members was significantly improved, and all were exposed to highlining for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite all the things achieved, we did not completely fulfil our aims. Many had wanted to climb some multi-pitch routes. The multipitch routes in the canyon rarely get climbed, leading to lots of vegetation growing in the holds, and the routes remaining ‘dirty’. This makes them much harder than the grade indicated. They are also quite committing with an abseil in approach meaning the route needs to be climbed in full to get back to the camp. The team all displayed sound judgement and adapted their aims to ones that could be achieved safely, an attitude that is a credit to them. I would recommend all future tour leaders to not be afraid of changing plans based on the conditions you find on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="future-development"&gt;Future Development
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a strong desire within the club to do more highlining. Since returning we have acquired a slackline for the club so members can develop these skills in London. Building on this another tour to a highline venue could be a possibility in the years going forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script src="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/jquery-3.7.0.min.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/lazy/jquery.lazy.min.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/swipebox/js/jquery.swipebox.min.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;link rel="stylesheet" href="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/swipebox/css/swipebox.min.css"&gt;
&lt;script src="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/justified_gallery/jquery.justifiedGallery.min.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;link rel="stylesheet" href="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/justified_gallery/justifiedGallery.min.css"/&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;div id="gallery-c9f96fd84620e75b7e3d9960fda73849-14-wrapper" class="gallery-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;div id="gallery-c9f96fd84620e75b7e3d9960fda73849-14" class="justified-gallery"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220910_105926%280%29.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AH3MgSN57qKM498n9f61Lpul2&amp;#43;p7XZliA5dUILfTHp71YGil1KiCQHHBZY3AP4tSafot3Y3L&amp;#43;VdXCs6nP&amp;#43;jgD653Y61tDENfaf4kukn0Lz6RpSShYdNlmVRksZD&amp;#43;tV4dBhWQF4lC5OAzc498ZFQ69cX&amp;#43;nWwcXzb34jQwj5j1OTk9vpVpLW8mG&amp;#43;O&amp;#43;BHYkVt9baVrsydBXNzA9KZk72Ge1Ppn8bfSvNOx7GXN&amp;#43;8fD/ADAnnPNaOxYzsRQqjoFGAKzpP9Z&amp;#43;Nab/AOsP1qYdTmw&amp;#43;7P/Z"
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220910_105926%280%29_hu_8ee6d947ca319d2c.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220911_115624.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/ALf9uTQsQj8elZOqX8txOJJBkZ7VnTXM0cyK6kFuVPrSwzvNIRkcHkN6d6OdjsVpJ2w5L4GcKv8An8Kg&amp;#43;0bY3IPzsRjA6AUt8himKsuFPKMOjCqTMOgquZisbMrF9AVmJZhIoBPJHy1nxkq6EHB2dqvv/wAi9/21X/0Gs9PvJ/uVhIp7l3WebSH8P5VkTcSDHHyitfWf&amp;#43;PSH/gP8qyJ/9YP90VfVAz//2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220911_115624_hu_43b9dce3c63bbf84.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220911_122440.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AOkg8c6VgSfaWUHj5hjn0qWHxlotzNlLxYSOu7IrygmIWu1o2YA/LIOClTPBePqRs3tmN0UAZcc9Bgn36VarR6mV2erXXiOyYkpqcAj9WfFU/wDhJtGh&amp;#43;aS/iP8Augt/IVwOowWdtKLeCU/u12y7chSR/PnvVRTCJBgI0hPyq2CMVhPFpOyQanV6nDFFqUwjiRMRu42qBhsnn61laxI8XiJ3jdkZ9gZlOCeO9bGr/wDISn/64v8AzNYuuf8AIfP1X&amp;#43;Vc0fhZvU2M52YWwYMcs53HPX5TUcpO2A55&amp;#43;YZ/Onyf8eif75/9BNRy/ct/q39a5Uc5/9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220911_122440_hu_6ab67aaab59ec14a.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220911_183504.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AMWNCb9mAAiWNSRnI5Hb9a3PDiNPc3VljjAlQe3Q/wBKyPPjiia3u5USWOQbWxyw/h/pUR1F/tqNYzmCaLI3qcHBrqpycHcwmlKNjt5NOW2TfORGvv1P4Vn3mo29lFHIls8vmNtTJxuP064rgbrxRrL3B&amp;#43;0X9x5qDa3zdfT8OlS6b4ou0v47i7likXG3dLHu2AemO/SssRXxT/h2SHSp0F8dyfxNwVxxhyBj021zdmzN57FiTwMk89RXSeJ&amp;#43;3/XQ/wDoIrmrL7s31H8xWdXcOhduwDbzkgE7P61UiUFIwQORz781cuv&amp;#43;Paf/AHDVSH7kX&amp;#43;6P51nHYg//2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220911_183504_hu_d269cf044b2c7986.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_114325.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AOdXUpVHmwTtsB5Qn7tdDoviLUbYhrObazfeUtlW/CuBS5xIXAAPp2rd0S6CXqGMfKxP7sjPOOx/Wt3UcVYz5bs7tPF&amp;#43;qwq0lx5YUsAEUDJ556isDxFLLNFLJdPKZVHLM&amp;#43;VOcZXHYelQSyGaV4wTvwNgBxkHGP1zVq/vGuNNFsuDPLtVmJ&amp;#43;Vj1/oKxk3Lc0SS2POu/410Oh8eYRwRHHg&amp;#43;mXGf5Cud/xrotE6S/8AXOL/ANDoqbEo2H/4/wAe0fH5VJY/vH0tX&amp;#43;ZXlXcDyG5frUb/APH9/wBsv6CpNO/1uk/9dF/m9J/Ey47H/9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_114325_hu_2014e8f96203e3f0.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_121506.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AKSAkySqqSQeY/lDnnjp7dfw/CpmSV4biK2lYnI2lmJBbOQB&amp;#43;Rq5ZQWl5YwoWZWGQqFeRnrxnnvz9PSrb2Qilje3ErPGTwxHGehx2xjtWUOjQW6M5O1vY1ut9yGIT5V3Lkj5uQc98ZqjBPcXU8ty84jijJcGRjt3dsep7D61o&amp;#43;IoYor4XHz/AOkoD8g6uDhwPfj9c81g3RaOIbJfNt92Yz2yf5HiupVLmTVjqtHdv7QX5jxnHPTiuog5t/MP3ynLdzXLaP8A8hAfU/yrqbf/AI8x/uVyYf4TRbGV4mjjbwxLuRThSwyOhyOfrXDR83toD/y0gUv/ALRPUn1rvPEv/Irzf9cz/MVwcX/H7Yf9e6Va&amp;#43;MHsz//Z"
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_121506_hu_421daf32306d721b.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_130527.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AI7hIUlivRKQ02BKF6I5Hc4&amp;#43;n9Knsri5gvVuRLksScKflRiOmD6E/wAqjsLYTySJGzlo0ISNmyMnvirK2F6AXWP5k&amp;#43;dSzcZzg8f/AKu3rXNB31RVrbnE6trl/dzst1cySztxiToDnoB2HsBUF9dR6bZ20IXe8ys74PPXA/Vc1qeMtGjWWHUbViGnfyps8DzOCCPTP9K5m8MSagkjpI0agDn&amp;#43;Ij09q9SE00mczVmehW/yasrJ8pLLyOK2nGbYg8/umH/jprFi/wCQov8AvLW2/wDx7n/rk3/oJryqXU7JGD4xUDwndYAG1o2Hsd5Ga4GD59On3/NiMsM84O4DNd/4y/5FO8&amp;#43;sX/ow1wFt/wAg64/64n/0IV6FL4Tnluf/2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_130527_hu_7c6e40241d985ff4.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_133604.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AKQluGkNxDJJtXAAjOTuAHJz3561Jq2rXDt9ru5pZEY4RC2Qo9PbJB6UggZZXWFWIXIVggJCsex9&amp;#43;P8AJNS3WlJeWUkFxG0bwri3UL1YA5PHHP8AhRTnr5ENXMq6vTY6Gk2A808uGK&amp;#43;mM/1FYt5cyQKImJjDINwHVjUk93INNtrSJVkjj/eyMrfez2I9P8ayLqd5py8jFmPUmuuE31Mmj1ezVVtpWVQDkjIHbIqOMk6ixJOQqY/Naltf&amp;#43;PSX6/4VDH/yEH/3E/mlcEPhR0I82vP3etzrH8gE7ABeMDJ4qteAC7cY48wfyqzf/wDIcuP&amp;#43;vhv/AEKq95/x&amp;#43;P8A9dB/KuxGJ//Z"
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_133604_hu_bcc9cbd2b46b3dad.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_140116.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="338" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAEgMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AM9Ed7RmiVo44FH3yDg9gcYzVeTUrg2glYkHOCAejD1xRZatplzMbaB5HJ2ljs4LdMDPPf8AWti80&amp;#43;30jUlieeJ4wo3KoLMv905HX06fjWEqMtJSRmqfRHPDUpGG4zxgnkgyGj&amp;#43;0H/5&amp;#43;I/8Av4a1k1O3WNVkuIN4ADYgkxnv2p39q2n/AD8Q/wDfiT/Cj2IvZMqJpM1mI7pRED5wdU8vJL54yB1PHTIrVt7u0vJpYrmEyC3xmV1Kg9MdeR16Z7E0zUCwtIrZFZdxBAU5xj&amp;#43;VSxCSKAR/M6yqCUcBuefXnjtXVWetnqaUiqLKzYBhbxgHnq5pfsNn/wA8I/8AyJWqumz7RmCHp6il/s2f/nhD&amp;#43;dY3kaaH/9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_140116_hu_56e27b95d3c77d8d.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_142510.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AK&amp;#43;nWkulEx3NxHc2867dqjjHv7ckVnW2nNb69b&amp;#43;QrQW7Hjz2XLeuPXjFb0tmXslubh2ihjXdImSduB94Dk//AFhWN4l1SG1awm8uSRVXzIrkoVDEnITB6dAaxpVqzd&amp;#43;/3GappvU1LmSyie5&amp;#43;0wm6t4WzsMRIXcCCR2x69aoT3JkuheRgRxB1C44K/dOeOlMTUrTXEZUnlfMhmePJBUnsTwMfzqa5vYJbl1EX7mVcSTNtyW6fQcDPAxwamUnVmqUdzVwjGLle1je1B3jtNqOyhoXJCnAPFctpkaS358xFfIIO4Z/5aJXT6l/x7D/ri/8AKua0j/j/AD9D/wChpXXhdmTV6G1qv/H5L/srgewz0rn/ABUoS0sigCkq2cDHpXQat/x&amp;#43;TfT&amp;#43;orA8Wf8AHnY/7rfyFcWB/wCRjH1f5Gdf&amp;#43;Gz/2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_142510_hu_9104e3b90245d073.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_161533.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AOjsfHkqRMjkuQgIEgww6g/jWJq/iW/vYZ3Ri0aKHZ1J&amp;#43;VeO31Iqmgt7eR8wKhY5POSe/Q1I62s8RYRRO&amp;#43;OpGM/kKj6yuw/YtrU5/V9ZkmVLcqsgjiwzRtnf3B/XFZ7XnCpFKqEA/d6A&amp;#43;p45rrDbwjCJEEBXBCt19gAOnv8ApXMXXh3yWb7MxwCTtk6D8afteZ6lPDO10bchJnBJPG3HtxU9uBlzjpnHtyarv/rv&amp;#43;&amp;#43;f5VZt/&amp;#43;Wn1P8zXCi47ocxPkSHPeq8bFoMMSeR1&amp;#43;hqdv&amp;#43;PeT61BF/qR/vD&amp;#43;RoNp7xP/2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220912_161533_hu_d9f6698ec96a6022.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220913_125108.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/ALGqu/7t7c9E3P5jdG9KhtL6WyeMeWrnGQ6kZdDk8k&amp;#43;/8qY11e3LBZkdg3KMAc/WpVEUAC7FLFcY&amp;#43;U8&amp;#43;vFdDqta3sZezT3JpNUSUgOpRWYHB/lmqN1evZXMjNPuQ8iMkgDgdOapXGpBWk8y0Vznk8r/IiqUqpeOIoyhMoyAWx&amp;#43;Bz35rmxFStK3NqghShH4SfVppZdYYySu&amp;#43;DgbmJwKrXUsiByrsu3pg4xU2pf8hd/wDeqtefdk/Gqkal2GR3sVdnYs0eSSeTyKr6eoJkyAeCKmt/&amp;#43;Qen/XIfzFQ6d1kpUthM/9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220913_125108_hu_789ce4c482868d9e.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220914_091839.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AONe&amp;#43;W3Ro92cnHmISQaRNQPmKYSDxncRyDW4fDOIwnnnqCqlRk0LohQ7QyMB/Cy4z/hUKpBq1zK8e5jrfylHZpQW5yAvXA9c/SqhmmlSdt7HGMZPfIroG0IGIscNJuGMHIA78d6YfDka48w7t3IHf8afPBD5orVHQwEkRE8k4qxIoa7lLAH5CefXFV4Puw/hVh/&amp;#43;PuX/AHD/ACrhW5BQmYqQVJB9Qag3Nktk5HQ56VNP2qDs1a9DNn//2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220914_091839_hu_c3c08fb69cc76b3c.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220914_123338.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="338" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAEgMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/APNredgVkbgFwR&amp;#43;GK6KHUUtL15ZJMO2yPjrgKM1labpc2pmOK3iMu0nzCOig9ye3Q/lWjc2EM3nSwO5wrSgMobjJ7g8VDpuSuiNHp1IptemeZ3DEbmJxupn9uTf3z&amp;#43;dZ32Sc9k/76o&amp;#43;yT&amp;#43;if99VHJEXIyzpkup6XdLeW0xhkXnIGfwPqK2bW/wDt2q380oUS3kD4RRgZxnAH4VHgAZ2lgP8APFKEIcsG8s4/h9PTitFJ2sdMVGLvYgCHH&amp;#43;qX8qNh/wCea/lS7M8icc&amp;#43;tHln/AJ7r&amp;#43;dRcXMf/2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220914_123338_hu_f000366360aaaa.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220914_145457.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="338" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAEgMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AOOlaafTIolRTLHdlNo/2gMfyNLrDFdbuY9y5jX5Wx94BBj9BWlpFq0a3E10o5HneXnn5e/cZyT&amp;#43;VS&amp;#43;KLOA65PLAnmIyDGzsWTv&amp;#43;tJr3bmdl2OWH2raMKSMcHaaXF3/dP/fBq4ILoAAK&amp;#43;B0&amp;#43;Y0eTd&amp;#43;j/APfR/wAaxHyy7HQuHis1Ib5roHIA5AB4Ptk5/KqbSGOGMRws2QckHvk&amp;#43;tOllAJ2g4x296ruTndhsHOMGrbbVjo5UGbo8ncD6DZx&amp;#43;lGbr1b/xz/CjeeyMfxNG8/3G/M1nyoj2UT//2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220914_145457_hu_73ab57bf61bf8b50.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220914_152622.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="338" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAEgMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AOOk1RpZ2lLFMt8xz0GPWrolSXT52EgZWKxqobJPU/8Asoqrb2s0Yk3QQkT/ACHeM7Bx8wHQfnmrl1aTWenW2ZPmk3yqghHK8AZ59j&amp;#43;ZrmVO/vGEoapCpK8SLHGgKINq5UHgdKX7TN/zzX/vgVjm/ugfuxfjGD/Sj7fdf3Yv&amp;#43;/Q/wqeRl&amp;#43;zZ2NmkGo6pHYS3vkzTdxHwRnnoP51FrkVrBqDRi7&amp;#43;1JCAivggKB2HGOPameXGznKAkfxAcg1DLyDGQAxOAx6VupLlsdL3uUDLpuTndmk83TP8Aaq39hjPJC5P0/wAaPsMf91f8/jUXH7x//9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220914_152622_hu_281e27499cd85f1d.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220915_085314.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="453"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABgAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AMkgFAHJA6YXvWvpGlRTQSSQxwqynaGmJJb1HtWEJy0pyMKq8e5rc0vWILeJI54zGiL1Ubt3r&amp;#43;Z/nXPGMowvFXZdKEHK1R2RPJZRXEMhWJYLiBtkiqMj2bHpisK&amp;#43;YwOtusaLJxlwOg9quWGoyDV5pCw/0jJI7ZzkD&amp;#43;Yp2qxwSWxlY8A8Hvz2rolCPxWMmuxir54lYqiA4/iJ59qVpbsjDICD3Emf6VO3&amp;#43;sP1pv8Ayz/GsFUkkbOK3K0M7RzBjGw2/wCexqaW4mmQFxlVOQo7e/1qFali&amp;#43;4/0NJ1JS0ZlbU//2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220915_085314_hu_7e53fa3a1df14bf9.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220915_100201.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="338" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAEgMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AL9re22pRGS71b7FcL/qo2jIXpgHI/Cry&amp;#43;I7bSHV47pr0LGVfy87XOTxz/n61xFyrtot40sB2hVdGZMbsZPB/wAKZo2mXF5HcNDZi2ZZArB36fKD357/AK1m6mlybWVzrW1Lw7KxkbTRlzk5U96Pt3hz/oGr/wB8msn&amp;#43;z5U&amp;#43;U24JHGQ3X9aPsMv/AD7f&amp;#43;PD/ABqPb&amp;#43;ZN13KKzJ9klt5YCylQEXOM54OfTip7RxbJIIowkUjbzyTg4A/pVJG3Jke1WA5C8dT35rl5ny8o7vlsWvt0o6KaPt03901RM8YJBkGR1&amp;#43;Wk&amp;#43;0Rf89R/3zWXKZ2P/9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220915_100201_hu_a142c389ec2d283d.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220915_103405.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/ANFvG2mqihorh93IDoo/rWtY&amp;#43;LtL8gPFfiMt/wAs5AQR/MV5rf6JeWZUPbuXRQwuYx8rcgYwR15qG3866uGiS3P73&amp;#43;6p2oe5HpVqtHZmfvI9aHifTRuaS/txnoWkx/MVSm8ZaRET5l8rY7ICf5CvNLwWoumWByYgcY6DPIqKNY5AY4ghJOHLjPP1rnni0nog1N7U5pW8Oxu0jlty8ljntUiTSx6erJK6n7N1DEH/AFgqDUf&amp;#43;Raj/AN9f6U//AJhy/wDXr/7UFZS3OjqZmqswjiOTklsnPXms&amp;#43;85ty/8AFkHd361f1X/VRfVv51Qu/wDj0P1H/oVc63MHuf/Z"
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220915_103405_hu_b9a1526de813f2ba.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220915_132347.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AOGEMolbf8oA&amp;#43;93PtXQeBds2pXO5wpjQsF9c45/SuannkBIK8HvW14Qjk8yRoJPmCnIOMOD2/SsYXuET0Lav2QuqoHdiAx6kD/8AXWPen7OfMlfPOAAOSfpWnOGv0SO0aN/LbBOeB69KT&amp;#43;z4raYS3P7yUNlGAyF9PxroV7aDe55ZcIrOdyg4J6iuo8BKuZhgYITIx7GuZm&amp;#43;&amp;#43;fqa6fwF9&amp;#43;X/gH8jXPT2Jid03ywnbxz2rMnYlhkk/PWm/&amp;#43;pP1rLm&amp;#43;8P8AfrqWwH//2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220915_132347_hu_d688bb0c3a3e7064.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220915_180905.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AMC701W1W6jckZjygx6bc4A9/wCVTxrHFMI1H&amp;#43;qG0YH5/rVmFGWWKSZg04jKnA5YEDkD61FZQDzJmckZYEKeuDzz/ntUMtHe&amp;#43;Eb43mhfZ5CTLaHyznrt6r/h&amp;#43;FXZuGxXGaBqQ0nxD&amp;#43;&amp;#43;kEcF0m1s9M54/X&amp;#43;ddpJMpbkV0xldGMlZnmWnM0li7uxZgowxOSPkFWnVQ0pAAPPIH0qnpn/IOk/3B/wCgCrsnWX8f6VzS3No9ShrP3z7Rkj24rqzNL9mVvNfOwc7j6Vyms/eP/XI/yNdQf&amp;#43;PVf9wfyralsZVNz//Z"
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220915_180905_hu_c260a0b66e02515c.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220916_174052.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="338"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AOVNzLNcea24q2Acjqcf4itxJnv1iscyIiwu&amp;#43;N3cKSP5CsRboghTcrIoGArxtj9GFTwX0ltJ5sc8aybdu4RMcLjGMFyP0rJVYrqRzxCO9f7PKuziQqGZgQVwccdsVFHqLpPIQ5G5yMjkgdM1Dej7RYSW8EiozY5II7565Jp6PGkMayPK7qACdwxkdxxU&amp;#43;1W4nJFFRwT3FOycDk0g&amp;#43;6aXsKxJHKSXGSTwKsWIBlYEZG8dfrVdPvr9BViw/wBc3&amp;#43;&amp;#43;v866qextDY//Z"
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220916_174052_hu_1bdbb7f20b7ae7e8.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220916_180742.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="338" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAEgMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/APQrrUFtDbKWAM8yxjPvTk1KKTU57FZEMkSK2A3POf8AAfnXM&amp;#43;Ir5ft1nhHZrQ&amp;#43;a2MgN3AyM91FY&amp;#43;k3U9x41guVhm2SyMSygbACD3z2rVyV7EKLtc9GzRmk3LRuWqsQec3WoxXc8lxG/mQyqMMuMEYFVrC7FtFFJE4/dybtyABeo96wklntgsayl4gixpDjgD&amp;#43;8T68Utq91FELdHR/mOc8k5rlad7nUmkrHdt450lWKm7XIODzSf8J1pH/P2v515&amp;#43;3huV3LeQeTn7rf40n/CMy/88D/3y3&amp;#43;Nb&amp;#43;0ZjyI//9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220916_180742_hu_2f9a67c8203bbdfa.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220916_194640.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="338" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAEgMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AN1/FVqE/fQy8jkoucVk395ZajC7WlwshA5U8MKybPUhb6hC3zsTG4AQgEnHFZur3u&amp;#43;7eRg0UgiUNv4JOTzXkqlFrmR2tSTsweF97fX0pvkv/kVkJcQ&amp;#43;Wu6b5sDP70/4077RB/z2H/f1v8ar2ZlYr2MkmoyRwoGMjNhVB9abq9tPpqmORQCx5KtuBx71nWV3JZ3QmjOGVsiui1y/tNY0e18plWVWwydxxXS1yvyISujlvNFHmCnG0kBxtNJ9lf8AumtbojlZ/9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220916_194640_hu_64719944809204ea.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220916_195100.jpg"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="338" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAEgMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AJNHt/KUEFQqdVHb612ujzZCmMgZ6cYNeZ290&amp;#43;l6LGYZW3Sz5Zu5GOf5Cuk8L66DcBCcttJyTWUIq9zolLSx6ejHy1z1wKdmsyLU1aJD6qDTv7SWtTGx4dLbPPplpDEy4jyxyeefT9auaFb3FleLLLjayEAg5/z0rK3yeRAyNgqoO05x0xVuxvJyEWbaNg2rt9OT/WuZTsrG/J1O7j1ULEg3dFAp39rD&amp;#43;9XHfa2/vfrR9rb&amp;#43;9&amp;#43;tVzCsf/9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/drill-and-chill-summer-tour-2022/images/20220916_195100_hu_570684f505ec19b4.jpg"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
if (!jQuery) {
alert("jquery is not loaded");
}
$( document ).ready(() =&gt; {
const gallery = $("#gallery-c9f96fd84620e75b7e3d9960fda73849-14");
let swipeboxInstance = null;
gallery.on('jg.complete', () =&gt; {
$(() =&gt; {
$('.lazy').Lazy({
visibleOnly: true,
afterLoad: element =&gt; element.css({filter: "none", transition: "filter 1.0s ease-in-out"})
});
});
swipeboxInstance = $('.galleryImg').swipebox(
jQuery.extend({},
{ }
)
);
});
gallery.justifiedGallery({
rowHeight : "150",
margins : "5",
border : 0,
randomize : false ,
waitThumbnailsLoad : false,
lastRow : "justify",
captions : false,
});
});
&lt;/script&gt;</description></item><item><title>Summer Tour 2021</title><link>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Summer Tour 2021" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Oliver Tippett&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="background"&gt;Background
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="history"&gt;History
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fontainebleau (Font) was used to practice the skills necessary for alpinism since the
1870s, but since the 1930s it has solidly established itself as one of the premier
bouldering destinations in the world. Everywhere you look there is something to
climb, with soft sandy landings and old shoeless Frenchmen offering advice on
technique. The boulders in Font are made of soft sandstone, which often forms very
rounded, chest shaving tops to boulders that can make even the most elegant of
climbers look like a beached whale. It is also world famous for its ridiculously
technical and sandbagged slabs that are incredibly useful for popping an overinflated
ego. It is also home to classic boulders of every grade, from &lt;em&gt;La Marie Rose&lt;/em&gt; (f6a+), to
&lt;em&gt;Carnage&lt;/em&gt; (f7b+) and &lt;em&gt;Rainbow Rocket&lt;/em&gt; (f8a). Moreover, every sector in Font will have
a couple of circuits. These comprise of about 50 easier problems and the aim is to
complete all of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fontainebleau was made famous to us by the movie &lt;em&gt;The Real Thing&lt;/em&gt; , a 1996 classic
full of techno and hard climbing featuring Jerry Moffatt and Ben Moon. In this they
train on the gritstone boulders of Derbyshire and then come over to teach the French
how to climb on their own rock. Spurred on by our club trips to the Peak, we were
determined to make the journey to Font to do the same!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="objectives"&gt;Objectives
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;After more than a year of COVID and lockdowns, our main objective was to be able
to travel abroad safely and responsibly. We all made sure to read up on the current
guidelines about international travel before setting off and adhered to all necessary
testing. It was unfortunate that the associated costs with extra testing in France and
on return to the UK made the trip prohibitively expensive for many potential
attendees. This limited our numbers to a small group of 8, but this served to
strengthen the relationships made within the group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also aimed to enjoy ourselves whilst staying safe as well as to sample some of
the French culture and language. This was done with great aplomb at the Lidl bakery
section. We all had our own climbing objectives for the trip, which are detailed below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="the-team"&gt;The Team
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="data-table" role="region" tabindex="0" &gt;
&lt;table class="table %!s(&lt;nil&gt;)" id="732496851"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Name&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Role&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Degree&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Year&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Aim&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Olly Tippett&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Tour Leader&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Mech Eng&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;4th&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Do Rainbow Rocket, some circuits and slabs&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Jake Lewis&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Tour Organiser&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Aero&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;4th&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Climb a f7a, 100 boulder problems&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Miguel &amp;ldquo;One Move f7a&amp;rdquo; Boland&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;One Move f7a Eliminate Fetishist&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;One Move f7a training&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;f7a&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Climb a one move f7a eliminate&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Emyr Williams&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;The Slab Hero&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Aero&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;4th&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Get back into climbing post COVID and do a full circuit.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;James Gibson&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;The Wad&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Maths&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;3rd&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Flash everyone else&amp;rsquo;s projects&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Chorley King&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Monsieur Dyno&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Aero&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;3rd&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Climb a f7a&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Ben Jones&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;The Medic&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Medicine&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;4th&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Climb a f7 in Font&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;George Gun&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Le Garçon Large&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Des Eng&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;3rd&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Climb a f7a&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="overview-of-the-tour"&gt;Overview of the tour
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="itinerary"&gt;Itinerary
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h4 id="day-1-19921"&gt;Day 1 (19/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first day was spent travelling to Fontainebleau. Olly
drove his van with a few pads to the campsite and set up
in the early afternoon. He was then joined by Miguel,
Jake, James, and Emyr who had driven a separate car
from England. They all set up the brand-new tent and
were excited by its lack of mould and holes. A tarp was
set up from the van to some trees to construct a sitting
area for when it rained. They had just missed the season
for the campsite swimming pool being open, so had to
settle for the occasional shower with poor water pressure. Eager to get climbing, the
early to arrive people ventured out to &lt;em&gt;Gorge aux Chats,&lt;/em&gt; the local crag to the
campsite. There they acquainted themselves with the local rock and attempted the
softest problem in Font, &lt;em&gt;Dallain&lt;/em&gt; (f6c). It was a one move dyno that most people did to
make them feel better about themselves after getting completely shut down by a
desperate f3+ slab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/van.png" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/ben.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a brief tickle of the rocks, Olly had to leave
to pick up Ben and George from the train station.
By the time this was done it was getting dark, so
everyone met back at the campsite. The team
cooked chilli sin carne and ate it very quickly. The
evening concluded with everyone sipping on
cheap tiny French beers, when suddenly the
question arose, where was Chorley?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/jake_ben.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-2-20921"&gt;Day 2 (20/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;That night, everyone could hear the sound of
rain on the tent, signalling a mandatory rest
day. Sandstone is very fragile when wet, so it
is very bad form to try to climb it after rain. This
meant that they decided to walk the 25 mounds
circuit of the forest. It was about 13 miles and
took in 25 hills with over 1000m of vertical
ascent, going through some of the classic
climbing locations. Miguel and Emyr decided to
run this circuit and did so impressively in under
3 hours. The rest got about halfway before
questioning their motivations but had to carry
on as it was the shortest way back. They all arrived back shortly before dark, all
grumpy that they had to go for a massive trek rather than climb.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/jake.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, Miguel had picked Chorley up from the train station, and everyone
was now at the campsite. Chorley had to undergo a Flixbus nightmare. His bus was
late on the ferry, meaning that he missed his connection. After being ushered onto a
seemingly random coach, he had to check maps on his phone to make sure the bus
was in fact destined for Paris. He eventually made it after almost 24 hours of travel.
For dinner, Olly made his famous chorizo carbonara, which everyone managed to
force down, but spirits were high as the forecast looked good for the next few days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/chorley_2.png" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-3-21921"&gt;Day 3 (21/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next morning the team headed to &lt;em&gt;Roche aux
Sabots&lt;/em&gt; , a crag with relatively little forest cover so the
rocks got the sun and dried quicker. The aim was to
complete either the blue or orange circuit over the
course of the day, however for most this changed to
climbing whatever looked cool. Most people got to
about the 20th problem of the circuit before going to try
hard on something else. A group went to try &lt;em&gt;Graviton&lt;/em&gt;
(f7a). The hard part of this was getting over the very
top, which prompted Chorley to
try to jump past the top, resulting in a rash over his chest.
Meanwhile Miguel was working on a boulder called &lt;em&gt;Legalize
This&lt;/em&gt; (f7a). This was a one move f7a eliminate from undercuts
to the top of the block. Miguel was consistently getting his
hand over the top but couldn’t latch the hold. Chorley came
over and sent it, fulfilling his aim of climbing f7a on his first day
climbing. He then repeated the problem next go to get it on
video. Olly also did the problem, first go, in flip flops, proving
once again that he is the greatest climber in the club. Olly had
also achieved his goal of completing the blue circuit that day,
which provided a lot of varied and entertaining boulder
problems. The best of these were recommended to the rest of
the group. Over the day James had done a few f7a and f7a+s without anyone
noticing. At the end of the day, Miguel had to be pulled away from his one move
eliminate f7a project as it was getting dark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/oli_rainbow.png" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/chorley_3.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/george_2.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/17.png" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ben cooked coq au van for dinner, which was delicious and contained a good
amount of red wine although it could not compete with the Lidl “peach rings” that
everyone on the trip had become addicted to by now. Everyone felt thoroughly
knackered by the end of the meal and got to sleep very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-4-22921"&gt;Day 4 (22/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next day most of the team ventured to F &lt;em&gt;ranchard Isatis&lt;/em&gt; , a classic of Font
bouldering areas. Chorley and Olly however went to &lt;em&gt;Franchard Sablons Carriers&lt;/em&gt;
instead in the morning to try their projects. Chorley was trying &lt;em&gt;Sylphide&lt;/em&gt; (f7a) whilst
Olly attempted &lt;em&gt;Rainbow Rocket&lt;/em&gt; (f8a). Both took turns at trying their boulders while
the other rested in the hammock. They each touched the top of their dynos, but neither could stick it. After a couple hours of trying, they both gave up and headed to
&lt;em&gt;Isatis&lt;/em&gt; to meet up with the others. When they got there,
they found that the rest had befriended an old pof-riddled
Frenchman. He was chastising them about using shoes
and crash pads as well as spotting with one hand with a
cigarette in to other. He did show us some good problems
though, as well as Miguel another eliminate f7a dyno for
him to wear his skin more on. Everyone was fairly tired
after the previous day of climbing so were taking it easy,
although a few people went to try some highball problems,
which put hairs on their chests. After a final bit of climbing, they all retreated to the
campsite for some well-earned risotto and rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/18.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/19.png" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/20.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-5-23921"&gt;Day 5 (23/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a brief stop to buy every baguette and
pastry at Lidl, the team ventured to &lt;em&gt;La Canche
aux Merciers&lt;/em&gt; for some more bouldering. This was
a particularly nice crag despite the hordes of
French urchins school children running around
being annoying and the disabled dog that could
boulder harder than any of us to get to our food
bag and eat our cured meats and cheese.
Today’s aim was the same as the others; start
trying to do a circuit, then get distracted and try
something too hard. Olly, Emyr and Jake did
manage to complete their full circuits, whilst
James smashed out some more f7a and f7a+s. A
multitude of other problems were attempted; a
few people tried a f7a+ roof, a few tried some
weird crack, and Miguel found another one move
f7a eliminate. Ben nearly finished the whole
circuit, but got completely shut down by a f3+
slab, which caused most people a lot of
frustration. They left the crag late that evening
with very sore skin and very hungry.
Unfortunately, they had to wait until 11pm for
Jake’s underwhelming spaghetti bolognaise to be
ready, by which time everyone was full from
snacking on too many peach rings and
bolognaise flavoured crisps. They didn’t let Jake
be in charge of cooking again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/21.png" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-6-24921"&gt;Day 6 (24/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;On their penultimate climbing day, the team awoke to a dense
fog. They drove to &lt;em&gt;Bas Cuvier&lt;/em&gt; to see if the rock was dry and
were greeted by a slightly moist crag. The team did some
stretching on the pads while they waited for the rock to dry
and realised that they were all very stiff from all the climbing.
They then warmed up by throwing a
crash pad at each other. By the time
they were bored of this the fog had
cleared, the sun was out, and the rock
was dry. &lt;em&gt;Bas Cuvier&lt;/em&gt; was supposed to
be the most classic crag in Font, however it was strewn with
broken glass, used hypodermic needles, condoms and
human excrement. This rather diminished the psych to
climb, and the rock was quite polished, however the team
tried &lt;em&gt;La Marie Rose&lt;/em&gt; (f6a+), which is potentially the most famous boulder in Font.
James tried to do &lt;em&gt;Carnage&lt;/em&gt; (f7b+) and got close
before giving up. Olly tried to do &lt;em&gt;L&amp;rsquo;Hélicoptère&lt;/em&gt;
(f7a), named for what your legs do when you fall
off. He didn’t do it but he also didn’t break
anything, so that was a win. Miguel couldn’t find a
one move eliminate f7a so was grumpy. George
tried &lt;em&gt;Pif-paf&lt;/em&gt; (f7a), a route named after a powerful
nerve agent cockroach killing spray. He swiftly
gave up due to the problem’s proximity to the
human turd. Well before it was dark, everone
realised that they were absolutely wrecked, so they went back to the campsite via a
pizza place for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/george_3.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/george_4.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-7-25921"&gt;Day 7 (25/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The day began with a trip to the local town to be
tested for COVID before travelling back to the UK.
After and French lady had aggressively swabbed our
noses, we headed to &lt;em&gt;Le Cul de Chien.&lt;/em&gt; This was half
crag half beach and was probably the best one that
the team went to. After a long week with only one rest
day at the very start, the team weren’t psyched on
trying anything too hard, so aimed for another circuit.
This didn’t end up happening for most however, since
as normal they were distracted by a different boulder.
The team tried some f6a+ mantle, which was another
chest scraper. Most people managed this, despite
some astounding inflexibility from Jake. A few people also managed to finish their
circuits after this, and the team made sure to dog proof their food bag. George tried
&lt;em&gt;Le Toit du Cul du Chien&lt;/em&gt; (f7a), which looked a bit like (and is named after) the behind of a dog. He got some good pictures
of him falling off it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miguel, again
unhappy with the lack of one move
f7a eliminates, went back to the
nearby &lt;em&gt;Roche aux Sabots&lt;/em&gt; to try his
one move f7a eliminate project. He
spent a short while trying before
realising that this one move f7a
eliminate wasn’t for him. He decided
in future to change his style and aim
to climb a one move f7a eliminate in
the UK on different rock. A few people
had meanwhile managed a full circuit,
while others lay on the sand trying to
grow back their skin that had been eroded over the week. They drove back to the
campsite for a final night of curry and tiny French beer, sad at the thought of leaving
the next day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2021/images/george_5.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h4 id="day-8-26921"&gt;Day 8 (26/9/21)
&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next morning they woke up and packed the tent
up. After checking out the campsite, Miguel drove his
car back to the UK. Olly and George had booked a
later ferry before going back in the van, so went to
have a final look at &lt;em&gt;Rainbow Rocket&lt;/em&gt; , but it was wet
after an overnight shower, so they drove back and
ate chips in Calais waiting for their ferry. The team
made the most of their duty free allowance, George
hasn’t been able to walk in a straight line since he got
back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="tour-review"&gt;Tour Review
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We all achieved negative COVID results both in
France and on return of the UK, which meant that we
had fulfilled our goal of not spreading the virus. We
had also had a week of climbing with no injuries or
major dramas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In terms of personal climbing objectives, only Chorley
managed to reach his goal of climbing f7a, whilst
Olly, Jake and Emyr managed to complete at least
one full circuit. Jake did manage to climb well over 100 problems and Emyr got back
into climbing with style. James ticked a number of hard problems over f7a but failed
to do the hardest problem of the trip, so decided to lock himself in a gym and train for
6 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miguel’s search for a one move f7a eliminate continues. The whole trip ran smoothly, without any real issues. The low number of people
meant that logistics were easier and that we could drive around crags. The main
negative of the trip was the lack of rest days. The team had 5 climbing days in a row,
which really took a toll on their skin and their psych. Next time it would be better to
go for a week extra and have more rest days. All in all Font delivered all that we
hoped it would, and the club will definitely be back in future years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="budget"&gt;Budget
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the initial budget was made for 15 people to take three
cars from the UK, the costs associated with being tested
both in France (€20 each) and in the UK (~£50 each) made
the trip more expensive per person than anticipated. This
was offset by the fact that only 8 people came as opposed to
the 15 budgeted for. Overall, the expenditure on travel was
£1665,13, which included getting a car and a van, as well as
the other members who couldn’t fit in these, to and from
Fontainebleau. The IC Trust gave us £670.50 of funding,
which was slightly less than the 40% of travel expenditure
we ended up having (£695.95). Overall, the trip could have
been much cheaper had we not had to spend so much on
testing and had we all gone to and from London together,
however space in the car was a major constraint. Added to this, George came from
Croatia and Ben from Rome, and Ben left a day early, adding to the expenses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="data-table" role="region" tabindex="0" &gt;
&lt;table class="table %!s(&lt;nil&gt;)" id="714623895"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Expenditure&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Campsite&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£488&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Food&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£253.33&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Ferries&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£380.73&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Tolls&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£91.27&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Fuel&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£449.15&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;COVID testing&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£520&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Busses&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£113.99&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Trains&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£183.99&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Total&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£2480.46&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 id="conclusion-and-future-plans"&gt;Conclusion and Future Plans
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour was a fun trip abroad for everyone, and we will definitely be back to Font in
future. All attendees not in their final year of study expressed interest in going on and
potentially running future tours, and the experience and competence of outdoor
boulderers in the club has been markedly improved. Miguel is still looking for a one
move f7a eliminate, if you know of one please contact him at:
&lt;a class="link" href="mailto:miguel@1movef7aeliminate.com" &gt;miguel@1movef7aeliminate.com&lt;/a&gt;. Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Summer tour 2014 - Verdon Gorge</title><link>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/4.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Summer tour 2014 - Verdon Gorge" /&gt;&lt;h3 id="member-attendees-17"&gt;Member Attendees: 17
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will Smith, Ben Coope, Harry Stuart- Smith, Yadu Bhageria, Mathew Lees, Milan Thakore, Will Macleod, Sam Cockman, Chris Brahms, Nathasha Saw, Catherine Spilsbury, Simeon Tsang, Anthony Fleming, James Weale, Jo Robbings, Amar Nanda, Kristjana Xhuxhi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="non-member-attendees-3"&gt;Non-Member Attendees: 3
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Georgia Drew, Laura Braun, Ed Poore&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="aims-and-objectives"&gt;Aims and Objectives
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The aim of the trip was to explore the Verdon area and give all those attending the opportunity to try the long, exposed and committing multipitch routes it had to offer. The trip achieved this aim; everybody was sad to leave! (Probably because of the two days in the minibus it would take to get home).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="financial-breakdown"&gt;Financial Breakdown
&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div class="data-table" role="region" tabindex="0" &gt;
&lt;table class="table %!s(&lt;nil&gt;)" id="765943218"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Income&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Member Income&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£4085.10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;ICU Funding&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£304.60&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Total&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£4389.7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="data-table" role="region" tabindex="0" &gt;
&lt;table class="table %!s(&lt;nil&gt;)" id="923576418"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Expenditure&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Minibus&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£1430&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Fuel&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£802.02&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Tolls&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£178.88&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Accomodation&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£948.09&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Food&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£985.56&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Guide books&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£45.25&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Total&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£4389.7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note that the above financial breakdown only applies to member attendees.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/0.jpg" width="400"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-1"&gt;Day 1
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everybody arrived on time in Beit Quad at 6 am ready to finish packing the busses and set off. Harry turned out to be a little worse for wear and had forgotten his passport. After a quick call to his dad it was agreed that the two busses and the car would rendezvous at the ferry terminal ready for the morning crossing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One bus arrived earlier, crossed on its own, both busses and the car all got lost independently and took different routes around Paris. We eventually ended up at Pres Camping south of Fountainbleu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-2"&gt;Day 2
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We got up early and had eggy bread, then headed over to boulder for the day. It was very hot and sunny, a slack line was set off and a few of us played boules while we enjoyed lunch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/1.jpg"
alt="The first of many games of danger boules." width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first of many games of danger boules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-3"&gt;Day 3
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/3.jpg"
alt="Harry." width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This day involved hundreds and hundreds of miles of driving. Luckily there were loads of drivers and we had lots of food. At one point Jo stopped wearing trousers and decided that the heated seats in the car were all a bit much. Late in the evening the red bus was hit by an oncoming van which destroyed the wing mirror, and the passenger side window. Thankfully nobody was hurt, though there was a lot of glass everywhere. A nearby irrigation system ensured that everybody in the windowless van stayed refreshed, which was great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We arrived in Palud Sur Verdon at around 11:30 pm and found the road leading up to the valley a bit exciting; the enormous drop to the right of the driver and sharp bends made sure that everybody was still awake. We arrived at the wrong campsite and put up the tents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-4"&gt;Day 4
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After waking up and realising that the campsite was wrong and rubbish, we de-camped and headed into town to try and find where we were meant to go. We immediately found Jean- Paul camping and headed over to pop the tents up. We then went to one of the shorter and supposedly more accessible crags in the area. After an hour of swearing and bashing through shrubs we arrived and got a decent afternoons climbing in, introducing the novices in the group to the techniques they’d need over the coming week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/4.jpg"
alt="Jo and James doing some of the very pleasant routes at the single pitch crag a little way down the valley." width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jo and James doing some of the very pleasant routes at the single pitch crag a little way down the valley.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-5"&gt;Day 5
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We headed over to a multi-pitch crag that didn’t involve any abseiling to give people some experience of the rope work before we committed to bigger routes. In the afternoon we headed down to the river for a swim!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-6"&gt;Day 6
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We knew that if we wanted to get anything big done while we were there we’d have to get used to the exposure presented by the enormous cliffs. To do this we spent the next day at one of the many abseil points at the edge of the road. Lots of tourists were taking our photos!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/5.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-7-8--9"&gt;Day 7, 8 &amp;amp; 9
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having taught people what they needed to know we split into three’s and took a series of groups to different multipitch crags over the next three days. The routes ranged from enormous crack and chimney climbs to interesting arête’s. Notably Ben and Amar tackled La Demande, one of the more famous routes in the area. Groups that didn’t do multipitch routes headed to abseil points along the roadside or along the valley to the extremely impressive Hulk area; a large scoop/ cave with some really interesting and challenging single pitch climbs. Handily it also stayed dry when the rest of the area was wet!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/6.jpg"
alt="Temperature inversion in the valley" width="400"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Temperature inversion in the valley&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/7.jpg"
alt="Georgia climbing above the river on a 9 pitch route." width="400"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Georgia climbing above the river on a 9 pitch route.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="images8.jpg"
alt="Milan and Sam on their first multipitch route, l’arete belvedere" width="400"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Milan and Sam on their first multipitch route, l’arete belvedere&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-10"&gt;Day 10
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a tiring few days we headed down to the river to wind down for a bit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/9.jpg" width="400"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/10.jpg" width="400"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-11"&gt;Day 11
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group went over to the Hulk area because of poor weather. The crag is in the middle of a series of ladders and narrow paths which allows for pretty big exposure in relative safety. On the opposite side of the valley a few people experienced the total darkness of the 1.5km long tunnel which runs along the river. Milan and Anthony got a bit stuck on their route so Ben and Amar shot up an adjacent route to help them out after their abseil line got stuck after they completed their route. Everybody got down in time for a late dinner though Milan and Anthony owed a lot of people a lot of drinks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2014-verdon-gorge/images/11.jpg"
alt="Milan climbing in Hulk" width="400"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Milan climbing in Hulk&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-12"&gt;Day 12
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the final day in Verdon the weather turned for the worse, those who hadn’t yet done it had a go at the via–ferrata which was about the only thing that was safe to do in the weather. The rest of the group had a relaxing day at the campsite and sorted the mountains of equipment out! The trip was rounded off with a meal at the local restaurant in Palud Sur Verdon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-13"&gt;Day 13
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We left Verdon and headed north making the campsite just south of Paris by 10 pm. Chilli was cooked hastily while a fire was built. Lunch and snack stops were spent at some of the many roadside picnicking areas that the cover much of the French road network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-14"&gt;Day 14
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a quick stop at the wine shop we caught the ferry home and remarked on how great cat-eyes were in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Summer Tour 2013</title><link>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/2.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Summer Tour 2013" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;By Will Macleod&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="objectives"&gt;Objectives
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For everyone to enjoy 2 weeks of sport climbing in the sun!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For members to improve their sport climbing ability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To experience and take advantage of a much better standard of sport climbing than
is available in the UK.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is no doubt that the tour fulfilled its objectives. Everyone had a great time, the quality
of sport climbing was excellent, and many people boosted their sport climbing grade by a
substantial amount; Sam and Milan boosted their grades from 6a+ to 6c and I went from
climbing 6c+ to 7b.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="attendees"&gt;Attendees
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will Macleod&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Andrew Wilkins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hamzah Shami&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Antje Lenhart&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jakov Marelic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cheehan Weereratne&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dak Scott&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Michael Chan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rosanna Nichols&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sam Cockman&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Milan Thakore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jack Beanland&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amar Nanda&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will Smith&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charlie Penny&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id="friday-september-6th"&gt;Friday, September 6th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first seven of us took our flight in today. Hamzah reinforced his position of club chopper
by trying to bring the most lethal looking ice screw I’ve ever seen onto the plane. The
security were nice enough not to arrest him, but he did lose his ice-screw-dagger. We
arrived in Reus at around 8pm and from there took a taxi straight to the campsite in Siurana.
We were immediately greeted by the campsite owners who were really friendly, and kept
the kitchen open late to get us all fed! After choosing our rooms in the campsite cabins and
moving all our stuff in, we went to bed setting an alarm for an early start tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/1.jpg"
alt="Choosing rooms" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choosing rooms&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="saturday-september-7th"&gt;Saturday, September 7th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A thunderstorm looming overhead
prevented people from doing much
climbing in the morning&amp;hellip; off to a good
start! Andy and I (Will) set off hitch-hiking
to the nearby town Cornudella, to buy food
supplies for the next few days. Other than
getting hopelessly lost and accidentally
hitch-hiking to a huge dam this was
successful. Meanwhile the rest of the
group spent the day slacklining and
meeting other climbers on the campsite.
Hannes – one guy we met – was kind
enough to drive some of us to a crag later
on in the day when it had dried out.
Cheehan, Dak and Rosanna arrived today!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/0.jpg"
alt="Hamzah showing off his slacklining skills" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hamzah showing off his slacklining skills&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="sunday-september-8th"&gt;Sunday, September 8th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are all up early to head to a nearby
crag – Can Marges - which has a range
of easy and hard routes for the day.
Everyone gets a good few climbs in. At
midday it gets really hot so we have a
break, and after another thunderstorm
at 5 we head back. This was our first
real go on Spanish rock as a group, and
everyone founds the climbs hard. This
rock will take some getting used to!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/2.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="monday-september-9th"&gt;Monday, September 9th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bulk of the group headed to Can Parasit to
climb in the morning. We were lucky to have
Hannes to drive some of us into town for food
shopping! Everyone regroups at the campsite at 4
and then heads back out to Can Parasit. Some of
us take fall practice to get confidence sport
climbing and some hard routes are attempted
until it gets dark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/3.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="tuesday-september-10th"&gt;Tuesday, September 10th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up super early. Scrambled eggs. The majority of people leave to Can Parasit again as it was
popular yesterday. Me Amar Michael and Hannes drive to Arboli, a beautiful crag just out of
walking distance. We climb a variety of routes ranging from 6a to 7b+. We had something
loosely resembling Piella for tea, took advantage of the unpolluted sky stargazing, then all
retreated to bed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/4.jpg"
alt="Hannes finding a no-hands rest on his 7b&amp;#43;" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hannes finding a no-hands rest on his 7b+&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/5.jpg"
alt="Me on a scarily run-out 6b&amp;#43;" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Me on a scarily run-out 6b+&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="wednesday-september-11th"&gt;Wednesday, September 11th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We spent the day at Grau del Masetes. There was a nice section of wall with a range of
easier routes that became the social hub of the crag. Lunch was Local baguettes with a
monstrous portion of nutella. Michael won chopper of the day award by trying to climb one
face of a chimney problem making it magnitudes harder, and benighting a small group of us
by getting a rope stuck at the top of a route!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/8.jpg"
alt="Hamzah spectating the 6b climb" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hamzah spectating the 6b climb&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/9.jpg"
alt="Amar attempting the 6b climb" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amar attempting the 6b climb&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="thursday-september-12th"&gt;Thursday, September 12th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We went to Grau del Masetes again. A portion of the
day was spent trying a 6a and 6a+ overhang at the
‘social hub’ of the crag. We also spent a long time all
trying a classic 6b nearby, with Michael taking photos
from a rope he had set up next to the route.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="friday-september-13th"&gt;Friday, September 13th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rest day today! Much slacklining was done! A number of people visited Siurana village
during the day. Charlie, Sam, Will Smith, Milan and Jack arrived later today. Amar had to go
back, and the campsite owners were kind enough to offer to drive him all the way to Reus
themselves! (A two hour round trip)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/10.jpg"
alt="Hamzah displaying some actual skill on a slackline" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hamzah displaying some actual skill on a slackline&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="saturday-september-14th"&gt;Saturday, September 14th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a morning excursion through a small jungle to a crag we wrongly thought would be big
enough for all of us, we headed to Can Melafots. This is the famous crag at Siurana, and with
good reason! It consists of a long stretch of amazing overhanging red rock, overlooking a
beautiful view of the lake nearby. It was obvious this crag would be visited many more times
this trip!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/12.jpg"
alt="Jack on ‘pizza de pinya’ 7a" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jack on ‘pizza de pinya’ 7a&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="sunday-september-15th"&gt;Sunday, September 15th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Due to a number of complaints about it being too hot, some people went to a shaded crag,
Reserva India. The rest of the group headed to Can Melafots again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/14.jpg"
alt="Jakov and Cheehan enjoying the Spanish rock" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jakov and Cheehan enjoying the Spanish rock&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/13.jpg"
alt="Will at Can Melafots" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will at Can Melafots&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="monday-september-16th"&gt;Monday, September 16th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We spent the day at Grau del Masetes, to show the new-comers the crag. A number of
people had a go at a short 7a+ with a really hard boulder move at the top. Only Jack got it!
Since everyone feels pretty spent we decided upon a rest day tomorrow. This is great news
because it allows us to indulge in all the Spanish wine we can get our hands on with no fear
of climbing hung-over!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/15.jpg"
alt="Will and Sam looking fabulous" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will and Sam looking fabulous&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/16.jpg"
alt="Will at Can Melafots" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will at Can Melafots&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="tuesday-september-17th"&gt;Tuesday, September 17th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally a full rest-day! Everyone had a big lie-in and then we trekked down to the lake for
some swimming. A herd of goats pestered us when we were all sitting by the lake. From the
lake we headed to Town to buy food and have a few drinks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/17.jpg"
alt="Will failing to swim" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will failing to swim&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/18.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="wednesday-september-18th"&gt;Wednesday September 18th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Me, Antje, Will Smith, Charlie, Milan, Jack and Jakov left early to go to the crag El Detot. The
rest were chilling out or climbing at Can Melafots. Michael got his 7c project, and I got a 7a I
had been trying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/19.jpg"
alt="Milan at El Detot" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Milan at El Detot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/20.jpg"
alt="Will at El Detot" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will at El Detot&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="thursday-september-19th"&gt;Thursday September 19th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today is the last day of real climbing! Everyone with projects they want to do has to get the
today! Me and Michael had a 7b and 7c+ project at Can Melafots to finish. I got the 7b and
was given a gummy-bear as a reward. We all drank a lot with dinner and for some reason
had a food-fight with spaghetti&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/21.jpg"
alt="Will on Hostia 7b" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Will on Hostia 7b&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/22.jpg"
alt="A nice view of us on Melafots" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A nice view of us on Melafots&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="friday-september-20th"&gt;Friday September 20th
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We got the campsite owners to order us a taxi for 3:30. The morning was spent packing and
clearing up the huts, primarily removing spaghetti from the walls. We had quite a large
amount of euros left over so thought we would splash out on a nice meal for lunch! We
went to a pizzeria in Siurana Village with Hannes before saying bye and heading off!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/23.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2013/images/finances.png" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;</description></item><item><title>Summer Tour 2011</title><link>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/0.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Summer Tour 2011" /&gt;&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;10 members of Imperial College Mountaineering Club travelled to the sunny
island of Mallorca from the 12th to the 25th September. Not for the cheap thrills of
Shagaluf but for the vast amounts of climbing on offer. While on tour many
different areas were visited with all sorts of climbing on offer from caves to slabs.
Some members achieved very highly whereas others had a less fortunate time.
The aims and objectives of the tour were for members to climb in a different
environment to those that they are used to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Mallorca the climbing was all sport
or deep water soloing which are less common in the UK. There were also some
longer multi pitch routs that members enjoyed climbing. Due to unforeseen
circumstances 2 members had to use their recently acquired advanced first aid
skills to help one team member out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall Mallorca was an excellent location to visit. There was a wide range of
grades from very easy to very hard. A lot of the very interesting routs were
harder than many members could climb. Despite being a relatively small island
there was a significant amount of driving. We managed to take advantage of
cheap villas due to the off peak season and found some cheap car rental places,
food was also remarkably low cost. We all learnt the hard way that accidents can
happen, even when not doing a particularly difficult climb and we must always
be aware of hazards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/5.jpg"
alt="Top Row: Ruth, Jon, Ali, Lisa, Ollie, Elliot, Murray. Bottom Row: Tristan, Abi, Fails" width="300"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Top Row: Ruth, Jon, Ali, Lisa, Ollie, Elliot, Murray. Bottom Row: Tristan, Abi, Fails&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="people"&gt;People
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The people going on the tour were:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Matthew Lees (Murray) - President&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mike Jones (Fails) – Vice President&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jonathan Price&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alastair Brash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lisa Alhadeff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elliot Carrington&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tristan Pollitt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruth Lawson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Abi Attrell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oliver Mower&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="diary"&gt;Diary
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="day-1--flight"&gt;Day 1 – Flight
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;With 10 members flying from all over the country to Palma it was quite
remarkable that all but one person had met in the country just after noon. The
one member who had decided to take a later flight for a sweet deal wouldn’t
arrive until much later that night and cause much unnecessary driving, the fuel
for which probably cancelled out his own saving. Picking up the cars turned out
to be not as simple as expected, the rental firm was too cheap to buy a place in
the airport and needed a bus to get there. The cars however were very cheap
and were already scratched and dented, as a bonus hey came with free
insurance meaning we wouldn’t get fined for bumping the car.
Driving out of Palma proved to be difficult but after a scenic drive around the city
the motorway was found and the other side of the island quickly reached.
Arriving at the accommodation Ali was convinced that the lead diver Murray was
completely lost but was surprised when it turned out that they had arrived at
their accommodation. The villa was perfect for the club needs and was very
cheap. Classic ICMC Chilli was had for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/0.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-2--el-fumat"&gt;Day 2 – El Fumat
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first crag to be visited on the trip was
thought to be a local crag called El Fumat,
but turned out to be the other side of a
mountain so there was some slow uphill
diving. The crag had excellent views and
was well bolted. Most members found the
grades to be hard; this was probably due
to the new location and tiredness. On the
menu for dinner was Curry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-3--les-perxes"&gt;Day 3 – Les Perxes
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The area chosen today had a couple of
different crags. Most of the group went to
the easier section near the car park called
Hairpin but Ali and Lisa decided to go for
the cave nearby. The easy crag got sun
around 2 and became too hot for climbing,
the cave being north facing remained cool
all day. Some members decided to go
watch the cave climbing and take photos but others went to the higher crag that
had a little bit more shade.
Ali managed to climb an impressive climb up with some good tufa action and a
nice rest in the middle. One of the local climbers then crushed it while warming
up for a much harder climb. Carbonara was on the table tonight, there was much
debate over what the ingredients should be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/1.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-4--deep-water-solo"&gt;Day 4 – Deep Water Solo
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Being the tour’s first venture into DWS an easy small crag was chosen. There
were 3 routs on the smallest section; the 6a was enjoyable and easy and done by
most. The water was very clear and we could easily see that the bottom was
a long way down There was a good 7a with a cool dino in the middle which
many people fell off. Some members quickly decided they didn’t like DWS
and others needed to work on jumping off to get over a fear of height. Some
members had no problem jumping off the cliffs but had some minor issues
entering the water.
At the top of the cliff there was a mast, probably used for sailing the island
to new locations, where we left all of our food and bags. Ali, Ruth and Lisa
managed to hit their heads on the mast; unfortunately since they were not
climbing at this point in time they didn’t have helmets on, all 3 felt very silly.
A DWS dinghy was bought to help get people to the bottom of the climbs
and to rescue them in case something went wrong. Various names were put
forward, there were: Lizzie Wilkins, Fun Splash, Enema, Ella and Emma. After
some debate the name Ella stuck, it was later revealed that this was also the
name of Jacob Dean’s 12 year old sister, after this the innuendos came thick and
fast. Fajitas were for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/2.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-5--rest-day-1"&gt;Day 5 – Rest day 1
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people slept in late this day after some early starts on the previous days.
Everyone except Ali went for a walk along the coast but Ali remained behind to
do a literature review. While walking a large number of naked people were seen,
this was highly disturbing. An old abandoned pill box was found and explored, it
was very hot inside. Finding a small cover everyone sat down and had a lovely
time playing in the water. Murray kicked a rock while swimming and bled all over
the place. Fails annoyed a sea anemone by destroying its home and it got its own
back by stinging Fails, Elliot and Ruth. Since it was Elliot’s last night with us we
had another Chilli to remind him of all the good times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-6--sa-gubia-eastern-side"&gt;Day 6 – Sa Gubia, eastern side
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another early start to get to the crag before the sun hit it. The massive walls of
Sa Gubia were on the table for today. Ali and Lisa decided to have a day alone
and headed over to the steep hard world of Fraguel. After quite a long walk in up
a dry river bed the bottom of the wall was reached where we met 2 local
climbers who gave us a lot of tips about which crags not to visit as they had bad
bolts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 2 best climbs of the day were
a delicate 6a and an outrageous
6a+ which had some cool tufa
action on it. Ali and Lisa also had a
good day out. The group split in 2
with half heading back to make a
curry for dinner and the others
taking Elliot to the airport for him
to head home early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-7--dws--more-sa-gubia"&gt;Day 7 – DWS &amp;amp; more Sa Gubia
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Murray, Jon, fails, Abi and Ollie
headed over to Cala Sa Nau to try
out a different area. There were a
number of easy climbs, fails
managed a 6b but failed on the
7a. Murray tried the 7a from day 4
but ripped the tip of his finer off
on the sloping crimp. Abi jumped
off the top and made a big splash.
Ella was launched; she was a
much finer vessel than the other group who were at the crag.
The climbers at Sa Gubia tried a number of different things. Tristan and Ruth had
a mini adventure on their 2 pitch multi pitch. Ali and Lisa tried a few hard things
with little success. Since it was a Sunday most shops were closed so there was
not a lot of food to be had. Heavy rain made the road outside the apartments
turn into a small river. Since it was Lisa’s last day she decided to get drunk
instead of packing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-8--rest-day-2"&gt;Day 8 – Rest Day 2
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ali got up early to take Lisa to the airport, everyone else stayed in bed for quite a
while. While Ali was sleeping most other people went for a large food shop taking
advantage of Lidl’s cheap prices. After the shop everyone moved to the beach to
enjoy the Mallorca sun. The slack line was put up and everyone had a good go
with various levels of susses, this attracted many tourists who took&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;photos, if a hat had been left out we probably would have made some money.
Towards the end of the day we moved the slack line to two trees that were much
further apart, right at the limit of how far the slack line could reach. While
tensioning the line we melted a section as there was so much force! This line was
very long and wobbled a lot. Murray and Tristan both got about half way on it but
nobody made it the whole length. Some people were scared off by the height of
the line but the soft sand gave a good landing and when it sagged in the middle
it was quite close to the floor anyway. While slack lining Fails failed and landed
with one leg either side of the line and had to sit down for a while, see right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/3.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2011/images/4.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-9--the-accident"&gt;Day 9 – The Accident
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ali and Fails headed off to a hard over hanging crag with short boulder like routs.
Everyone else went to Puig St Martin where there was shade all day and easy
climbs. A number of different routes were done. While trying a 5+ with a high first bolt Ollie slipped and hit the ground. He had broken his ankle and mountain
rescue were called to evacuate him. Jon and Murray had both been on the union
run outdoor first aid course which proved very useful. Both tried to check for
broken bones but didn’t feel anything that felt broken, both were carrying first
aid kits but there was little they could do. Four firemen arrived with a stretcher to
carry him out, they were not particularly gentle. Everyone went to visit Ollie that
evening, he was on pain killers at this point and seemed quite merry, fortunately
he had BMC insurance and everything was OK.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-10--dws"&gt;Day 10 – DWS
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abi decided that she wanted to stay with Ollie for the day and keep him company
as being in a foreign hospital. Everyone else decided to go deep water soloing as
there would be nothing to hit and get hurt on. Ali and Fails went to Cala Barques
and everyone else went to Santanyi. Ali and Fails found their perfect climbs of
steep jug climbing with big powerful moves. The others enjoyed their day and
went to visit the legendary Es Pontas and were surprised by how shallow the
water was there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-11--les-perxes-mark-ii"&gt;Day 11 – Les Perxes Mark II
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;A permanent problem with Mallorca was trying to find shady crags where the
heat was not too severe. Port Soller had a large amount of shade but we
discovered building works and so couldn’t climb there. Returning to a previously
visit crag is generally avoided on tour but this area has several sections. Ali and
Fails went to the cave and tried more hard things. Everyone else went to the
upper section called Muro de Caimari. There were several hard climbs done by
all. Ruth and Tristan found an extremely pumpy 6b which was very hard. Ollie
was visited in the evening and this time had a large amount of metal in his leg
after the operation and was in for a bad night sleep. After climbing we took Fails
to the airport as he had found a sweet deal and booked an earlier flight home&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-12--betlem"&gt;Day 12 – Betlem
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Waking to the sound of heavy rain was not a good start to the day. Almost all the
climbing locations would be soaked and the only things able to be climbed would
be caves. Contrary to the malicious propaganda spread by the Outdoor Club we
did not go to a pub, we went climbing instead. A crag called El Calo de Betlem
was decided upon as it had some shelter and easy cave climbs. Arriving at the
crag to find that rock fax lied and only a part of the routes were dry we soldiered
on. Most people tried a cool looking 6b which had some hard moves in it to a
hidden and now sodden slot. While Abi was on top rope an assisted dyno was
attempted with no result. Another nearby area was investigated but the best
routs were slabs that were still wet and there were serious signs of seepage.
Murray and Ruth checked out an abandoned house which had an aloe vera plant
in front that was about 3m tall and you could stand on its branches/leaves.
Setting up a water line over the pool was discussed at length. We found 2 points
that we felt would be suitable anchors and active spotting near the edges of the
pool was also proposed. Unfortunately it was felt that the 2 anchors were too far apart and a water line was not put up. Instead a raft was built from the many
empty water bottles with an impressively poor result.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="day-13--home-time"&gt;Day 13 – Home Time
&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ali and Abi went back to Les Perxes for Ali to try and finish his route. The top slab
was wet and no route finishing happened. Packing the cars with all of our stuff
took a while and lead to a rather uncomfortable trip to the airport. Both cars had
to be returned empty and so the economy race was on. Murrays diesel had only
had 1 ½ tanks of fuel so was already low but made it to the rental drop of shortly
after the fuel light came on. Ali was forced to put in an extra 5 euros of fuel. At
the airport there was a slight challenge convincing the staff that Ollie couldn’t
walk and that he needed a wheel chair. After a large amount of repacking to get
everyone under the weight limit we all ate and drank as much as we could to get
as heavy as possible to reduce the fuel economy of the plane to restore Ryanair’s
karma. Arriving late at Stansted we were all greeted by an enormous line for
border control with some grumpy staff who were extremely unhelpful. We retried
our bags and then all went our separate ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="finances"&gt;Finances
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 id="cost-breakdown"&gt;Cost Breakdown
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="data-table" role="region" tabindex="0" &gt;
&lt;table class="table %!s(&lt;nil&gt;)" id="987463251"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Income&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Member Income&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£1800&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;ICU Funding&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£410&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="data-table" role="region" tabindex="0" &gt;
&lt;table class="table %!s(&lt;nil&gt;)" id="325681794"&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style="text-align: center"&gt;Expenditure&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Value&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Consumable&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£400&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Accomodation&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£1240&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Car hire&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£370&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style="text-align: center"&gt;Fuel&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;£200&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description></item><item><title>Summer tour 2010</title><link>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/cover.png" alt="Featured image of post Summer tour 2010" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Written by James Lawson (Webmaster) &amp;amp; Alistair Brash (President)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-1-15th-september"&gt;Day 1 (15th September):
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flew out to Kos from Gatwick after a 3am start, Lizzie is woken up by a phonecall 10 mins before the
Easybus leaves but somehow makes it in time. From Kos we take taxis to the port, a ferry to
Kalymnos and then a bus to Massouri. Eventually we arrive late on in the afternoon at Babis bar in
Massouri on Kalymnos, our accommodation for the trip. As it was getting dark when we arrived at
the bar we decided to go for a swim in the pool and eat rather than attempting to climb.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-2"&gt;Day 2:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We fafffed with gear/breakfast till 10:15 then headed out to the Poets sector, the closest to Babis
bar. Kip managed to forget his shoes and attempted to Alistair’s size “too small” downturned
bouldering shoes to much hilarity. Kip flashed his first 6a (after going back for shoes) and Ruth did
her first sport lead (5a). Dac lead a 5a that she found “nice” called Pindaros. The bolts on “Sevasti”
(7b) were found to be in silly places which was a shame as the bottom of the route involved
wrestling with an incredible tufa feature. Climbing halted at mid afternoon due to climbing not been
possible in the sun, we decided to wake up early the next day to climb for a greater amount of the
day. At dinner that night Lizzie claimed that she could taste the fennel (despite the herbs not been
fennel) and the phrase “getting involved with” was deemed acceptable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-3"&gt;Day 3:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up at 5:30AM! (It was still dark) to beat the daystar at its own game. Breakfast of two eggs and
bread is already getting slightly sickening. Kip took a big fall while clipping on a 6b+ and decided to
sac the rest of the day off. Cheehan found a mobile phone charger and learnt how to belay. Johan
found that the phrase “just bisioning around” annoyed Alistair. Ruth tried a 5b but weighted the
rope due to deficiencies in route finding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-4"&gt;Day 4:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lisa Beats Kip’s tour fall distance record by falling from the last move of the 40m route Trella (7a).
Johan managed to climb 9 routes in a day with Dak and kip managing 8 as part of a group of 3.
Alistair flashes Trella for his first 7a flash (climbed without falls on first attempt). We had lentils for
tea, they were tasty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-5"&gt;Day 5:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Babi took the cool kids to a crag that had all day climbing due to the presence of a north face.
Meanwhile red point club (Lisa, Alistair, Cheehan) had a rest day. Johan and Johnny both flashed 6c.
Kip learnt how to tie in with a bowline knot which is quicker to undo than a figure 8. Dak tried a 6c
for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-6"&gt;Day 6:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rest day for everyone who wasn’t in red point club. Red point club went and red pointed some
more. Everyone else went and hired scooters and became a crazy motorbike gang for the day which
involved going to the supermarket for cheap food and 1.93euro/1.5L wine and riding the mountain
road to Vathy and Pothia. This was the best day of Fresher’s life. Cheehan flashes 7b+ despite
having never lead outside before the trip! And Lisa almost redpoints 7a+. Kip doesn’t hold up well
on the paint stripper wine (methanol content?!) and falls asleep early.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-7"&gt;Day 7:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fresher and Kip embarked on the first multipitch of the tour at the ‘School’ sector of Kalymnos.
‘Platon’ a five pitch route: 4c, 5a, 5b, 5c, 4b. This was Kip’s first multipitch climb but as the first two
pitches were easy it was decided to simul-climb (leader and second moving together) them for
speed. This was extremely fun and the first two and a half pitches were dispatched in between 5
and 10 minutes, thus showing the speed advantage this style of climbing has. As the climbing
became harder and more technical towards the end of the 5b pitch they switched to belayed
climbing for the end of this pitch and the following pitch with Fresher leading. The final pitch was
lead by Kip with big run outs (big fall potential due to spaced protection) presumably because the
first ascensionist had run out of bolts. The view from the top of the ridge line the climb went up was
pretty spectacular, unfortunately for weight saving we brought no camera. The whole climb took a
surprisingly brief period of time; been dispatched including abseil decent before 1:30pm!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alistair dispatched the route Zorba Le Gros on his 2nd attempt for his first route at the 7b grade. Lisa
falls right from the end of Polipitis (7a+), plans to come back later in the trip to finish it off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-8"&gt;Day 8:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;More climbing at Poets for most people, Alistair, Cheehan, Jonny &amp;amp; Lizzie head to the impressive
cave of Spartacus where amazing routes and shade until 6pm are found. Cheehan starts work on
Daniboy which at the grade of 8a is harder than any IC student in recent memory has climbed.
Alistair picks the classic line of Spartacus, both routes require painfully jamming your knee in to get a
hands-off rest, plans are made for one of Babis’ hand-towels to become a crucial knee-pad. Jonny
tries Magnetus, a very short and powerful route at the 7c grade. Lizzie starts attempting climbs at
the 6c grade. All four are enthusiastic to return another day to complete their projects. Chris &amp;amp; Lisa
head back to Polipitis, get close but again not quite close enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-9"&gt;Day 9:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone takes a rest day, Fresher sets off determined to hire a boat. Turns out nobody on Kalymnos
is stupid enough to hire Fresher a boat. Much larking around in the swimming pool happens and not
a lot else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-10"&gt;Day 10:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Psyched after successfully imitating turbo Germans; Fresher and Kip embarked on their second
multipitch climb of the tour. This time on the small island of Telendos (or Telly’d as it became
known) with the objective of climbing a 6b+ overhanging “offwidth” (off width cracks are named as
such because they don’t easily fit human body parts and so lead to a particularly physical form of
climbing).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Figure 7 - Telendos as seen from Kalymnos&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The day started at noon with catching the ferry to Telendos due to the climb being north-easterly
facing. Upon leaving the town on Telendos a dog started to follow us. This dog obviously used to
climbers going to the closer crags giving it food proceeded to follow us over very broken terrain for
over an hour and a half to our climb despite our best efforts to turn it back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kip lead the first 6a+ pitch of crimpy Telendos limestone which had a nice unprotected bushy muddy
sloping ledge at the top. Fresher, been the expert in all things disgusting then attempted the 6b+
“offwidth” pitch which turned out to be more of a fist/hand jamming crack. The inside of the crack was made of fossilised shells that hurt a lot. After about 4hrs of pain the “offwidth” pitch was
dispatched. The delay was primarily due to it been impossible to second with a backpack and having
to prussic up a fixed line instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Figure 8 - The notorious offwidth&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Resting at the top of the 2nd pitch the decision was made to abseil off the climb due to the
encroaching darkness and the “meat” of the climb having been dispatched. In the twilight at the
bottom we found the dog now very dehydrated and so we shared some of our water with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What followed was 3hrs of stumbling through the dark trying to find our way back to the town but
always finding ourselves above a cliff line with an increasingly distressed dog while getting very
dehydrated. Eventually unable to find a way down from the cliff line we abseiled off a sturdy bush
to a low angled scree slope which lead to the shore line path to town. Unfortunately the attempts
to save the dog by making a sling harness for it such that we could take it on the abseil were
unsuccessful (kept wriggling out). So we feared as the dog was scrabbling around in a dangerous
position (top of a loose cliff) it would die. However just as we had given the dog up as lost it came
bounding down the slope towards us, obviously it knew the decent and hadn’t told us. We brought
the dog back to its owner and endeavoured to explain just how lucky a dog it was.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While this madness went down Johan managed 11 routes in a day on Castalia (good when each day
only has 6hrs of climbing time).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back in the realm of the sane, Alistair successfully redpointed Spartacus for his first 7b+ route, the
hand-towel taped to the knee making all the difference. Cheehan fell from near the end of Daniboy
and Jonny was shot down by Magnetus but managed to climb a neighbouring 7b. Chris and Lisa both
managed to redpoint Polipitis for their first 7a+ routes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-12"&gt;Day 12:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were sufficient funds for all of us to have all you can eat BBQ, as a vegetarian Kip decided to
spend his money on a BIG pizza instead. Certain members hit the all you can drink wine pretty hard
and after a moonlit trip to the beach, are unable to find their own beds so instead settle for sharing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-13"&gt;Day 13:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cheehan successfully redpointed Daniboy (8a), Johnny and Johan followed suit with Magnetus (7c)
and a 7b getting redpointed respectively. All very good achievements!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-14"&gt;Day 14:
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of us decided to have a rest day and went to Telendos where we hired sea kayaks and went to a
small uninhabited island with a church on (about 2km away). We then had a tasty cheap lunch at a
restaurant on Telendos. For afternoon entertainment most of us swam the 1km from Telendos to
Kalymnos, for many of us our first open water swim. Fresher paddled the dinghy from the swimming
pool at Babis Bar using a slippery when wet sign, a true act of heroism that required reinflation at
the half-way mark. Celebratory ice-cream and beer were consumed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-15-september-29th"&gt;Day 15 (September 29th):
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Return to London via two buses, a ferry and Easyjet. Minor drama with luggage not showing up in
time for Easybus, however Easybus was late so all is well. London is grey, rainy and miserable and
generally inferior to Kalymnos in every respect. Still, Kalymnos has left a big impression upon all of us
and we cannot wait to return in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="full-list-of-attendees"&gt;Full List of Attendees:
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alistair Brash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ruth Lawson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;James Lawson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lisa Alhadeff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Johan Gausden&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dakshina Scott&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jonathan Hazell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Matt Pusey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ed Stott&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lizzie Wilkins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sarah Woodrow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chris Hunt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cheehan Weereratne&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elliot Carrington&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jonathan Bull&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of the above are full-time IC students and members of ICMC. The tour budget projected 15
attendees with 14 being IC students, however the alumni member dropped out, the result was that
15 IC students attended the tour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="financial-breakdown"&gt;Financial Breakdown:
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CSB awarded this tour £463.00 of subsidy which will be split equally between all attendees to
cover travel expenditure when received. The tour broke even. There was not a fixed ticket price as
not everyone came for the duration of the tour, however individual prices were calculated based on
the cost of food + accommodation for the number of nights the attendees were present. The cost of
the tour for a single attendee for the full two weeks once subsidy is received was £400.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="difficulties--objectives"&gt;Difficulties / Objectives:
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tour originally intended to run to Sardinia, however owing to a lack of eligible hire car drivers,
the destination was changed to Kalymnos as it was possible to walk to the climbing from our
accommodation. Changing the destination actually presented very few problems and the new
destination was able to fulfil all of the tour objectives. The cost of the flights increased however this
was offset by the money saved from not needing to hire cars. This also meant that our subsidy
allocation was still valid, the change in destination was cleared with the DPCS well before departure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many new skills were learnt from simul-climbing to new tie-in knots and even just better mental &amp;amp;
physical tactics for attempting a hard route. Not a single member came away from the trip without
increasing the level at which they climbed. Several members lead climbed outdoors for the first
time, this is a major milestone in anyone’s personal climbing development. The well-protected and
enjoyable routes played a major role in this&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;script src="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/jquery-3.7.0.min.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/lazy/jquery.lazy.min.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;script src="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/swipebox/js/jquery.swipebox.min.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;link rel="stylesheet" href="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/swipebox/css/swipebox.min.css"&gt;
&lt;script src="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/justified_gallery/jquery.justifiedGallery.min.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
&lt;link rel="stylesheet" href="YAYAYA/shortcode-gallery/justified_gallery/justifiedGallery.min.css"/&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;div id="gallery-3b1b40e27d9adb7835f474760f60f4fd-0-wrapper" class="gallery-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;div id="gallery-3b1b40e27d9adb7835f474760f60f4fd-0" class="justified-gallery"&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-010.png"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="450"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABgAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AOguPH2vXD4stLjjQ93VmI/UCswar4q1Ay&amp;#43;XdNCC&amp;#43;WAUAZwM4OM4&amp;#43;nfNZkviM6fdiKWKaDfCWdmwoGOhB&amp;#43;oxUsOrSpp3mSwMSWzI6kEkNnBJ79c1m5NGsYJk8&amp;#43;mX9zZbb2aWaZ25eWRiEHtk1i3ejWsZKvfgnI2qE5wfUZ9xV&amp;#43;TxZLLMLWSJY0ysbFUy3J4PXJAxz3rG1zS7yK&amp;#43;KRM9yxY8oOvrxj9al3E1YueLrV7a6hW5IlhmiJAGQpIz&amp;#43;vT86xrW/eWaW0kuStqJUJ7kIrfQnoK6T4h/c0z6yfyFcTZf8fVz/ALlXboJOyuej3/gy2m1QzFrgbbdTEI4vlYgnvj5j0461j6tHJYKdLgu3GyNZpFuV/eNwejcdAenvXpz/AHNO&amp;#43;n9BXm3jT/kcLn/r2P8AMVFRs0oxTZ//2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-010_hu_b9b9f49d1eb1f35d.png"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-009.png"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="336"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABIAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AO5uPGbNlYLRR7yPn&amp;#43;VU5PFl6QCqWw9sH/GuenitUDKOM9zjP8qz59Y06zQEXtu8ynHlbhn05C81D9pHcpKEuh1Mni6/YEqIY1/vhf5ZrNk8Y3uS8l5yOpwMfgKwvOia3Uec5LAEZfkfh/iKrKY49ynLhm3Hfz/nrTtPqxe4tkalyqhmIUDLHtWVdKN/QdfSta66t/vGsq6&amp;#43;/wDj/jXWtznIh99vpUX8Z&amp;#43;tSj77fSof4z9aUho//2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-009_hu_c1ebddf8deceeaee.png"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-008.png"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="419"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABYAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AJ0di4VuMcge9DSxWy&amp;#43;bcOPLJ&amp;#43;QE4wc9OvrTNTZYbXAO5yQ2ce5/wrDub6UW7Fskkjy8EA7u1ccN7HXLa5sG9JztUk/xZ6j1HFT24aSUyMxeKT7y7ugPf8P6VmaPK8qLK8ZBUYYMvT/GrjyS2kvmBQ0Lf3f1xT&amp;#43;Fi3RB4gcxPDAOvl7ifr/&amp;#43;o/nWbaBZZVjdA2W289j61oeJv&amp;#43;P&amp;#43;L/riv8zWfYf8fif9daJLUcdidJZrdJBGwUZ2kqcH8D&amp;#43;FaUUzT/u7gl1YBlYYBGRWbJ9yT/rof61et/vR/wDXNKExNH//2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-008_hu_38370cfb8753b709.png"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-007.png"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="450" height="600"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAGAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AO3vfE9xK5WD9wmM5GCce5rm7zWpBqMRlupWEjYU7jnOPrVCTUJ5FG6M7ccbefzzUEdq0t0k0hCxpy47k9sflRzAojtQE0dyfKV8OGw/GFNUMal/z9P/AN9CtS5gRszuchM4yBlfz5zVX7RD/wA9ZfzqVCLE2yd3k2NKm1xnhV/wpIhKJmmMhYHkIRnHHHP1qSSOFI2eXgE5wD8wHP6VRnlZpdsULSL7fzNAXJ7uJ5QpeR2Uj5lZcjv269zVT7Hbf884v&amp;#43;/BqWOCS4uleVjHx8oQ/wA6vf2ef&amp;#43;e8n5j/AApJ2Kep/9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-007_hu_ccb17609b34302f1.png"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-006.png"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="450"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABgAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/ALi2nbFSCz9qjj1e3boGP4VL/a8AU4RyR2xXouqlucCpth9jHUio3swwwRSpqBlcvyuOx6U97&amp;#43;NV3ONtTHEJuxbotI5aGwvZcFCmCeMt1pj2mpKCTaSnAydozjjNbOn/AOqj&amp;#43;tay/wDLx9B/6Ca4I4ubdmdcsNFao4Pz5QW&amp;#43;V&amp;#43;OvHSkN6QOtTv1u/p/Wsp&amp;#43;hrvg7nHI//9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-006_hu_24986783c3352073.png"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-005.png"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="360"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABMAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AJIodtzvVvm27gCMgHI9PrSfa7eIyXt64hQsEVc8ufT6dKjsJmW1YSje8JI3gdRnOPz/AJVj6xuv4Fg4LJkh8bflJ&amp;#43;7x1/GuBJc2p2Nu2h1luxIN6gy5jO3avy1nTQzGOQBdyhMgg/545FS6W9w2j23m4BVCAcAYAJ64qz5aASlm2qq7ty8EE/8A16bVmLUoWKhRKBnk88/j/WqWxfPI2jgp2&amp;#43;tXrL/lp9RVP/l4b6p/WpZaNeMB7eQHoiAj26VVnuJonjjSQhXbkfTdVuH/AI95/wDrmv8ASs&amp;#43;7/wBfD/vH&amp;#43;TVRPU//2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-005_hu_c85ab5a3c0d777f9.png"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-004.png"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="429" height="443"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIACAAHwMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/APMIwxvohcZZFIwp9K9JsfAmp3cC3E6QWm4ZVZn&amp;#43;YL1yQBxXD&amp;#43;HZ44vFOmT3cZljS4RnAXcTz198V7leWTzrDJdG1lhUN50rny2K87QMA8AMe4yfxrWNeUNiHBM8w13R7vQIw9zFvjc4SaP5kJ69a5W41aTaF2FQeQRxmvXPExisfBd0L&amp;#43;5jl3QGKFIgEjLEgphf7wPp2rya8trA2iSm52vgYQg8/wCf6U/a1at9dPuJ5Yx6HWabfHVtRs7SLS1i&amp;#43;wnzJJohnOFIXA25AJx3pi634rhxbXU1yZi6kRNEozHg7scdenvT/Bdw8d7qITyxM0arGrtyzDcRj255qjr&amp;#43;ua3v8i6EH2qJsqYv4QeoyD/nFYrVWKejM3X5L6&amp;#43;1eSN5pJYYm&amp;#43;RXckLwOmayJrG7uNm1PlUYUf4VuTPLNexTqhaSSJC2FJGeM5/Kunk0bTbqNGuLZYpCoLNE&amp;#43;w5/l&amp;#43;lTpF2HdvU//9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-004_hu_8eb4c6ab7a6c4915.png"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-003.png"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="450"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABgAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AG5y24KzbT82PSpxcNtjNr5c4aQIVDYI6nv9KQAK&amp;#43;V6sMc96qR2RlvJImYxpKpGBn5mAJA457cVLTLjZmlcZSRo2xuGeGXBH09arXUbS2xQn5CPlOfunsamtLuO60&amp;#43;OK4Qx3EQwVccH6Hv8AzoSbblcg8dOoNNCasxsLhRhs4PzetE8AlhIiPluDlXC8oe1M/hX/AHasp/F9KuxmVBgwGCchyB16E0tqII4EWJQNgwV6ZA7Z9abJ/r/wqKD7w/36T2Gtz//Z"
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-003_hu_dbf183a75cf787db.png"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-002.png"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="450"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABgAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/ALTnz7qNf4FbkVV1m5VJCWyUiUlFH8T9quxhIrYvtyxB6&amp;#43;lc1cXX2q&amp;#43;kiC5EWMsT39KysapnTwkPpck7uGlmG3IHC59PzP61EI/OaC4ErAQbkRB2JJH8hT4h5OkxjqY1OB6ux/8A1/pSQQOjQjcNiKQFHc54/SqlsKO5U1O6aOLYgyegyefaqlrocNvPFeJKwk3rtU87z3JqTVv9dF/vL/M1eT7ll&amp;#43;H86rqT0JpcSX6W6HCQp/48eef0qeJlJJIIwTj3qun/ACGbj/eX/wBBWpU6D/eP8jSlsOO5/9k="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-002_hu_767be06613a47354.png"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;a href="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-000.png"
class="galleryImg"
&gt;
&lt;img
width="600" height="450"
style="filter: blur(25px);"
src="data:image/jpeg;base64,/9j/2wCEAAoHBwgHBgoICAgLCgoLDhgQDg0NDh0VFhEYIx8lJCIfIiEmKzcvJik0KSEiMEExNDk7Pj4&amp;#43;JS5ESUM8SDc9PjsBCgsLDg0OHBAQHDsoIig7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7Ozs7O//AABEIABgAIAMBIgACEQEDEQH/xAGiAAABBQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAAAAQIDBAUGBwgJCgsQAAIBAwMCBAMFBQQEAAABfQECAwAEEQUSITFBBhNRYQcicRQygZGhCCNCscEVUtHwJDNicoIJChYXGBkaJSYnKCkqNDU2Nzg5OkNERUZHSElKU1RVVldYWVpjZGVmZ2hpanN0dXZ3eHl6g4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2drh4uPk5ebn6Onq8fLz9PX29/j5&amp;#43;gEAAwEBAQEBAQEBAQAAAAAAAAECAwQFBgcICQoLEQACAQIEBAMEBwUEBAABAncAAQIDEQQFITEGEkFRB2FxEyIygQgUQpGhscEJIzNS8BVictEKFiQ04SXxFxgZGiYnKCkqNTY3ODk6Q0RFRkdISUpTVFVWV1hZWmNkZWZnaGlqc3R1dnd4eXqCg4SFhoeIiYqSk5SVlpeYmZqio6Slpqeoqaqys7S1tre4ubrCw8TFxsfIycrS09TV1tfY2dri4&amp;#43;Tl5ufo6ery8/T19vf4&amp;#43;fr/2gAMAwEAAhEDEQA/AK6OougcFQDyP1/xrULb4mjPXjFZCsBqMShdyyjb9M55qV50tVheR2RQvDdfzqmtCU9SG8doLsB8Bt3yf7We36frVvSbqax8QRyxuV3f3T2IxVbXUMlqsqgNtO8nHTHX&amp;#43;tJBcgXlrKcjcCuRz9KSdinqRSzGxlinI6SbR7cdK2ZoLS709YvKAGCyNnODnvmsLWv9Qv8A18ity2/48U/3W/nWhmUIJwH8qUBsHJHY9jVO6gkgZlhceUp&amp;#43;RCOVPoD&amp;#43;BqRf&amp;#43;P1v&amp;#43;Bf&amp;#43;hU&amp;#43;9&amp;#43;&amp;#43;3/AF0X&amp;#43;tS0Uj//2Q=="
class="lazy"
data-src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2010/images/-000_hu_6652cec6c6ed79c6.png"
&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script&gt;
if (!jQuery) {
alert("jquery is not loaded");
}
$( document ).ready(() =&gt; {
const gallery = $("#gallery-3b1b40e27d9adb7835f474760f60f4fd-0");
let swipeboxInstance = null;
gallery.on('jg.complete', () =&gt; {
$(() =&gt; {
$('.lazy').Lazy({
visibleOnly: true,
afterLoad: element =&gt; element.css({filter: "none", transition: "filter 1.0s ease-in-out"})
});
});
swipeboxInstance = $('.galleryImg').swipebox(
jQuery.extend({},
{ }
)
);
});
gallery.justifiedGallery({
rowHeight : "150",
margins : "5",
border : 0,
randomize : false ,
waitThumbnailsLoad : false,
lastRow : "justify",
captions : false,
});
});
&lt;/script&gt;</description></item><item><title>Summer Tour 2009</title><link>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/</guid><description>&lt;img src="YAYAYA/YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/0.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Summer Tour 2009" /&gt;&lt;h2 id="members-who-attended"&gt;Members who attended
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alistair Brash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simon Partridge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tom Coyne&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brigette Atkins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Joergen Myrtroeen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ed Poore&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charlene Lawton&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lizzie Wilkins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob Dean&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jonathan Hazell&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-1"&gt;Day 1
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the 10 tour members departing from different airports throughout the country everyone
arrived in Alicante Airport, Spain at roughly the same time (varying between 09:30am and 11am
local time). The first port of call was the car rental station where two hire cars were collected. One
being upgraded two stages for free because they didn&amp;rsquo;t have the booked car, thus providing us with
a 7-seater, dubbed the &amp;ldquo;win-car&amp;rdquo; for the rest of the tour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A (theoretical) hour later with some exploration of the Spanish coast led to everyone arriving in the
first villa of the stay, graciously provided by Joergen. Unloading and lunch ensued then reloading
into the cars and off to the beach to find one of the deep-water-soloing crags mentioned in the
guide-books. After some non-existent right-turns eventually an alternative was found and the fun
began.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For many of our members this was the first time they had been deep-water-soloing, climbing
without ropes above the sea, the day ended with a spot of tombstoning from the top of the cliff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-2"&gt;Day 2
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We traveled the short journey down the coast to Sierra de Toix to climb at a place called Toix TV.
After spending thirty minutes driving around the maze of holiday homes, we finally reached the crag
as it began to pour with rain. Climbing began, regardless, with several routes being lead including a
7a (very hard!) lead by Joergen. After this, Tom set off on a route –accessed via a dodgy rope bridge -
but ended up climbing past the lower-off, resulting in a run out traverse and a scramble to safety!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-3"&gt;Day 3
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We set off to Forrada in search of some quality climbing. Four hours later, after driving through
continuous hairpins, we reached a track described in the guide book as “rough in places”. This was
discovered to be something of an understatement!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The climbing at Forrada was fantastic and turned out to be well worth the journey. At least it was
until the monsoon arrived and forced us to shelter in a cave for the next hour, waiting for the rock to
dry. The heavy downpour turned out to be a daily occurrence and always coincided with Brigette
being stranded halfway up a lead. Joergen and Jacob managed to find some more difficult climbing
in an area sheltered from the storm. One particular route (Starman, 7a+) provided them with
conversation for the rest of the week. The journey back to the villa that evening was considerably
shorter due to the saturated soil which allowed us to ‘mud-plane’ back down the track from the
crag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-4"&gt;Day 4
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/1.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We headed back to the Sierra de Toix region but this time to Toix Ouest. Once again it rained in the
afternoon (there is a theme here) so we went back to the villa for lunch. The plan for the afternoon
was to head a short distance from the villa to Echo Valley. Unfortunately we got lost and drove half
an hour into the valleys, ending up at a place that wasn’t in the guide book but did come
recommended by a woman in stripy yellow trousers (clearly a climber). The boulderers among the
group made friends with a local man-of -the-crag who showed them the best traverse in the area
whilst chain smoking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-5"&gt;Day 5
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the antics of the previous three days, it was decided we should take a rest day. We had a lazy
morning by the pool followed by some deep water soloing in the afternoon. It was warmer in the sea
than out, so we swam about before coming home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/2.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/3.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-6"&gt;Day 6
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was our first trip to Sella (the biggest crag in the area) and we were not disappointed. The
routes were amazing. Tom and Brigette started a multipitch but true to form, when Brigette’s
involved, it began to rain as soon as they had both reached the first belay. After much commotion
and a variety of problems, they both abseiled down to safety. Meanwhile, diehard boulderer, Jacob
gets his head for heights as he takes his first fall whilst leading (after much bullying from Alistair and
Joergen).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fresher took a less active approach to the day and made a hammock at the base of the crag. His
creativity got the better of him later in the day when he attempted to make a zip line into the
swimming pool back at the villa. Fail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-7"&gt;Day 7
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We went to Echo Playa and for the first time since the first day, the sun was out. Quickly, we realized
that it was too hot and hoped for mild temperatures once again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of us went off to do ‘traditional’ climbing, whilst the others climbed sport routes. By lunch
time everyone was far too hot, so we decided to go back to the villa for a siesta.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, Fresher had a brilliant idea: He built a raft from water bottles and set sail in the
swimming pool. However, his success was short lived as Tom and Jacob bombed him, sinking his
raft!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That night, we moved to a villa in the mountains. Whilst everyone was packing, Fresher managed to
put a large dent in the car. However, he did fix it with his trusty plunger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-8"&gt;Day 8
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jacob, Alistair and Joergen climbed a three pitch route. Joergen, however, left his shoes at home, so
they ended up sharing two pairs between three people, swapping shoes for each pitch. In the
meantime, Charlene and Simon completed their first lead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/4.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That evening ICMC stormed Benidom! We saw the delights that were on offer, Sticky Vicki, The
Mediteraneun Bar to name but two&amp;hellip; We opted for the beach. Simon and the girls somehow ended
up in the sea, partly clothed and Fresher got buried. ICMC returned home, distinctly weter and
sandier than before and settled down for a nice bowl of carrot curry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/5.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="YAYAYA/p/summer-tour-2009/images/6.jpg" width="300"&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-9"&gt;Day 9
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back to Sierra de Toix again! Spurred on by the previous days multipitch, Fresher, Simon and Brigette
set off on a three pitch excursion. Charlene climbed a route with a rope that was too short to be
lowered off, so had to do some imaginative maneuvers to get down!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By this stage everyone else was bored with Toix and decided to do some more deep-water-soloing,
leaving Fresher and co halfway up their multipitch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-10"&gt;Day 10
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was our last full day of climbing, so we decided to go back to Sella as it was so good before. Tom
and Ed managed to complete the multipitch that they got rained off last time. Charlene and Simon
continued to tick off a number of lead climbs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During late afternoon, there was a massive downpour which resulted in half the group running for
cover and leaving everyone else to pack up all the gear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="day-11"&gt;Day 11
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last day! The weather was worse than ever, it was raining when we woke up! We packed and
cleaned the house before driving towards Alicante. When we got there it was far too wet to sit on
the beach, so what would a group of university students do in Alicante for a day? Obviously we
found the nearest Toys ’R’Us and set about trying to play with every toy in the shop!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the tour went very well. I would not have made any fundamental changes to the way
it ran, things that could be improved in the future are small organizational things such as being
better at buying the correct amount of food for a large number of people. Financially, the tour broke
even. And a good time was had by all! The only thing that did not go as planned was the fact that it
rained so often! But that being said, we went climbing every day and still had an amazing time.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>